[
    {
        "question": "1 + 1",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 2",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 3",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 4",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 5",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 6",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 7",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 8",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 9",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 10",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 11",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 12",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 13",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 14",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 15",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 1",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 2",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 3",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 4",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 5",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 6",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 7",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 8",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 9",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 10",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 11",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 12",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 13",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 14",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 15",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 1",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 2",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 3",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 4",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 5",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 6",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 7",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 8",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 9",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 10",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 11",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 12",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 13",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 14",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 15",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 1",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 2",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 3",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 4",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 5",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 6",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 7",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 8",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 9",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 10",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 11",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 12",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 13",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 14",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 15",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 1",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 2",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 3",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 4",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 5",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 6",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 7",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 8",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 9",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 10",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 11",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 12",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 13",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 14",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 15",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 1",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 2",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 3",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 4",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 5",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 6",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 7",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 8",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 9",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 10",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 11",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 12",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 13",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 14",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 15",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 1",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 2",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 3",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 4",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 5",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 6",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 7",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 8",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 9",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 10",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 11",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 12",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 13",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 14",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 15",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 1",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 2",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 3",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 4",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 5",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 6",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 7",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 8",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 9",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 10",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 11",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 12",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 13",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 14",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 15",
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 1",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 2",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 3",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 4",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 5",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 6",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 7",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 8",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 9",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 10",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 11",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 12",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 13",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 14",
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 15",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 1",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 2",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 3",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 4",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 5",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 6",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 7",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 8",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 9",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 10",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 11",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 12",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 13",
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 14",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 15",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 1",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 2",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 3",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 4",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 5",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 6",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 7",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 8",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 9",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 10",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 11",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 12",
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 13",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 14",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 15",
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 1",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 2",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 3",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 4",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 5",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 6",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 7",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 8",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 9",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 10",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 11",
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 12",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 13",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 14",
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 15",
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 1",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 2",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 3",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 4",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 5",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 6",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 7",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 8",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 9",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 10",
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 11",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 12",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 13",
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 14",
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 15",
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 1",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 2",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 3",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 4",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 5",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 6",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 7",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 8",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 9",
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 10",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 11",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 12",
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 13",
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 14",
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 15",
        "answer": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 1",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 2",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 3",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 4",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 5",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 6",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 7",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 8",
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 9",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 10",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 11",
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 12",
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 13",
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 14",
        "answer": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 15",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 1",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 2",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 3",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 4",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 5",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 6",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 7",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 8",
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 9",
        "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 10",
        "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 11",
        "answer": "-10"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 12",
        "answer": "-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 13",
        "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 14",
        "answer": "-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 15",
        "answer": "-14"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 1",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 2",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 3",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 4",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 5",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 6",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 7",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 8",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 9",
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 10",
        "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 11",
        "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 12",
        "answer": "-10"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 13",
        "answer": "-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 14",
        "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 15",
        "answer": "-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 1",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 2",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 3",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 4",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 5",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 6",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 7",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 8",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 9",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 10",
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 11",
        "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 12",
        "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 13",
        "answer": "-10"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 14",
        "answer": "-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 15",
        "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 1",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 2",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 3",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 4",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 5",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 6",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 7",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 8",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 9",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 10",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 11",
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 12",
        "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 13",
        "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 14",
        "answer": "-10"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 15",
        "answer": "-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 1",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 2",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 3",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 4",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 5",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 6",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 7",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 8",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 9",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 10",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 11",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 12",
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 13",
        "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 14",
        "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 15",
        "answer": "-10"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 1",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 2",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 3",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 4",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 5",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 6",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 7",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 8",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 9",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 10",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 11",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 12",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 13",
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 14",
        "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 15",
        "answer": "-9"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 1",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 2",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 3",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 4",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 5",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 6",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 7",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 8",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 9",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 10",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 11",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 12",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 13",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 14",
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 15",
        "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 1",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 2",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 3",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 4",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 5",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 6",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 7",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 8",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 9",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 10",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 11",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 12",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 13",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 14",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 15",
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 1",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 2",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 3",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 4",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 5",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 6",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 7",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 8",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 9",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 10",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 11",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 12",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 13",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 14",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 15",
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 1",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 2",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 3",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 4",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 5",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 6",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 7",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 8",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 9",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 10",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 11",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 12",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 13",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 14",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 15",
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 1",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 2",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 3",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 4",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 5",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 6",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 7",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 8",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 9",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 10",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 11",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 12",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 13",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 14",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 15",
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 1",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 2",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 3",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 4",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 5",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 6",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 7",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 8",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 9",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 10",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 11",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 12",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 13",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 14",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 15",
        "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 1",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 2",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 3",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 4",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 5",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 6",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 7",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 8",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 9",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 10",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 11",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 12",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 13",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 14",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 15",
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 1",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 2",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 3",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 4",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 5",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 6",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 7",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 8",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 9",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 10",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 11",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 12",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 13",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 14",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 15",
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 1",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 2",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 3",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 4",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 5",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 6",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 7",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 8",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 9",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 10",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 11",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 12",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 13",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 14",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 15",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 1",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 2",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 3",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 4",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 5",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 6",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 7",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 8",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 9",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 10",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 11",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 12",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 13",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 14",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 15",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 1",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 2",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 3",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 4",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 5",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 6",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 7",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 8",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 9",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 10",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 11",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 12",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 13",
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 14",
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 15",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 1",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 2",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 3",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 4",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 5",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 6",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 7",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 8",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 9",
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 10",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 11",
        "answer": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 12",
        "answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 13",
        "answer": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 14",
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 15",
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 1",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 2",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 3",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 4",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 5",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 6",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 7",
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 8",
        "answer": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 9",
        "answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 10",
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 11",
        "answer": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 12",
        "answer": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 13",
        "answer": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 14",
        "answer": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 15",
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 1",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 2",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 3",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 4",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 5",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 6",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 7",
        "answer": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 8",
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 9",
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 10",
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 11",
        "answer": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 12",
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 13",
        "answer": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 14",
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 15",
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 1",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 2",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 3",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 4",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 5",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 6",
        "answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 7",
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 8",
        "answer": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 9",
        "answer": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 10",
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 11",
        "answer": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 12",
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 13",
        "answer": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 14",
        "answer": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 15",
        "answer": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 1",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 2",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 3",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 4",
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 5",
        "answer": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 6",
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 7",
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 8",
        "answer": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 9",
        "answer": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 10",
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 11",
        "answer": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 12",
        "answer": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 13",
        "answer": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 14",
        "answer": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 15",
        "answer": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 1",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 2",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 3",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 4",
        "answer": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 5",
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 6",
        "answer": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 7",
        "answer": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 8",
        "answer": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 9",
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 10",
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 11",
        "answer": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 12",
        "answer": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 13",
        "answer": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 14",
        "answer": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 15",
        "answer": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 1",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 2",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 3",
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 4",
        "answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 5",
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 6",
        "answer": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 7",
        "answer": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 8",
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 9",
        "answer": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 10",
        "answer": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 11",
        "answer": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 12",
        "answer": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 13",
        "answer": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 14",
        "answer": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 15",
        "answer": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 1",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 2",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 3",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 4",
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 5",
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 6",
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 7",
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 8",
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 9",
        "answer": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 10",
        "answer": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 11",
        "answer": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 12",
        "answer": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 13",
        "answer": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 14",
        "answer": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 15",
        "answer": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 1",
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 2",
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 3",
        "answer": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 4",
        "answer": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 5",
        "answer": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 6",
        "answer": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 7",
        "answer": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 8",
        "answer": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 9",
        "answer": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 10",
        "answer": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 11",
        "answer": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 12",
        "answer": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 13",
        "answer": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 14",
        "answer": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 15",
        "answer": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 1",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 2",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 3",
        "answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 4",
        "answer": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 5",
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 6",
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 7",
        "answer": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 8",
        "answer": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 9",
        "answer": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 10",
        "answer": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 11",
        "answer": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 12",
        "answer": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 13",
        "answer": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 14",
        "answer": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 15",
        "answer": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 1",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 2",
        "answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 3",
        "answer": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 4",
        "answer": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 5",
        "answer": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 6",
        "answer": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 7",
        "answer": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 8",
        "answer": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 9",
        "answer": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 10",
        "answer": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 11",
        "answer": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 12",
        "answer": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 13",
        "answer": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 14",
        "answer": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 15",
        "answer": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 1",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 2",
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 3",
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 4",
        "answer": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 5",
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 6",
        "answer": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 7",
        "answer": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 8",
        "answer": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 9",
        "answer": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 10",
        "answer": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 11",
        "answer": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 12",
        "answer": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 13",
        "answer": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 14",
        "answer": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 15",
        "answer": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 1",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 2",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 3",
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 4",
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 5",
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 6",
        "answer": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 7",
        "answer": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 8",
        "answer": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 9",
        "answer": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 10",
        "answer": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 11",
        "answer": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 12",
        "answer": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 13",
        "answer": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 14",
        "answer": "210"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 15",
        "answer": "225"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 1",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 2",
        "answer": "0.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 3",
        "answer": "0.3333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 4",
        "answer": "0.25"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 5",
        "answer": "0.2"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 6",
        "answer": "0.16666666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 7",
        "answer": "0.14285714285714285"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 8",
        "answer": "0.125"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 9",
        "answer": "0.1111111111111111"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 10",
        "answer": "0.1"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 11",
        "answer": "0.09090909090909091"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 12",
        "answer": "0.08333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 13",
        "answer": "0.07692307692307693"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 14",
        "answer": "0.07142857142857142"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 / 15",
        "answer": "0.06666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 1",
        "answer": "2.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 2",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 3",
        "answer": "0.6666666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 4",
        "answer": "0.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 5",
        "answer": "0.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 6",
        "answer": "0.3333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 7",
        "answer": "0.2857142857142857"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 8",
        "answer": "0.25"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 9",
        "answer": "0.2222222222222222"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 10",
        "answer": "0.2"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 11",
        "answer": "0.18181818181818182"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 12",
        "answer": "0.16666666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 13",
        "answer": "0.15384615384615385"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 14",
        "answer": "0.14285714285714285"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 / 15",
        "answer": "0.13333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 1",
        "answer": "3.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 2",
        "answer": "1.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 3",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 4",
        "answer": "0.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 5",
        "answer": "0.6"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 6",
        "answer": "0.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 7",
        "answer": "0.42857142857142855"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 8",
        "answer": "0.375"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 9",
        "answer": "0.3333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 10",
        "answer": "0.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 11",
        "answer": "0.2727272727272727"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 12",
        "answer": "0.25"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 13",
        "answer": "0.23076923076923078"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 14",
        "answer": "0.21428571428571427"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 / 15",
        "answer": "0.2"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 1",
        "answer": "4.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 2",
        "answer": "2.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 3",
        "answer": "1.3333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 4",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 5",
        "answer": "0.8"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 6",
        "answer": "0.6666666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 7",
        "answer": "0.5714285714285714"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 8",
        "answer": "0.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 9",
        "answer": "0.4444444444444444"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 10",
        "answer": "0.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 11",
        "answer": "0.36363636363636365"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 12",
        "answer": "0.3333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 13",
        "answer": "0.3076923076923077"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 14",
        "answer": "0.2857142857142857"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 / 15",
        "answer": "0.26666666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 1",
        "answer": "5.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 2",
        "answer": "2.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 3",
        "answer": "1.6666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 4",
        "answer": "1.25"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 5",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 6",
        "answer": "0.8333333333333334"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 7",
        "answer": "0.7142857142857143"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 8",
        "answer": "0.625"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 9",
        "answer": "0.5555555555555556"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 10",
        "answer": "0.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 11",
        "answer": "0.45454545454545453"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 12",
        "answer": "0.4166666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 13",
        "answer": "0.38461538461538464"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 14",
        "answer": "0.35714285714285715"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 / 15",
        "answer": "0.3333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 1",
        "answer": "6.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 2",
        "answer": "3.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 3",
        "answer": "2.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 4",
        "answer": "1.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 5",
        "answer": "1.2"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 6",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 7",
        "answer": "0.8571428571428571"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 8",
        "answer": "0.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 9",
        "answer": "0.6666666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 10",
        "answer": "0.6"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 11",
        "answer": "0.5454545454545454"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 12",
        "answer": "0.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 13",
        "answer": "0.46153846153846156"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 14",
        "answer": "0.42857142857142855"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 / 15",
        "answer": "0.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 1",
        "answer": "7.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 2",
        "answer": "3.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 3",
        "answer": "2.3333333333333335"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 4",
        "answer": "1.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 5",
        "answer": "1.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 6",
        "answer": "1.1666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 7",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 8",
        "answer": "0.875"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 9",
        "answer": "0.7777777777777778"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 10",
        "answer": "0.7"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 11",
        "answer": "0.6363636363636364"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 12",
        "answer": "0.5833333333333334"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 13",
        "answer": "0.5384615384615384"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 14",
        "answer": "0.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 / 15",
        "answer": "0.4666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 1",
        "answer": "8.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 2",
        "answer": "4.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 3",
        "answer": "2.6666666666666665"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 4",
        "answer": "2.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 5",
        "answer": "1.6"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 6",
        "answer": "1.3333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 7",
        "answer": "1.1428571428571428"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 8",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 9",
        "answer": "0.8888888888888888"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 10",
        "answer": "0.8"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 11",
        "answer": "0.7272727272727273"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 12",
        "answer": "0.6666666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 13",
        "answer": "0.6153846153846154"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 14",
        "answer": "0.5714285714285714"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 / 15",
        "answer": "0.5333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 1",
        "answer": "9.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 2",
        "answer": "4.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 3",
        "answer": "3.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 4",
        "answer": "2.25"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 5",
        "answer": "1.8"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 6",
        "answer": "1.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 7",
        "answer": "1.2857142857142858"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 8",
        "answer": "1.125"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 9",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 10",
        "answer": "0.9"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 11",
        "answer": "0.8181818181818182"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 12",
        "answer": "0.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 13",
        "answer": "0.6923076923076923"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 14",
        "answer": "0.6428571428571429"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 / 15",
        "answer": "0.6"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 1",
        "answer": "10.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 2",
        "answer": "5.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 3",
        "answer": "3.3333333333333335"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 4",
        "answer": "2.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 5",
        "answer": "2.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 6",
        "answer": "1.6666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 7",
        "answer": "1.4285714285714286"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 8",
        "answer": "1.25"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 9",
        "answer": "1.1111111111111112"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 10",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 11",
        "answer": "0.9090909090909091"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 12",
        "answer": "0.8333333333333334"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 13",
        "answer": "0.7692307692307693"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 14",
        "answer": "0.7142857142857143"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 / 15",
        "answer": "0.6666666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 1",
        "answer": "11.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 2",
        "answer": "5.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 3",
        "answer": "3.6666666666666665"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 4",
        "answer": "2.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 5",
        "answer": "2.2"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 6",
        "answer": "1.8333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 7",
        "answer": "1.5714285714285714"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 8",
        "answer": "1.375"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 9",
        "answer": "1.2222222222222223"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 10",
        "answer": "1.1"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 11",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 12",
        "answer": "0.9166666666666666"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 13",
        "answer": "0.8461538461538461"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 14",
        "answer": "0.7857142857142857"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 / 15",
        "answer": "0.7333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 1",
        "answer": "12.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 2",
        "answer": "6.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 3",
        "answer": "4.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 4",
        "answer": "3.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 5",
        "answer": "2.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 6",
        "answer": "2.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 7",
        "answer": "1.7142857142857142"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 8",
        "answer": "1.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 9",
        "answer": "1.3333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 10",
        "answer": "1.2"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 11",
        "answer": "1.0909090909090908"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 12",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 13",
        "answer": "0.9230769230769231"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 14",
        "answer": "0.8571428571428571"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 / 15",
        "answer": "0.8"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 1",
        "answer": "13.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 2",
        "answer": "6.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 3",
        "answer": "4.333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 4",
        "answer": "3.25"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 5",
        "answer": "2.6"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 6",
        "answer": "2.1666666666666665"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 7",
        "answer": "1.8571428571428572"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 8",
        "answer": "1.625"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 9",
        "answer": "1.4444444444444444"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 10",
        "answer": "1.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 11",
        "answer": "1.1818181818181819"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 12",
        "answer": "1.0833333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 13",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 14",
        "answer": "0.9285714285714286"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 / 15",
        "answer": "0.8666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 1",
        "answer": "14.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 2",
        "answer": "7.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 3",
        "answer": "4.666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 4",
        "answer": "3.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 5",
        "answer": "2.8"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 6",
        "answer": "2.3333333333333335"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 7",
        "answer": "2.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 8",
        "answer": "1.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 9",
        "answer": "1.5555555555555556"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 10",
        "answer": "1.4"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 11",
        "answer": "1.2727272727272727"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 12",
        "answer": "1.1666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 13",
        "answer": "1.0769230769230769"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 14",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 / 15",
        "answer": "0.9333333333333333"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 1",
        "answer": "15.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 2",
        "answer": "7.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 3",
        "answer": "5.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 4",
        "answer": "3.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 5",
        "answer": "3.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 6",
        "answer": "2.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 7",
        "answer": "2.142857142857143"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 8",
        "answer": "1.875"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 9",
        "answer": "1.6666666666666667"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 10",
        "answer": "1.5"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 11",
        "answer": "1.3636363636363635"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 12",
        "answer": "1.25"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 13",
        "answer": "1.1538461538461537"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 14",
        "answer": "1.0714285714285714"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 / 15",
        "answer": "1.0"
    },
    {
        "question": "9921 + 3871",
        "answer": "Add 9921 and 3871 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 13792"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 37",
        "answer": "Add 57 and 37 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 94"
    },
    {
        "question": "42059 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 42059 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 42066"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 93 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 120"
    },
    {
        "question": "85842 + 500",
        "answer": "Add 85842 and 500 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 86342"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 10",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 10 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 107"
    },
    {
        "question": "464 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 464 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 492"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 69 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 97"
    },
    {
        "question": "30697 + 253",
        "answer": "Add 30697 and 253 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 30950"
    },
    {
        "question": "4139 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 4139 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4148"
    },
    {
        "question": "30 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 30 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 33"
    },
    {
        "question": "880 + 591",
        "answer": "Add 880 and 591 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1471"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 24",
        "answer": "Add 90 and 24 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 114"
    },
    {
        "question": "3279 + 37",
        "answer": "Add 3279 and 37 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3316"
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 19 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 1 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 35"
    },
    {
        "question": "27505 + 270",
        "answer": "Add 27505 and 270 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 27775"
    },
    {
        "question": "65393 + 376",
        "answer": "Add 65393 and 376 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 65769"
    },
    {
        "question": "8662 + 8402",
        "answer": "Add 8662 and 8402 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 17064"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 137"
    },
    {
        "question": "74251 + 2820",
        "answer": "Add 74251 and 2820 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 77071"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 67",
        "answer": "Add 90 and 67 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 157"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 62",
        "answer": "Add 79 and 62 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 141"
    },
    {
        "question": "758 + 61",
        "answer": "Add 758 and 61 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 819"
    },
    {
        "question": "588 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 588 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 593"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 12 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 15"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 77",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 77 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 168"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 59",
        "answer": "Add 92 and 59 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 151"
    },
    {
        "question": "34832 + 8679",
        "answer": "Add 34832 and 8679 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 7 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 8 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 43511"
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 39 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 41"
    },
    {
        "question": "609 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 609 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 613"
    },
    {
        "question": "620 + 246",
        "answer": "Add 620 and 246 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 866"
    },
    {
        "question": "50702 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 50702 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 50707"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 45 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 68"
    },
    {
        "question": "720 + 292",
        "answer": "Add 720 and 292 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1012"
    },
    {
        "question": "960 + 482",
        "answer": "Add 960 and 482 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1442"
    },
    {
        "question": "9956 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 9956 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9961"
    },
    {
        "question": "3577 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 3577 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3593"
    },
    {
        "question": "411 + 94",
        "answer": "Add 411 and 94 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 505"
    },
    {
        "question": "193 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 193 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 196"
    },
    {
        "question": "8308 + 927",
        "answer": "Add 8308 and 927 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9235"
    },
    {
        "question": "52822 + 51565",
        "answer": "Add 52822 and 51565 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 104387"
    },
    {
        "question": "83572 + 48310",
        "answer": "Add 83572 and 48310 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 131882"
    },
    {
        "question": "73971 + 6397",
        "answer": "Add 73971 and 6397 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 6 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 80368"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 52",
        "answer": "Add 69 and 52 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 121"
    },
    {
        "question": "72088 + 46",
        "answer": "Add 72088 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 72134"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 58",
        "answer": "Add 67 and 58 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 125"
    },
    {
        "question": "3456 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 3456 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3462"
    },
    {
        "question": "5176 + 635",
        "answer": "Add 5176 and 635 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 6 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5811"
    },
    {
        "question": "88717 + 79",
        "answer": "Add 88717 and 79 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 7 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 88796"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 72",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 72 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 163"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 85 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 134"
    },
    {
        "question": "36479 + 52",
        "answer": "Add 36479 and 52 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 36531"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 74 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 123"
    },
    {
        "question": "3680 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 3680 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3688"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 45",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 45 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 113"
    },
    {
        "question": "975 + 737",
        "answer": "Add 975 and 737 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1712"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 92"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 59",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 59 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 127"
    },
    {
        "question": "7994 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 7994 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7998"
    },
    {
        "question": "97777 + 525",
        "answer": "Add 97777 and 525 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 98302"
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 10",
        "answer": "Add 19 and 10 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 29"
    },
    {
        "question": "936 + 375",
        "answer": "Add 936 and 375 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 7 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1311"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 19",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 19 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 113"
    },
    {
        "question": "8928 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 8928 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8962"
    },
    {
        "question": "402 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 402 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 408"
    },
    {
        "question": "762 + 669",
        "answer": "Add 762 and 669 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1431"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 115"
    },
    {
        "question": "3108 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 3108 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3151"
    },
    {
        "question": "47774 + 8058",
        "answer": "Add 47774 and 8058 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 55832"
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 19",
        "answer": "Add 64 and 19 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 83"
    },
    {
        "question": "79096 + 82",
        "answer": "Add 79096 and 82 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 79178"
    },
    {
        "question": "603 + 154",
        "answer": "Add 603 and 154 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 757"
    },
    {
        "question": "917 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 917 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 923"
    },
    {
        "question": "48428 + 31326",
        "answer": "Add 48428 and 31326 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 79754"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 40",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 40 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 131"
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 20",
        "answer": "Add 44 and 20 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 64"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 59 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 86"
    },
    {
        "question": "961 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 961 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 968"
    },
    {
        "question": "5394 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 5394 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5400"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 99 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "708 + 63",
        "answer": "Add 708 and 63 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 771"
    },
    {
        "question": "341 + 282",
        "answer": "Add 341 and 282 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 623"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 96"
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 61",
        "answer": "Add 63 and 61 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 124"
    },
    {
        "question": "4150 + 3828",
        "answer": "Add 4150 and 3828 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7978"
    },
    {
        "question": "737 + 247",
        "answer": "Add 737 and 247 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 4 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 984"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 119"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 51 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 52"
    },
    {
        "question": "55685 + 51",
        "answer": "Add 55685 and 51 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 55736"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 61",
        "answer": "Add 69 and 61 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 130"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 64",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 64 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 139"
    },
    {
        "question": "42 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 42 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 70"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 37 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 39"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 93 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 116"
    },
    {
        "question": "8396 + 99",
        "answer": "Add 8396 and 99 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 1 = 19 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8495"
    },
    {
        "question": "91386 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 91386 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 91389"
    },
    {
        "question": "58098 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 58098 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 58102"
    },
    {
        "question": "2358 + 874",
        "answer": "Add 2358 and 874 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 8 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3232"
    },
    {
        "question": "52734 + 82",
        "answer": "Add 52734 and 82 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 52816"
    },
    {
        "question": "481 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 481 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 485"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 83 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 111"
    },
    {
        "question": "919 + 594",
        "answer": "Add 919 and 594 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 9 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1513"
    },
    {
        "question": "64379 + 64026",
        "answer": "Add 64379 and 64026 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 128405"
    },
    {
        "question": "1592 + 53",
        "answer": "Add 1592 and 53 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1645"
    },
    {
        "question": "591 + 562",
        "answer": "Add 591 and 562 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1153"
    },
    {
        "question": "6154 + 75",
        "answer": "Add 6154 and 75 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6229"
    },
    {
        "question": "58145 + 3207",
        "answer": "Add 58145 and 3207 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 61352"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 81 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 86"
    },
    {
        "question": "2430 + 37",
        "answer": "Add 2430 and 37 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2467"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 93 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 127"
    },
    {
        "question": "96729 + 93",
        "answer": "Add 96729 and 93 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 96822"
    },
    {
        "question": "3594 + 32",
        "answer": "Add 3594 and 32 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3626"
    },
    {
        "question": "587 + 185",
        "answer": "Add 587 and 185 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 772"
    },
    {
        "question": "6184 + 1923",
        "answer": "Add 6184 and 1923 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 9 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 8107"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 56",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 56 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 124"
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 44 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53"
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 26 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 43"
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 12",
        "answer": "Add 48 and 12 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 60"
    },
    {
        "question": "20414 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 20414 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 20422"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 22",
        "answer": "Add 71 and 22 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 93"
    },
    {
        "question": "6111 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 6111 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6117"
    },
    {
        "question": "6664 + 4206",
        "answer": "Add 6664 and 4206 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10870"
    },
    {
        "question": "655 + 55",
        "answer": "Add 655 and 55 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 710"
    },
    {
        "question": "535 + 403",
        "answer": "Add 535 and 403 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 938"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 115"
    },
    {
        "question": "523 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 523 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 532"
    },
    {
        "question": "737 + 53",
        "answer": "Add 737 and 53 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 5 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 790"
    },
    {
        "question": "7126 + 534",
        "answer": "Add 7126 and 534 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7660"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 14",
        "answer": "Add 54 and 14 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 68"
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 55",
        "answer": "Add 65 and 55 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 120"
    },
    {
        "question": "665 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 665 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 674"
    },
    {
        "question": "9893 + 75",
        "answer": "Add 9893 and 75 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9968"
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 54",
        "answer": "Add 118 and 54 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 5 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 172"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 22",
        "answer": "Add 27 and 22 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 49"
    },
    {
        "question": "8156 + 885",
        "answer": "Add 8156 and 885 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 8 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 8 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9041"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 81 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 84"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 58 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 60"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 50 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 55"
    },
    {
        "question": "3631 + 33",
        "answer": "Add 3631 and 33 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3664"
    },
    {
        "question": "95021 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 95021 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 95025"
    },
    {
        "question": "9606 + 8040",
        "answer": "Add 9606 and 8040 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 17646"
    },
    {
        "question": "508 + 382",
        "answer": "Add 508 and 382 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 890"
    },
    {
        "question": "8056 + 6140",
        "answer": "Add 8056 and 6140 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 14196"
    },
    {
        "question": "9091 + 4240",
        "answer": "Add 9091 and 4240 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 13331"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 26",
        "answer": "Add 36 and 26 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 62"
    },
    {
        "question": "4980 + 64",
        "answer": "Add 4980 and 64 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5044"
    },
    {
        "question": "781 + 639",
        "answer": "Add 781 and 639 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1420"
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 65 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 100"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 42",
        "answer": "Add 47 and 42 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 89"
    },
    {
        "question": "939 + 410",
        "answer": "Add 939 and 410 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1349"
    },
    {
        "question": "3380 + 2376",
        "answer": "Add 3380 and 2376 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 5756"
    },
    {
        "question": "53749 + 67",
        "answer": "Add 53749 and 67 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53816"
    },
    {
        "question": "247 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 247 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 297"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 71",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 71 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 155"
    },
    {
        "question": "863 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 863 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 892"
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 46 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 80"
    },
    {
        "question": "83425 + 426",
        "answer": "Add 83425 and 426 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 83851"
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 25 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 48"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 114"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 45",
        "answer": "Add 89 and 45 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 134"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 14",
        "answer": "Add 88 and 14 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "984 + 551",
        "answer": "Add 984 and 551 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1535"
    },
    {
        "question": "4865 + 11",
        "answer": "Add 4865 and 11 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4876"
    },
    {
        "question": "79826 + 7330",
        "answer": "Add 79826 and 7330 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 87156"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 63",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 63 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 150"
    },
    {
        "question": "99423 + 300",
        "answer": "Add 99423 and 300 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 99723"
    },
    {
        "question": "546 + 422",
        "answer": "Add 546 and 422 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 968"
    },
    {
        "question": "56116 + 83",
        "answer": "Add 56116 and 83 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 56199"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 81",
        "answer": "Add 86 and 81 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 167"
    },
    {
        "question": "455 + 451",
        "answer": "Add 455 and 451 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 906"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 60 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 88"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 12",
        "answer": "Add 50 and 12 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 62"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 42",
        "answer": "Add 47 and 42 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 89"
    },
    {
        "question": "76918 + 46",
        "answer": "Add 76918 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 4 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 76964"
    },
    {
        "question": "927 + 367",
        "answer": "Add 927 and 367 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1294"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 61",
        "answer": "Add 72 and 61 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 133"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 55",
        "answer": "Add 67 and 55 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 122"
    },
    {
        "question": "4798 + 2243",
        "answer": "Add 4798 and 2243 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7041"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 10",
        "answer": "Add 73 and 10 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 83"
    },
    {
        "question": "8122 + 2533",
        "answer": "Add 8122 and 2533 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10655"
    },
    {
        "question": "39273 + 9104",
        "answer": "Add 39273 and 9104 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 48377"
    },
    {
        "question": "84698 + 13668",
        "answer": "Add 84698 and 13668 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 98366"
    },
    {
        "question": "2920 + 165",
        "answer": "Add 2920 and 165 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3085"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 61 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 88"
    },
    {
        "question": "82240 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 82240 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 82283"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 99"
    },
    {
        "question": "29627 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 29627 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 29628"
    },
    {
        "question": "850 + 162",
        "answer": "Add 850 and 162 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1012"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 38 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 41"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 91"
    },
    {
        "question": "3794 + 22",
        "answer": "Add 3794 and 22 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3816"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 91",
        "answer": "Add 92 and 91 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 183"
    },
    {
        "question": "1212 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 1212 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1217"
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 12",
        "answer": "Add 44 and 12 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 56"
    },
    {
        "question": "716 + 488",
        "answer": "Add 716 and 488 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1204"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 37",
        "answer": "Add 67 and 37 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 104"
    },
    {
        "question": "12205 + 38",
        "answer": "Add 12205 and 38 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 8 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 12243"
    },
    {
        "question": "737 + 593",
        "answer": "Add 737 and 593 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 9 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1330"
    },
    {
        "question": "488 + 206",
        "answer": "Add 488 and 206 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 694"
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 13",
        "answer": "Add 44 and 13 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 57"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 89 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 95"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 13 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 14"
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 52",
        "answer": "Add 65 and 52 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 117"
    },
    {
        "question": "25191 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 25191 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 25198"
    },
    {
        "question": "5600 + 4492",
        "answer": "Add 5600 and 4492 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10092"
    },
    {
        "question": "49374 + 44",
        "answer": "Add 49374 and 44 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 49418"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 28 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 35"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 61 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 63"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 59 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 76"
    },
    {
        "question": "36773 + 8905",
        "answer": "Add 36773 and 8905 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 8 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45678"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 26",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 26 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 124"
    },
    {
        "question": "572 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 572 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 580"
    },
    {
        "question": "788 + 14",
        "answer": "Add 788 and 14 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 802"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 57 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 106"
    },
    {
        "question": "446 + 85",
        "answer": "Add 446 and 85 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 531"
    },
    {
        "question": "67234 + 269",
        "answer": "Add 67234 and 269 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 6 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 67503"
    },
    {
        "question": "3670 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 3670 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3679"
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 63",
        "answer": "Add 64 and 63 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 127"
    },
    {
        "question": "52 + 13",
        "answer": "Add 52 and 13 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 65"
    },
    {
        "question": "950 + 367",
        "answer": "Add 950 and 367 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1317"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 58 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 61"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 31",
        "answer": "Add 71 and 31 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 95 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 142"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 73 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 80"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 71",
        "answer": "Add 92 and 71 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 163"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 70 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 91"
    },
    {
        "question": "71913 + 20797",
        "answer": "Add 71913 and 20797 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 9 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 92710"
    },
    {
        "question": "990 + 743",
        "answer": "Add 990 and 743 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1733"
    },
    {
        "question": "30189 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 30189 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 30238"
    },
    {
        "question": "6112 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 6112 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6155"
    },
    {
        "question": "2660 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 2660 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2667"
    },
    {
        "question": "288 + 36",
        "answer": "Add 288 and 36 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 324"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 32",
        "answer": "Add 70 and 32 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "5252 + 33",
        "answer": "Add 5252 and 33 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5285"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 58 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 61"
    },
    {
        "question": "566 + 432",
        "answer": "Add 566 and 432 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 998"
    },
    {
        "question": "51079 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 51079 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 51087"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 61",
        "answer": "Add 61 and 61 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 122"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 48",
        "answer": "Add 73 and 48 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 121"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 121"
    },
    {
        "question": "53437 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 53437 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53440"
    },
    {
        "question": "97829 + 94406",
        "answer": "Add 97829 and 94406 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 9 + 1 = 19 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 192235"
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 20",
        "answer": "Add 77 and 20 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 97"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 70",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 70 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 157"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 41",
        "answer": "Add 59 and 41 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 100"
    },
    {
        "question": "432 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 432 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 440"
    },
    {
        "question": "93360 + 30",
        "answer": "Add 93360 and 30 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 93390"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 73 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 123"
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 82 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 85"
    },
    {
        "question": "22057 + 669",
        "answer": "Add 22057 and 669 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 6 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 22726"
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 60",
        "answer": "Add 196 and 60 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 256"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 84",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 84 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 171"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 56",
        "answer": "Add 90 and 56 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 146"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 88",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 88 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 179"
    },
    {
        "question": "953 + 809",
        "answer": "Add 953 and 809 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1762"
    },
    {
        "question": "1017 + 45",
        "answer": "Add 1017 and 45 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 4 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1062"
    },
    {
        "question": "817 + 458",
        "answer": "Add 817 and 458 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 5 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1275"
    },
    {
        "question": "1282 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 1282 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1287"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 52",
        "answer": "Add 54 and 52 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 106"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 22",
        "answer": "Add 80 and 22 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "789 + 453",
        "answer": "Add 789 and 453 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1242"
    },
    {
        "question": "34385 + 8433",
        "answer": "Add 34385 and 8433 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 4 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 42818"
    },
    {
        "question": "386 + 269",
        "answer": "Add 386 and 269 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 655"
    },
    {
        "question": "8076 + 11",
        "answer": "Add 8076 and 11 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8087"
    },
    {
        "question": "63593 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 63593 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 63595"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 10",
        "answer": "Add 58 and 10 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 68"
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 42",
        "answer": "Add 63 and 42 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 105"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 26",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 26 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 110"
    },
    {
        "question": "87412 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 87412 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 87416"
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 46 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 89"
    },
    {
        "question": "4674 + 4217",
        "answer": "Add 4674 and 4217 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 8891"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 56 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 58"
    },
    {
        "question": "51896 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 51896 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 51901"
    },
    {
        "question": "90972 + 82782",
        "answer": "Add 90972 and 82782 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 173754"
    },
    {
        "question": "66629 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 66629 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 66647"
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 12",
        "answer": "Add 24 and 12 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 36"
    },
    {
        "question": "6292 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 6292 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6301"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 46",
        "answer": "Add 54 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 100"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 67 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 75"
    },
    {
        "question": "80071 + 66496",
        "answer": "Add 80071 and 66496 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 4 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 146567"
    },
    {
        "question": "940 + 109",
        "answer": "Add 940 and 109 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1049"
    },
    {
        "question": "60973 + 372",
        "answer": "Add 60973 and 372 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 61345"
    },
    {
        "question": "44726 + 1138",
        "answer": "Add 44726 and 1138 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45864"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 54",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 54 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 141"
    },
    {
        "question": "461 + 437",
        "answer": "Add 461 and 437 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 898"
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 33 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 35"
    },
    {
        "question": "734 + 624",
        "answer": "Add 734 and 624 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1358"
    },
    {
        "question": "41602 + 3175",
        "answer": "Add 41602 and 3175 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 44777"
    },
    {
        "question": "6829 + 70",
        "answer": "Add 6829 and 70 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6899"
    },
    {
        "question": "973 + 715",
        "answer": "Add 973 and 715 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1688"
    },
    {
        "question": "66796 + 60743",
        "answer": "Add 66796 and 60743 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 7 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 127539"
    },
    {
        "question": "59590 + 6340",
        "answer": "Add 59590 and 6340 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 65930"
    },
    {
        "question": "88363 + 625",
        "answer": "Add 88363 and 625 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 88988"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 86 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 115"
    },
    {
        "question": "469 + 430",
        "answer": "Add 469 and 430 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 899"
    },
    {
        "question": "3039 + 491",
        "answer": "Add 3039 and 491 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 9 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 4 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3530"
    },
    {
        "question": "989 + 270",
        "answer": "Add 989 and 270 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1259"
    },
    {
        "question": "9754 + 562",
        "answer": "Add 9754 and 562 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 10316"
    },
    {
        "question": "5859 + 1765",
        "answer": "Add 5859 and 1765 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7624"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 15",
        "answer": "Add 27 and 15 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 42"
    },
    {
        "question": "87406 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 87406 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 87410"
    },
    {
        "question": "506 + 160",
        "answer": "Add 506 and 160 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 666"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 25",
        "answer": "Add 80 and 25 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 105"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 83 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 89"
    },
    {
        "question": "73042 + 68",
        "answer": "Add 73042 and 68 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 73110"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 71 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 121"
    },
    {
        "question": "5641 + 20",
        "answer": "Add 5641 and 20 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5661"
    },
    {
        "question": "701 + 173",
        "answer": "Add 701 and 173 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 874"
    },
    {
        "question": "971 + 178",
        "answer": "Add 971 and 178 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1149"
    },
    {
        "question": "728 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 728 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 735"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 13",
        "answer": "Add 78 and 13 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 91"
    },
    {
        "question": "40935 + 10",
        "answer": "Add 40935 and 10 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 40945"
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 15",
        "answer": "Add 63 and 15 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 78"
    },
    {
        "question": "5840 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 5840 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5889"
    },
    {
        "question": "29 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 29 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 56"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 31",
        "answer": "Add 72 and 31 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 103"
    },
    {
        "question": "801 + 517",
        "answer": "Add 801 and 517 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1318"
    },
    {
        "question": "94052 + 67",
        "answer": "Add 94052 and 67 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 94119"
    },
    {
        "question": "94635 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 94635 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 94644"
    },
    {
        "question": "17725 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 17725 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 17726"
    },
    {
        "question": "5665 + 435",
        "answer": "Add 5665 and 435 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6100"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 45 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 8 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 83",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 83 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 180"
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 92",
        "answer": "Add 154 and 92 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 246"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 36 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45"
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 33 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 51"
    },
    {
        "question": "124 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 124 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 133"
    },
    {
        "question": "42 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 42 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 63"
    },
    {
        "question": "8100 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 8100 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8102"
    },
    {
        "question": "9939 + 26",
        "answer": "Add 9939 and 26 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9965"
    },
    {
        "question": "5215 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 5215 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5217"
    },
    {
        "question": "86852 + 78880",
        "answer": "Add 86852 and 78880 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 8 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 8 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 165732"
    },
    {
        "question": "918 + 487",
        "answer": "Add 918 and 487 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1405"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 112"
    },
    {
        "question": "84852 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 84852 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 84860"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 77",
        "answer": "Add 81 and 77 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 158"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 11",
        "answer": "Add 37 and 11 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 48"
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 13",
        "answer": "Add 40 and 13 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 53"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 72 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 77"
    },
    {
        "question": "842 + 124",
        "answer": "Add 842 and 124 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 966"
    },
    {
        "question": "508 + 214",
        "answer": "Add 508 and 214 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 1 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 722"
    },
    {
        "question": "9350 + 15",
        "answer": "Add 9350 and 15 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9365"
    },
    {
        "question": "728 + 528",
        "answer": "Add 728 and 528 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1256"
    },
    {
        "question": "95954 + 21597",
        "answer": "Add 95954 and 21597 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 9 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 117551"
    },
    {
        "question": "859 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 859 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 864"
    },
    {
        "question": "7548 + 6145",
        "answer": "Add 7548 and 6145 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 13693"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 85 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 92"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 73",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 73 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 167"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 119"
    },
    {
        "question": "5111 + 2409",
        "answer": "Add 5111 and 2409 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7520"
    },
    {
        "question": "4303 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 4303 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4305"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 40",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 40 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 138"
    },
    {
        "question": "5575 + 2592",
        "answer": "Add 5575 and 2592 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 8167"
    },
    {
        "question": "2447 + 87",
        "answer": "Add 2447 and 87 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2534"
    },
    {
        "question": "23872 + 361",
        "answer": "Add 23872 and 361 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 24233"
    },
    {
        "question": "721 + 321",
        "answer": "Add 721 and 321 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1042"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 85 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 41",
        "answer": "Add 76 and 41 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 117"
    },
    {
        "question": "3016 + 369",
        "answer": "Add 3016 and 369 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 6 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3385"
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 40 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 63"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 58",
        "answer": "Add 99 and 58 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 157"
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 30",
        "answer": "Add 53 and 30 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 83"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 54",
        "answer": "Add 74 and 54 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 128"
    },
    {
        "question": "56694 + 39",
        "answer": "Add 56694 and 39 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 56733"
    },
    {
        "question": "967 + 294",
        "answer": "Add 967 and 294 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 9 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1261"
    },
    {
        "question": "93780 + 56355",
        "answer": "Add 93780 and 56355 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 6 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 150135"
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 24",
        "answer": "Add 49 and 24 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 73"
    },
    {
        "question": "349 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 349 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 353"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 36",
        "answer": "Add 37 and 36 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 73"
    },
    {
        "question": "329 + 285",
        "answer": "Add 329 and 285 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 614"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 71"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 67 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 71"
    },
    {
        "question": "311 + 226",
        "answer": "Add 311 and 226 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 537"
    },
    {
        "question": "431 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 431 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 436"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 75",
        "answer": "Add 88 and 75 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 163"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 54",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 54 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 145"
    },
    {
        "question": "87550 + 86323",
        "answer": "Add 87550 and 86323 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 173873"
    },
    {
        "question": "41887 + 901",
        "answer": "Add 41887 and 901 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 42788"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 85 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 8 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 103"
    },
    {
        "question": "583 + 314",
        "answer": "Add 583 and 314 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 897"
    },
    {
        "question": "1985 + 531",
        "answer": "Add 1985 and 531 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2516"
    },
    {
        "question": "710 + 148",
        "answer": "Add 710 and 148 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 858"
    },
    {
        "question": "69191 + 59772",
        "answer": "Add 69191 and 59772 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 7 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 128963"
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 49 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 57"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 41",
        "answer": "Add 76 and 41 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 117"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 56 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 65"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 99"
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 12",
        "answer": "Add 82 and 12 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 94"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 24",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 24 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 99"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 45",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 45 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 141"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 25",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 25 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 109"
    },
    {
        "question": "3370 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 3370 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3373"
    },
    {
        "question": "21 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 21 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 27"
    },
    {
        "question": "903 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 903 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 931"
    },
    {
        "question": "5882 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 5882 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5887"
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 55 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 98"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 73 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "8584 + 69",
        "answer": "Add 8584 and 69 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8653"
    },
    {
        "question": "730 + 674",
        "answer": "Add 730 and 674 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1404"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 30",
        "answer": "Add 59 and 30 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 89"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 22",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 22 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 106"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 57 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 74"
    },
    {
        "question": "1523 + 86",
        "answer": "Add 1523 and 86 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1609"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 74 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 77"
    },
    {
        "question": "25053 + 674",
        "answer": "Add 25053 and 674 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 6 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 25727"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 38 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 65"
    },
    {
        "question": "9764 + 6544",
        "answer": "Add 9764 and 6544 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 16308"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 72 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 88"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 60 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 67"
    },
    {
        "question": "5522 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 5522 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5556"
    },
    {
        "question": "3324 + 44",
        "answer": "Add 3324 and 44 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3368"
    },
    {
        "question": "5671 + 5132",
        "answer": "Add 5671 and 5132 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10803"
    },
    {
        "question": "30666 + 4287",
        "answer": "Add 30666 and 4287 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 8 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 34953"
    },
    {
        "question": "9705 + 4076",
        "answer": "Add 9705 and 4076 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 13781"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 117"
    },
    {
        "question": "62496 + 23738",
        "answer": "Add 62496 and 23738 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 7 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 3 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 86234"
    },
    {
        "question": "75449 + 47023",
        "answer": "Add 75449 and 47023 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 122472"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 71"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 44",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 44 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 135"
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 55 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 8 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 63"
    },
    {
        "question": "79480 + 2969",
        "answer": "Add 79480 and 2969 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 9 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 82449"
    },
    {
        "question": "36753 + 468",
        "answer": "Add 36753 and 468 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 37221"
    },
    {
        "question": "391 + 317",
        "answer": "Add 391 and 317 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 708"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 38",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 38 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 136"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 74",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 74 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 171"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 14 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 19"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 99"
    },
    {
        "question": "53377 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 53377 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53383"
    },
    {
        "question": "740 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 740 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 744"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 75",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 75 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 172"
    },
    {
        "question": "89259 + 36",
        "answer": "Add 89259 and 36 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 89295"
    },
    {
        "question": "4795 + 939",
        "answer": "Add 4795 and 939 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 9 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5734"
    },
    {
        "question": "37507 + 8225",
        "answer": "Add 37507 and 8225 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45732"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 69 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 75"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 65",
        "answer": "Add 76 and 65 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 141"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 27 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 32"
    },
    {
        "question": "31142 + 566",
        "answer": "Add 31142 and 566 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 5 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 31708"
    },
    {
        "question": "33833 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 33833 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 33840"
    },
    {
        "question": "7607 + 19",
        "answer": "Add 7607 and 19 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 1 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7626"
    },
    {
        "question": "565 + 125",
        "answer": "Add 565 and 125 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 690"
    },
    {
        "question": "5184 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 5184 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5205"
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 53 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 62"
    },
    {
        "question": "8648 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 8648 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8651"
    },
    {
        "question": "289 + 278",
        "answer": "Add 289 and 278 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 567"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 80"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 76 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 82"
    },
    {
        "question": "701 + 211",
        "answer": "Add 701 and 211 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 912"
    },
    {
        "question": "717 + 478",
        "answer": "Add 717 and 478 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 7 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1195"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 45",
        "answer": "Add 54 and 45 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 99"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 65",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 65 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 163"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 58",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 58 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 145"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 46",
        "answer": "Add 59 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 105"
    },
    {
        "question": "396 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 396 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 403"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 40",
        "answer": "Add 69 and 40 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 109"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 41",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 41 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 132"
    },
    {
        "question": "20086 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 20086 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 20088"
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 44 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 78"
    },
    {
        "question": "3526 + 75",
        "answer": "Add 3526 and 75 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3601"
    },
    {
        "question": "624 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 624 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 632"
    },
    {
        "question": "66525 + 171",
        "answer": "Add 66525 and 171 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 66696"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 33",
        "answer": "Add 56 and 33 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 89"
    },
    {
        "question": "9922 + 884",
        "answer": "Add 9922 and 884 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 8 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 10806"
    },
    {
        "question": "9029 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 9029 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 4 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9072"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 110"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 66",
        "answer": "Add 86 and 66 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 152"
    },
    {
        "question": "868 + 155",
        "answer": "Add 868 and 155 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1023"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 73 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 123"
    },
    {
        "question": "90124 + 31435",
        "answer": "Add 90124 and 31435 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 121559"
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 64",
        "answer": "Add 77 and 64 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 141"
    },
    {
        "question": "7795 + 87",
        "answer": "Add 7795 and 87 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7882"
    },
    {
        "question": "880 + 74",
        "answer": "Add 880 and 74 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 954"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 91",
        "answer": "Add 99 and 91 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 1 = 19 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 190"
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 26 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 29"
    },
    {
        "question": "9774 + 2510",
        "answer": "Add 9774 and 2510 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 12284"
    },
    {
        "question": "777 + 349",
        "answer": "Add 777 and 349 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1126"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 65",
        "answer": "Add 76 and 65 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 141"
    },
    {
        "question": "2025 + 91",
        "answer": "Add 2025 and 91 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2116"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 + 82",
        "answer": "Add 83 and 82 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 165"
    },
    {
        "question": "3790 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 3790 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3792"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 14",
        "answer": "Add 15 and 14 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 29"
    },
    {
        "question": "861 + 744",
        "answer": "Add 861 and 744 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1605"
    },
    {
        "question": "44208 + 25114",
        "answer": "Add 44208 and 25114 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 1 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 69322"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 89",
        "answer": "Add 99 and 89 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 188"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 76 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 126"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 94",
        "answer": "Add 95 and 94 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 189"
    },
    {
        "question": "85075 + 93",
        "answer": "Add 85075 and 93 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 85168"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 63",
        "answer": "Add 67 and 63 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 130"
    },
    {
        "question": "970 + 440",
        "answer": "Add 970 and 440 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1410"
    },
    {
        "question": "596 + 595",
        "answer": "Add 596 and 595 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 1 = 19 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1191"
    },
    {
        "question": "494 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 494 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 498"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 51",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 51 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 147"
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 31",
        "answer": "Add 41 and 31 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 72"
    },
    {
        "question": "5971 + 130",
        "answer": "Add 5971 and 130 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6101"
    },
    {
        "question": "9205 + 7256",
        "answer": "Add 9205 and 7256 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 16461"
    },
    {
        "question": "52 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 52 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 70"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 93"
    },
    {
        "question": "9157 + 7985",
        "answer": "Add 9157 and 7985 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 8 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 9 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 17142"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 54 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 97"
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 54",
        "answer": "Add 236 and 54 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 5 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 290"
    },
    {
        "question": "4022 + 3479",
        "answer": "Add 4022 and 3479 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 4 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7501"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 66 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 100"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 + 82",
        "answer": "Add 83 and 82 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 165"
    },
    {
        "question": "6474 + 2728",
        "answer": "Add 6474 and 2728 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 7 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9202"
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 31",
        "answer": "Add 104 and 31 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 135"
    },
    {
        "question": "7160 + 1160",
        "answer": "Add 7160 and 1160 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 1 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 8320"
    },
    {
        "question": "512 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 512 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 513"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 74",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 74 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 170"
    },
    {
        "question": "82758 + 61519",
        "answer": "Add 82758 and 61519 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 144277"
    },
    {
        "question": "8312 + 4650",
        "answer": "Add 8312 and 4650 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 12962"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 93",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 93 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 189"
    },
    {
        "question": "757 + 405",
        "answer": "Add 757 and 405 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1162"
    },
    {
        "question": "56660 + 7048",
        "answer": "Add 56660 and 7048 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 63708"
    },
    {
        "question": "93480 + 724",
        "answer": "Add 93480 and 724 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 7 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 94204"
    },
    {
        "question": "109 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 109 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 112"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 10",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 10 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 94"
    },
    {
        "question": "1372 + 1259",
        "answer": "Add 1372 and 1259 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 2631"
    },
    {
        "question": "53437 + 15905",
        "answer": "Add 53437 and 15905 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 5 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 69342"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 56",
        "answer": "Add 69 and 56 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 125"
    },
    {
        "question": "425 + 185",
        "answer": "Add 425 and 185 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 1 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 610"
    },
    {
        "question": "97892 + 79278",
        "answer": "Add 97892 and 79278 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 9 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 177170"
    },
    {
        "question": "13998 + 90",
        "answer": "Add 13998 and 90 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 14088"
    },
    {
        "question": "525 + 416",
        "answer": "Add 525 and 416 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 941"
    },
    {
        "question": "8901 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 8901 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8908"
    },
    {
        "question": "706 + 512",
        "answer": "Add 706 and 512 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1218"
    },
    {
        "question": "7133 + 2240",
        "answer": "Add 7133 and 2240 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9373"
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 24 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 45"
    },
    {
        "question": "308 + 197",
        "answer": "Add 308 and 197 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 505"
    },
    {
        "question": "62937 + 53",
        "answer": "Add 62937 and 53 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 5 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 62990"
    },
    {
        "question": "986 + 152",
        "answer": "Add 986 and 152 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1138"
    },
    {
        "question": "380 + 380",
        "answer": "Add 380 and 380 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 760"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 58 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 108"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 53",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 53 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 150"
    },
    {
        "question": "39233 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 39233 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 39238"
    },
    {
        "question": "690 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 690 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 725"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 79",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 79 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 163"
    },
    {
        "question": "65812 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 65812 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 4 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 65861"
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 31",
        "answer": "Add 39 and 31 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 70"
    },
    {
        "question": "4356 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 4356 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4358"
    },
    {
        "question": "62 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 62 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 65"
    },
    {
        "question": "5144 + 1701",
        "answer": "Add 5144 and 1701 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 6845"
    },
    {
        "question": "666 + 117",
        "answer": "Add 666 and 117 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 783"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 50 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 71"
    },
    {
        "question": "529 + 142",
        "answer": "Add 529 and 142 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 4 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 671"
    },
    {
        "question": "459 + 244",
        "answer": "Add 459 and 244 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 703"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 33",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 33 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 127"
    },
    {
        "question": "59436 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 59436 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 59439"
    },
    {
        "question": "983 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 983 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1018"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 46",
        "answer": "Add 67 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 113"
    },
    {
        "question": "69437 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 69437 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 69443"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 24",
        "answer": "Add 47 and 24 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 71"
    },
    {
        "question": "47405 + 92",
        "answer": "Add 47405 and 92 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 47497"
    },
    {
        "question": "713 + 228",
        "answer": "Add 713 and 228 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 941"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 54",
        "answer": "Add 78 and 54 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 132"
    },
    {
        "question": "7691 + 3803",
        "answer": "Add 7691 and 3803 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 11494"
    },
    {
        "question": "9143 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 9143 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9152"
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 25",
        "answer": "Add 40 and 25 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 65"
    },
    {
        "question": "6843 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 6843 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6846"
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 26 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 43"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 54 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 88"
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 44 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 67"
    },
    {
        "question": "459 + 55",
        "answer": "Add 459 and 55 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 514"
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 13",
        "answer": "Add 41 and 13 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 54"
    },
    {
        "question": "9712 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 9712 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9717"
    },
    {
        "question": "7691 + 1705",
        "answer": "Add 7691 and 1705 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9396"
    },
    {
        "question": "717 + 62",
        "answer": "Add 717 and 62 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 779"
    },
    {
        "question": "34 + 10",
        "answer": "Add 34 and 10 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 44"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 54",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 54 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 129"
    },
    {
        "question": "94438 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 94438 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 94444"
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 39 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 74"
    },
    {
        "question": "2477 + 293",
        "answer": "Add 2477 and 293 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2770"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 51",
        "answer": "Add 72 and 51 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 123"
    },
    {
        "question": "8861 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 8861 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8869"
    },
    {
        "question": "696 + 653",
        "answer": "Add 696 and 653 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1349"
    },
    {
        "question": "15538 + 3204",
        "answer": "Add 15538 and 3204 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 18742"
    },
    {
        "question": "75480 + 11155",
        "answer": "Add 75480 and 11155 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 1 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 86635"
    },
    {
        "question": "306 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 306 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 314"
    },
    {
        "question": "878 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 878 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 885"
    },
    {
        "question": "9770 + 2647",
        "answer": "Add 9770 and 2647 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 12417"
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 30",
        "answer": "Add 48 and 30 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 78"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 105"
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 296",
        "answer": "Add 371 and 296 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 667"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 32",
        "answer": "Add 50 and 32 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 82"
    },
    {
        "question": "2936 + 1973",
        "answer": "Add 2936 and 1973 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 9 + 1 = 19 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 4909"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 51",
        "answer": "Add 56 and 51 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 107"
    },
    {
        "question": "8675 + 2253",
        "answer": "Add 8675 and 2253 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10928"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 + 48",
        "answer": "Add 60 and 48 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 108"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 85 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 132"
    },
    {
        "question": "48076 + 814",
        "answer": "Add 48076 and 814 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 48890"
    },
    {
        "question": "96335 + 144",
        "answer": "Add 96335 and 144 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 96479"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 44",
        "answer": "Add 51 and 44 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 95"
    },
    {
        "question": "43691 + 215",
        "answer": "Add 43691 and 215 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 43906"
    },
    {
        "question": "888 + 372",
        "answer": "Add 888 and 372 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1260"
    },
    {
        "question": "440 + 381",
        "answer": "Add 440 and 381 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 821"
    },
    {
        "question": "434 + 61",
        "answer": "Add 434 and 61 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 495"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 48",
        "answer": "Add 89 and 48 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 137"
    },
    {
        "question": "4905 + 1331",
        "answer": "Add 4905 and 1331 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 1 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 6236"
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 11",
        "answer": "Add 41 and 11 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 52"
    },
    {
        "question": "6303 + 3460",
        "answer": "Add 6303 and 3460 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9763"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 57",
        "answer": "Add 74 and 57 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 131"
    },
    {
        "question": "151 + 53",
        "answer": "Add 151 and 53 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 204"
    },
    {
        "question": "765 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 765 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 808"
    },
    {
        "question": "19006 + 4768",
        "answer": "Add 19006 and 4768 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 23774"
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 24",
        "answer": "Add 43 and 24 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 67"
    },
    {
        "question": "88583 + 26179",
        "answer": "Add 88583 and 26179 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 114762"
    },
    {
        "question": "5983 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 5983 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5999"
    },
    {
        "question": "410 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 410 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 415"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 61 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 88"
    },
    {
        "question": "61100 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 61100 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 61103"
    },
    {
        "question": "9754 + 8783",
        "answer": "Add 9754 and 8783 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 8 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 7 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 8 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 18537"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 72 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 81"
    },
    {
        "question": "42 + 22",
        "answer": "Add 42 and 22 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 64"
    },
    {
        "question": "86423 + 64853",
        "answer": "Add 86423 and 64853 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 151276"
    },
    {
        "question": "51769 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 51769 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 51773"
    },
    {
        "question": "6197 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 6197 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6206"
    },
    {
        "question": "523 + 317",
        "answer": "Add 523 and 317 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 840"
    },
    {
        "question": "1543 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 1543 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1546"
    },
    {
        "question": "95446 + 81727",
        "answer": "Add 95446 and 81727 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 177173"
    },
    {
        "question": "6232 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 6232 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6255"
    },
    {
        "question": "891 + 723",
        "answer": "Add 891 and 723 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1614"
    },
    {
        "question": "23 + 11",
        "answer": "Add 23 and 11 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 34"
    },
    {
        "question": "760 + 356",
        "answer": "Add 760 and 356 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1116"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 89 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 116"
    },
    {
        "question": "24636 + 269",
        "answer": "Add 24636 and 269 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 6 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 24905"
    },
    {
        "question": "4091 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 4091 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4092"
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 48 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 74 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 83"
    },
    {
        "question": "56603 + 95",
        "answer": "Add 56603 and 95 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 56698"
    },
    {
        "question": "9412 + 2679",
        "answer": "Add 9412 and 2679 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 7 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 12091"
    },
    {
        "question": "42341 + 80",
        "answer": "Add 42341 and 80 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 42421"
    },
    {
        "question": "45567 + 32",
        "answer": "Add 45567 and 32 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45599"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 90 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 137"
    },
    {
        "question": "1948 + 62",
        "answer": "Add 1948 and 62 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2010"
    },
    {
        "question": "8253 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 8253 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8257"
    },
    {
        "question": "4886 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 4886 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4902"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 10 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 13"
    },
    {
        "question": "79333 + 919",
        "answer": "Add 79333 and 919 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 80252"
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 49 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 51"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 60 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 61"
    },
    {
        "question": "961 + 463",
        "answer": "Add 961 and 463 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1424"
    },
    {
        "question": "85365 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 85365 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 85372"
    },
    {
        "question": "1158 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 1158 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1159"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 46",
        "answer": "Add 86 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 132"
    },
    {
        "question": "88438 + 64467",
        "answer": "Add 88438 and 64467 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 6 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 152905"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 37 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45"
    },
    {
        "question": "5153 + 3691",
        "answer": "Add 5153 and 3691 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 6 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 8844"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 66",
        "answer": "Add 74 and 66 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 140"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 31",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 31 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 106"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 30",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 30 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 124"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 87"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 56",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 56 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 140"
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 13",
        "answer": "Add 53 and 13 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 66"
    },
    {
        "question": "6471 + 55",
        "answer": "Add 6471 and 55 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6526"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 26",
        "answer": "Add 81 and 26 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 107"
    },
    {
        "question": "91493 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 91493 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 91497"
    },
    {
        "question": "5759 + 1622",
        "answer": "Add 5759 and 1622 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7381"
    },
    {
        "question": "42254 + 66",
        "answer": "Add 42254 and 66 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 42320"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 53",
        "answer": "Add 56 and 53 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 109"
    },
    {
        "question": "7682 + 604",
        "answer": "Add 7682 and 604 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8286"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 27 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 28"
    },
    {
        "question": "773 + 401",
        "answer": "Add 773 and 401 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1174"
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 65 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 100"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 50 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 77",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 77 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 175"
    },
    {
        "question": "475 + 306",
        "answer": "Add 475 and 306 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 781"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 79 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 81"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 113"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 30",
        "answer": "Add 47 and 30 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 77"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 24",
        "answer": "Add 71 and 24 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 95"
    },
    {
        "question": "787 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 787 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 795"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 144"
    },
    {
        "question": "363 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 363 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 410"
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 64",
        "answer": "Add 64 and 64 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 128"
    },
    {
        "question": "532 + 30",
        "answer": "Add 532 and 30 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 562"
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 12",
        "answer": "Add 64 and 12 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 76"
    },
    {
        "question": "516 + 356",
        "answer": "Add 516 and 356 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 5 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 872"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 89"
    },
    {
        "question": "8267 + 8196",
        "answer": "Add 8267 and 8196 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 9 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 16463"
    },
    {
        "question": "6630 + 674",
        "answer": "Add 6630 and 674 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7304"
    },
    {
        "question": "77407 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 77407 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 77414"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 84"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 58 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 79"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 36",
        "answer": "Add 79 and 36 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 115"
    },
    {
        "question": "814 + 84",
        "answer": "Add 814 and 84 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 898"
    },
    {
        "question": "4183 + 86",
        "answer": "Add 4183 and 86 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4269"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 24",
        "answer": "Add 66 and 24 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 90"
    },
    {
        "question": "683 + 629",
        "answer": "Add 683 and 629 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1312"
    },
    {
        "question": "746 + 265",
        "answer": "Add 746 and 265 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1011"
    },
    {
        "question": "9593 + 8436",
        "answer": "Add 9593 and 8436 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 8 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 18029"
    },
    {
        "question": "989 + 548",
        "answer": "Add 989 and 548 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1537"
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 46 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 81"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 66 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 84"
    },
    {
        "question": "9034 + 2224",
        "answer": "Add 9034 and 2224 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 11258"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 57",
        "answer": "Add 95 and 57 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 152"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 13",
        "answer": "Add 61 and 13 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 74"
    },
    {
        "question": "8182 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 8182 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8187"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 85 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "8725 + 2407",
        "answer": "Add 8725 and 2407 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 11132"
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 106",
        "answer": "Add 347 and 106 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 453"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 65",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 65 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 140"
    },
    {
        "question": "3213 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 3213 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3220"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 70",
        "answer": "Add 90 and 70 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 160"
    },
    {
        "question": "620 + 174",
        "answer": "Add 620 and 174 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 794"
    },
    {
        "question": "5993 + 3544",
        "answer": "Add 5993 and 3544 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9537"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 128"
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 374 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 381"
    },
    {
        "question": "564 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 564 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 565"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 40",
        "answer": "Add 61 and 40 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 101"
    },
    {
        "question": "8427 + 2569",
        "answer": "Add 8427 and 2569 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10996"
    },
    {
        "question": "20282 + 265",
        "answer": "Add 20282 and 265 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 20547"
    },
    {
        "question": "520 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 520 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 521"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 80 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 129"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 37",
        "answer": "Add 93 and 37 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 130"
    },
    {
        "question": "9549 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 9549 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9553"
    },
    {
        "question": "32 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 32 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 60"
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 15",
        "answer": "Add 65 and 15 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 80"
    },
    {
        "question": "686 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 686 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 702"
    },
    {
        "question": "982 + 583",
        "answer": "Add 982 and 583 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1565"
    },
    {
        "question": "84233 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 84233 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 84254"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 84"
    },
    {
        "question": "4257 + 1122",
        "answer": "Add 4257 and 1122 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 5379"
    },
    {
        "question": "4522 + 2566",
        "answer": "Add 4522 and 2566 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7088"
    },
    {
        "question": "845 + 685",
        "answer": "Add 845 and 685 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1530"
    },
    {
        "question": "390 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 390 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 391"
    },
    {
        "question": "9530 + 7503",
        "answer": "Add 9530 and 7503 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 17033"
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 20 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 37"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 88 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 94"
    },
    {
        "question": "768 + 367",
        "answer": "Add 768 and 367 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1135"
    },
    {
        "question": "9733 + 1686",
        "answer": "Add 9733 and 1686 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 11419"
    },
    {
        "question": "71809 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 71809 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 71818"
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 43 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 49"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 66",
        "answer": "Add 95 and 66 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 161"
    },
    {
        "question": "6178 + 4584",
        "answer": "Add 6178 and 4584 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 8 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 5 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10762"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 36 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 42"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 15",
        "answer": "Add 80 and 15 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 95"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 76 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 103"
    },
    {
        "question": "7673 + 51",
        "answer": "Add 7673 and 51 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7724"
    },
    {
        "question": "6989 + 2126",
        "answer": "Add 6989 and 2126 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9115"
    },
    {
        "question": "6976 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 6976 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6979"
    },
    {
        "question": "884 + 561",
        "answer": "Add 884 and 561 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1445"
    },
    {
        "question": "865 + 159",
        "answer": "Add 865 and 159 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1024"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 55",
        "answer": "Add 79 and 55 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 134"
    },
    {
        "question": "2965 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 2965 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2972"
    },
    {
        "question": "21 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 21 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 25"
    },
    {
        "question": "250 + 242",
        "answer": "Add 250 and 242 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 492"
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 33 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 62"
    },
    {
        "question": "41794 + 3719",
        "answer": "Add 41794 and 3719 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 7 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 3 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45513"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 65",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 65 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 152"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 94"
    },
    {
        "question": "45322 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 45322 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45343"
    },
    {
        "question": "17563 + 1490",
        "answer": "Add 17563 and 1490 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 19053"
    },
    {
        "question": "32337 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 32337 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 32345"
    },
    {
        "question": "19054 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 19054 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 19062"
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 33 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 56"
    },
    {
        "question": "42 + 33",
        "answer": "Add 42 and 33 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 75"
    },
    {
        "question": "8189 + 2180",
        "answer": "Add 8189 and 2180 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 1 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10369"
    },
    {
        "question": "922 + 742",
        "answer": "Add 922 and 742 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1664"
    },
    {
        "question": "942 + 288",
        "answer": "Add 942 and 288 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1230"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 51",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 51 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 126"
    },
    {
        "question": "727 + 476",
        "answer": "Add 727 and 476 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1203"
    },
    {
        "question": "3314 + 44",
        "answer": "Add 3314 and 44 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3358"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 63",
        "answer": "Add 73 and 63 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 136"
    },
    {
        "question": "6663 + 903",
        "answer": "Add 6663 and 903 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7566"
    },
    {
        "question": "7706 + 6936",
        "answer": "Add 7706 and 6936 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 14642"
    },
    {
        "question": "743 + 38",
        "answer": "Add 743 and 38 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 781"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 91 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 99"
    },
    {
        "question": "558 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 558 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 562"
    },
    {
        "question": "1602 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 1602 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1611"
    },
    {
        "question": "971 + 121",
        "answer": "Add 971 and 121 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1092"
    },
    {
        "question": "8013 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 8013 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8020"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 27 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 50"
    },
    {
        "question": "472 + 344",
        "answer": "Add 472 and 344 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 816"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 86 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 135"
    },
    {
        "question": "73874 + 265",
        "answer": "Add 73874 and 265 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 74139"
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 77 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 95"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 19",
        "answer": "Add 88 and 19 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 107"
    },
    {
        "question": "635 + 584",
        "answer": "Add 635 and 584 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1219"
    },
    {
        "question": "91742 + 74065",
        "answer": "Add 91742 and 74065 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 165807"
    },
    {
        "question": "16832 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 16832 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 16833"
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 15",
        "answer": "Add 41 and 15 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 56"
    },
    {
        "question": "724 + 501",
        "answer": "Add 724 and 501 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1225"
    },
    {
        "question": "9234 + 4856",
        "answer": "Add 9234 and 4856 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 5 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 14090"
    },
    {
        "question": "64684 + 221",
        "answer": "Add 64684 and 221 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 64905"
    },
    {
        "question": "31 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 31 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 60"
    },
    {
        "question": "537 + 61",
        "answer": "Add 537 and 61 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 598"
    },
    {
        "question": "9066 + 5666",
        "answer": "Add 9066 and 5666 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 6 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 14732"
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 19",
        "answer": "Add 39 and 19 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 58"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 60 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 62"
    },
    {
        "question": "457 + 257",
        "answer": "Add 457 and 257 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 714"
    },
    {
        "question": "6971 + 2017",
        "answer": "Add 6971 and 2017 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 8988"
    },
    {
        "question": "59563 + 7403",
        "answer": "Add 59563 and 7403 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 66966"
    },
    {
        "question": "26114 + 88",
        "answer": "Add 26114 and 88 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 26202"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 99 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 120"
    },
    {
        "question": "40080 + 8985",
        "answer": "Add 40080 and 8985 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 9 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 8 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 49065"
    },
    {
        "question": "32658 + 18997",
        "answer": "Add 32658 and 18997 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 9 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 9 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 8 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 51655"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 88 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 122"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 48",
        "answer": "Add 78 and 48 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 126"
    },
    {
        "question": "62724 + 959",
        "answer": "Add 62724 and 959 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 63683"
    },
    {
        "question": "992 + 347",
        "answer": "Add 992 and 347 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1339"
    },
    {
        "question": "52 + 39",
        "answer": "Add 52 and 39 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 91"
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 32",
        "answer": "Add 35 and 32 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 67"
    },
    {
        "question": "93176 + 5020",
        "answer": "Add 93176 and 5020 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 98196"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 46",
        "answer": "Add 47 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 93"
    },
    {
        "question": "621 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 621 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 628"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 57",
        "answer": "Add 70 and 57 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 127"
    },
    {
        "question": "514 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 514 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 537"
    },
    {
        "question": "59698 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 59698 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 59704"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 47 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 52"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 145"
    },
    {
        "question": "3850 + 261",
        "answer": "Add 3850 and 261 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4111"
    },
    {
        "question": "88526 + 4610",
        "answer": "Add 88526 and 4610 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 93136"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 86 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 115"
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 41",
        "answer": "Add 49 and 41 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 90"
    },
    {
        "question": "26575 + 2486",
        "answer": "Add 26575 and 2486 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 8 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 29061"
    },
    {
        "question": "623 + 429",
        "answer": "Add 623 and 429 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1052"
    },
    {
        "question": "843 + 676",
        "answer": "Add 843 and 676 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1519"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 67",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 67 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 135"
    },
    {
        "question": "9197 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 9197 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9199"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 11",
        "answer": "Add 79 and 11 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 90"
    },
    {
        "question": "690 + 394",
        "answer": "Add 690 and 394 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1084"
    },
    {
        "question": "97262 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 97262 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 97265"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 38 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 67"
    },
    {
        "question": "86533 + 8330",
        "answer": "Add 86533 and 8330 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 94863"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 27",
        "answer": "Add 69 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 96"
    },
    {
        "question": "79140 + 32432",
        "answer": "Add 79140 and 32432 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 111572"
    },
    {
        "question": "8123 + 4625",
        "answer": "Add 8123 and 4625 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 12748"
    },
    {
        "question": "8349 + 41",
        "answer": "Add 8349 and 41 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8390"
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 46 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 47"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 110"
    },
    {
        "question": "78911 + 70455",
        "answer": "Add 78911 and 70455 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 149366"
    },
    {
        "question": "453 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 453 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 454"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 62",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 62 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 160"
    },
    {
        "question": "9670 + 39",
        "answer": "Add 9670 and 39 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9709"
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 55 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "432 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 432 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 436"
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 55 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 59"
    },
    {
        "question": "631 + 442",
        "answer": "Add 631 and 442 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1073"
    },
    {
        "question": "604 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 604 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 612"
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 20 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 38"
    },
    {
        "question": "2053 + 445",
        "answer": "Add 2053 and 445 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2498"
    },
    {
        "question": "21382 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 21382 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 21388"
    },
    {
        "question": "890 + 199",
        "answer": "Add 890 and 199 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1089"
    },
    {
        "question": "3295 + 687",
        "answer": "Add 3295 and 687 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 6 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3982"
    },
    {
        "question": "70287 + 143",
        "answer": "Add 70287 and 143 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 70430"
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 40 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 46"
    },
    {
        "question": "27699 + 863",
        "answer": "Add 27699 and 863 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 8 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 28562"
    },
    {
        "question": "794 + 82",
        "answer": "Add 794 and 82 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 876"
    },
    {
        "question": "914 + 363",
        "answer": "Add 914 and 363 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1277"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 76 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 80"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 59 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 62"
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 22",
        "answer": "Add 26 and 22 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 48"
    },
    {
        "question": "832 + 134",
        "answer": "Add 832 and 134 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 966"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 44",
        "answer": "Add 58 and 44 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "854 + 578",
        "answer": "Add 854 and 578 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1432"
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 43 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 51"
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 77 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 127"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 31",
        "answer": "Add 70 and 31 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 101"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 84",
        "answer": "Add 85 and 84 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 169"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 104"
    },
    {
        "question": "49844 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 49844 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 49893"
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 41",
        "answer": "Add 63 and 41 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 104"
    },
    {
        "question": "951 + 820",
        "answer": "Add 951 and 820 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1771"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 + 64",
        "answer": "Add 83 and 64 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 147"
    },
    {
        "question": "473 + 375",
        "answer": "Add 473 and 375 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 848"
    },
    {
        "question": "802 + 440",
        "answer": "Add 802 and 440 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1242"
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 63 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 66"
    },
    {
        "question": "55504 + 393",
        "answer": "Add 55504 and 393 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 55897"
    },
    {
        "question": "6779 + 4136",
        "answer": "Add 6779 and 4136 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10915"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 46",
        "answer": "Add 71 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 117"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 53",
        "answer": "Add 74 and 53 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 127"
    },
    {
        "question": "54265 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 54265 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 54274"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 49",
        "answer": "Add 71 and 49 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 120"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 32",
        "answer": "Add 75 and 32 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 107"
    },
    {
        "question": "78257 + 73",
        "answer": "Add 78257 and 73 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 78330"
    },
    {
        "question": "7232 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 7232 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7235"
    },
    {
        "question": "9278 + 1727",
        "answer": "Add 9278 and 1727 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 7 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 11005"
    },
    {
        "question": "5559 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 5559 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5567"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 17",
        "answer": "Add 72 and 17 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 89"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 73",
        "answer": "Add 95 and 73 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 168"
    },
    {
        "question": "56964 + 9509",
        "answer": "Add 56964 and 9509 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 9 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 66473"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 43",
        "answer": "Add 57 and 43 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 100"
    },
    {
        "question": "763 + 720",
        "answer": "Add 763 and 720 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1483"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 32",
        "answer": "Add 54 and 32 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 86"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 36",
        "answer": "Add 94 and 36 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 130"
    },
    {
        "question": "85931 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 85931 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 85932"
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 48",
        "answer": "Add 53 and 48 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 101"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 23",
        "answer": "Add 73 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 96"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 45",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 45 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 132"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 77",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 77 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 161"
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 20 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 28"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 38 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 67"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 27 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 29"
    },
    {
        "question": "77173 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 77173 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 77178"
    },
    {
        "question": "123 + 77",
        "answer": "Add 123 and 77 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 200"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 66 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 101"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 47",
        "answer": "Add 66 and 47 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 113"
    },
    {
        "question": "611 + 593",
        "answer": "Add 611 and 593 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1204"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 70 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 120"
    },
    {
        "question": "915 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 915 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 918"
    },
    {
        "question": "260 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 260 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 266"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 18",
        "answer": "Add 80 and 18 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 98"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 97 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 102"
    },
    {
        "question": "3097 + 58",
        "answer": "Add 3097 and 58 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3155"
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 145 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 151"
    },
    {
        "question": "3427 + 54",
        "answer": "Add 3427 and 54 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3481"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 35",
        "answer": "Add 36 and 35 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 71"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 38",
        "answer": "Add 90 and 38 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 128"
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 51",
        "answer": "Add 82 and 51 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 133"
    },
    {
        "question": "9826 + 6656",
        "answer": "Add 9826 and 6656 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 16482"
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 15",
        "answer": "Add 20 and 15 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 35"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 56",
        "answer": "Add 78 and 56 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 134"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 41",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 41 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 125"
    },
    {
        "question": "158 + 143",
        "answer": "Add 158 and 143 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 1 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 301"
    },
    {
        "question": "1775 + 76",
        "answer": "Add 1775 and 76 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 7 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1851"
    },
    {
        "question": "8877 + 1403",
        "answer": "Add 8877 and 1403 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10280"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 14",
        "answer": "Add 86 and 14 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 100"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 70",
        "answer": "Add 81 and 70 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 151"
    },
    {
        "question": "517 + 489",
        "answer": "Add 517 and 489 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1006"
    },
    {
        "question": "6102 + 5733",
        "answer": "Add 6102 and 5733 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 11835"
    },
    {
        "question": "2958 + 2369",
        "answer": "Add 2958 and 2369 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 5327"
    },
    {
        "question": "557 + 69",
        "answer": "Add 557 and 69 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 626"
    },
    {
        "question": "73178 + 27860",
        "answer": "Add 73178 and 27860 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 8 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 7 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 101038"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 34",
        "answer": "Add 93 and 34 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 127"
    },
    {
        "question": "5274 + 353",
        "answer": "Add 5274 and 353 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 3 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5627"
    },
    {
        "question": "606 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 606 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 610"
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 26 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 47"
    },
    {
        "question": "26222 + 26",
        "answer": "Add 26222 and 26 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 26248"
    },
    {
        "question": "984 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 984 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 987"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 39",
        "answer": "Add 51 and 39 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 90"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 6",
        "answer": "Add 87 and 6 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 93"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 42",
        "answer": "Add 89 and 42 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 131"
    },
    {
        "question": "52 + 44",
        "answer": "Add 52 and 44 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 96"
    },
    {
        "question": "889 + 19",
        "answer": "Add 889 and 19 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 908"
    },
    {
        "question": "9342 + 1421",
        "answer": "Add 9342 and 1421 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10763"
    },
    {
        "question": "9564 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 9564 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9572"
    },
    {
        "question": "94896 + 59501",
        "answer": "Add 94896 and 59501 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 9 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 154397"
    },
    {
        "question": "361 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 361 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 389"
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 22",
        "answer": "Add 43 and 22 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 65"
    },
    {
        "question": "27960 + 6517",
        "answer": "Add 27960 and 6517 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 34477"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 57",
        "answer": "Add 93 and 57 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 150"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 61",
        "answer": "Add 68 and 61 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 129"
    },
    {
        "question": "82103 + 21",
        "answer": "Add 82103 and 21 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 82124"
    },
    {
        "question": "24287 + 7",
        "answer": "Add 24287 and 7 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 24294"
    },
    {
        "question": "78389 + 28999",
        "answer": "Add 78389 and 28999 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 9 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 107388"
    },
    {
        "question": "848 + 737",
        "answer": "Add 848 and 737 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1585"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 12",
        "answer": "Add 98 and 12 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 110"
    },
    {
        "question": "660 + 299",
        "answer": "Add 660 and 299 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 959"
    },
    {
        "question": "35769 + 651",
        "answer": "Add 35769 and 651 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 36420"
    },
    {
        "question": "83474 + 999",
        "answer": "Add 83474 and 999 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 9 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 84473"
    },
    {
        "question": "49871 + 49184",
        "answer": "Add 49871 and 49184 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 9 + 1 = 19 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 99055"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 72",
        "answer": "Add 72 and 72 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 144"
    },
    {
        "question": "710 + 543",
        "answer": "Add 710 and 543 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1253"
    },
    {
        "question": "4373 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 4373 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4423"
    },
    {
        "question": "542 + 2",
        "answer": "Add 542 and 2 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 544"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 61 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 66"
    },
    {
        "question": "57419 + 1021",
        "answer": "Add 57419 and 1021 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 58440"
    },
    {
        "question": "93712 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 93712 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 93717"
    },
    {
        "question": "73196 + 280",
        "answer": "Add 73196 and 280 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 73476"
    },
    {
        "question": "4649 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 4649 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4653"
    },
    {
        "question": "7885 + 1486",
        "answer": "Add 7885 and 1486 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9371"
    },
    {
        "question": "6312 + 315",
        "answer": "Add 6312 and 315 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6627"
    },
    {
        "question": "29953 + 21047",
        "answer": "Add 29953 and 21047 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 51000"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 80",
        "answer": "Add 96 and 80 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 176"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 69",
        "answer": "Add 84 and 69 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 153"
    },
    {
        "question": "621 + 1",
        "answer": "Add 621 and 1 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 622"
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 29",
        "answer": "Add 82 and 29 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 111"
    },
    {
        "question": "43922 + 794",
        "answer": "Add 43922 and 794 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 44716"
    },
    {
        "question": "9543 + 25",
        "answer": "Add 9543 and 25 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9568"
    },
    {
        "question": "3100 + 1906",
        "answer": "Add 3100 and 1906 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 5006"
    },
    {
        "question": "4836 + 896",
        "answer": "Add 4836 and 896 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 9 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5732"
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 3",
        "answer": "Add 19 and 3 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 22"
    },
    {
        "question": "9565 + 6624",
        "answer": "Add 9565 and 6624 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 16189"
    },
    {
        "question": "825 + 317",
        "answer": "Add 825 and 317 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1142"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 28",
        "answer": "Add 54 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 82"
    },
    {
        "question": "7715 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 7715 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 8 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7723"
    },
    {
        "question": "76597 + 44320",
        "answer": "Add 76597 and 44320 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 120917"
    },
    {
        "question": "763 + 633",
        "answer": "Add 763 and 633 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1396"
    },
    {
        "question": "31 + 16",
        "answer": "Add 31 and 16 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 47"
    },
    {
        "question": "79618 + 30036",
        "answer": "Add 79618 and 30036 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 3 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 109654"
    },
    {
        "question": "2284 + 789",
        "answer": "Add 2284 and 789 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 7 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3073"
    },
    {
        "question": "970 + 696",
        "answer": "Add 970 and 696 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1666"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 40",
        "answer": "Add 47 and 40 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 87"
    },
    {
        "question": "487 + 279",
        "answer": "Add 487 and 279 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 766"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 + 5",
        "answer": "Add 22 and 5 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 27"
    },
    {
        "question": "9797 + 6086",
        "answer": "Add 9797 and 6086 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 8 + 1 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 15883"
    },
    {
        "question": "62012 + 50",
        "answer": "Add 62012 and 50 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 62062"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 4",
        "answer": "Add 89 and 4 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 9 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 93"
    },
    {
        "question": "9642 + 78",
        "answer": "Add 9642 and 78 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 7 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9720"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 62",
        "answer": "Add 78 and 62 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 6 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 140"
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 8",
        "answer": "Add 41 and 8 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 49"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 36",
        "answer": "Add 92 and 36 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 128"
    },
    {
        "question": "591 + 133",
        "answer": "Add 591 and 133 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 724"
    },
    {
        "question": "4611 + 265",
        "answer": "Add 4611 and 265 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4876"
    },
    {
        "question": "855 + 305",
        "answer": "Add 855 and 305 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1160"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 19",
        "answer": "Add 79 and 19 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 98"
    },
    {
        "question": "543 + 52",
        "answer": "Add 543 and 52 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 595"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 9",
        "answer": "Add 36 and 9 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45"
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 44",
        "answer": "Add 64 and 44 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nThe final answer is 108"
    },
    {
        "question": "5491 + 2628",
        "answer": "Add 5491 and 2628 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 6 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 8119"
    },
    {
        "question": "884 + 824",
        "answer": "Add 884 and 824 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1708"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 * 79",
        "answer": "Multiply 79 and 79 step by step:\nMultiplying 79 by the 9 in the ones place\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\n7 * 9 + 8 = 71 (carry 7, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 79 by the 9 in the ones place yields 711\n\nMultiplying 79 by the 7 in the tens place\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n7 * 7 + 6 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 79 by the 7 in the tens place yields 5530\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 711 + 5530:\n\nAdd 5530 and 711 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6241\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6241"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 * 61",
        "answer": "Multiply 66 and 61 step by step:\nMultiplying 66 by the 1 in the ones place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 66 by the 1 in the ones place yields 66\n\nMultiplying 66 by the 6 in the tens place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n6 * 6 + 3 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 66 by the 6 in the tens place yields 3960\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 66 + 3960:\n\nAdd 3960 and 66 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4026\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4026"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 * 80",
        "answer": "Multiply 98 and 80 step by step:\nMultiplying 98 by the 0 in the ones place\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 98 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 98 by the 8 in the tens place\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\n9 * 8 + 6 = 78 (carry 7, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 98 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7840\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 7840:\n\nAdd 7840 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7840\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7840"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 * 15",
        "answer": "Multiply 91 and 15 step by step:\nMultiplying 91 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 91 by the 5 in the ones place yields 455\n\nMultiplying 91 by the 1 in the tens place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 91 by the 1 in the tens place yields 910\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 455 + 910:\n\nAdd 910 and 455 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1365\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1365"
    },
    {
        "question": "325 * 14",
        "answer": "Multiply 325 and 14 step by step:\nMultiplying 325 by the 4 in the ones place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n2 * 4 + 2 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n3 * 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 325 by the 4 in the ones place yields 1300\n\nMultiplying 325 by the 1 in the tens place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 325 by the 1 in the tens place yields 3250\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1300 + 3250:\n\nAdd 3250 and 1300 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 4550\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4550"
    },
    {
        "question": "409 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 409 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 409 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n0 * 5 + 4 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 409 by the 5 in the ones place yields 2045\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2045:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "435 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 435 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 435 by the 3 in the ones place\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n3 * 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n4 * 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 435 by the 3 in the ones place yields 1305\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1305:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 * 82",
        "answer": "Multiply 88 and 82 step by step:\nMultiplying 88 by the 2 in the ones place\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 88 by the 2 in the ones place yields 176\n\nMultiplying 88 by the 8 in the tens place\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\n8 * 8 + 6 = 70 (carry 7, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 88 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7040\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 176 + 7040:\n\nAdd 7040 and 176 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 1 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7216\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7216"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 * 17",
        "answer": "Multiply 76 and 17 step by step:\nMultiplying 76 by the 7 in the ones place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n7 * 7 + 4 = 53 (carry 5, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 76 by the 7 in the ones place yields 532\n\nMultiplying 76 by the 1 in the tens place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 76 by the 1 in the tens place yields 760\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 532 + 760:\n\nAdd 760 and 532 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1292\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1292"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 * 47",
        "answer": "Multiply 96 and 47 step by step:\nMultiplying 96 by the 7 in the ones place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n9 * 7 + 4 = 67 (carry 6, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 96 by the 7 in the ones place yields 672\n\nMultiplying 96 by the 4 in the tens place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n9 * 4 + 2 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 96 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3840\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 672 + 3840:\n\nAdd 3840 and 672 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4512\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4512"
    },
    {
        "question": "265 * 142",
        "answer": "Multiply 265 and 142 step by step:\nMultiplying 265 by the 2 in the ones place\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n2 * 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 265 by the 2 in the ones place yields 530\n\nMultiplying 265 by the 4 in the tens place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n6 * 4 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\n2 * 4 + 2 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 265 by the 4 in the tens place yields 10600\n\nMultiplying 265 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 265 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 26500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 530 + 10600 + 26500:\n\nAdd 10600 and 530 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 11130\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 11130 + 26500\nAdd 26500 and 11130 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 37630\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 37630"
    },
    {
        "question": "399 * 76",
        "answer": "Multiply 399 and 76 step by step:\nMultiplying 399 by the 6 in the ones place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n9 * 6 + 5 = 59 (carry 5, remainder 9)\n3 * 6 + 5 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 399 by the 6 in the ones place yields 2394\n\nMultiplying 399 by the 7 in the tens place\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n9 * 7 + 6 = 69 (carry 6, remainder 9)\n3 * 7 + 6 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 399 by the 7 in the tens place yields 27930\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2394 + 27930:\n\nAdd 27930 and 2394 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 9 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 30324\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 30324"
    },
    {
        "question": "342 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 342 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 342 by the 4 in the ones place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n3 * 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 342 by the 4 in the ones place yields 1368\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1368:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 * 82",
        "answer": "Multiply 96 and 82 step by step:\nMultiplying 96 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n9 * 2 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 96 by the 2 in the ones place yields 192\n\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the tens place\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n9 * 8 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7680\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 192 + 7680:\n\nAdd 7680 and 192 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7872\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7872"
    },
    {
        "question": "516 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 516 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 516 by the 4 in the ones place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n1 * 4 + 2 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 516 by the 4 in the ones place yields 2064\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2064:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 * 43",
        "answer": "Multiply 70 and 43 step by step:\nMultiplying 70 by the 3 in the ones place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 70 by the 3 in the ones place yields 210\n\nMultiplying 70 by the 4 in the tens place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 70 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 210 + 2800:\n\nAdd 2800 and 210 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3010\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3010"
    },
    {
        "question": "34 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 34 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 34 by the 5 in the ones place\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n3 * 5 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 34 by the 5 in the ones place yields 170\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 170:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "690 * 42",
        "answer": "Multiply 690 and 42 step by step:\nMultiplying 690 by the 2 in the ones place\n0 * 2 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 690 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1380\n\nMultiplying 690 by the 4 in the tens place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n6 * 4 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 690 by the 4 in the tens place yields 27600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1380 + 27600:\n\nAdd 27600 and 1380 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 28980\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 28980"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 51 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 51 by the 1 in the ones place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 51 by the 1 in the ones place yields 51\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 51:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 * 23",
        "answer": "Multiply 76 and 23 step by step:\nMultiplying 76 by the 3 in the ones place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n7 * 3 + 1 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 76 by the 3 in the ones place yields 228\n\nMultiplying 76 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 76 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1520\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 228 + 1520:\n\nAdd 1520 and 228 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1748\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1748"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 * 32",
        "answer": "Multiply 58 and 32 step by step:\nMultiplying 58 by the 2 in the ones place\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 58 by the 2 in the ones place yields 116\n\nMultiplying 58 by the 3 in the tens place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 3 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 58 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1740\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 116 + 1740:\n\nAdd 1740 and 116 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1856\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1856"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 45 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 45 by the 4 in the ones place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n4 * 4 + 2 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 45 by the 4 in the ones place yields 180\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 180:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 * 37",
        "answer": "Multiply 70 and 37 step by step:\nMultiplying 70 by the 7 in the ones place\n0 * 7 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 7 + 0 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 70 by the 7 in the ones place yields 490\n\nMultiplying 70 by the 3 in the tens place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 70 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2100\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 490 + 2100:\n\nAdd 2100 and 490 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2590\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2590"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 12 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 12 by the 3 in the ones place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 12 by the 3 in the ones place yields 36\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 36:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 * 48",
        "answer": "Multiply 76 and 48 step by step:\nMultiplying 76 by the 8 in the ones place\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n7 * 8 + 4 = 60 (carry 6, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 76 by the 8 in the ones place yields 608\n\nMultiplying 76 by the 4 in the tens place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n7 * 4 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 76 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3040\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 608 + 3040:\n\nAdd 3040 and 608 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3648\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3648"
    },
    {
        "question": "65 * 53",
        "answer": "Multiply 65 and 53 step by step:\nMultiplying 65 by the 3 in the ones place\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n6 * 3 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 65 by the 3 in the ones place yields 195\n\nMultiplying 65 by the 5 in the tens place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n6 * 5 + 2 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 65 by the 5 in the tens place yields 3250\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 195 + 3250:\n\nAdd 3250 and 195 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3445\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3445"
    },
    {
        "question": "891 * 60",
        "answer": "Multiply 891 and 60 step by step:\nMultiplying 891 by the 0 in the ones place\n1 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 891 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 891 by the 6 in the tens place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n8 * 6 + 5 = 53 (carry 5, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 891 by the 6 in the tens place yields 53460\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 53460:\n\nAdd 53460 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53460\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 53460"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 87 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 87 by the 1 in the ones place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 87 by the 1 in the ones place yields 87\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 87:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 45 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 45 by the 4 in the ones place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n4 * 4 + 2 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 45 by the 4 in the ones place yields 180\n\nMultiplying 45 by the 2 in the tens place\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n4 * 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 45 by the 2 in the tens place yields 900\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 180 + 900:\n\nAdd 900 and 180 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1080\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1080"
    },
    {
        "question": "24 * 17",
        "answer": "Multiply 24 and 17 step by step:\nMultiplying 24 by the 7 in the ones place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n2 * 7 + 2 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 24 by the 7 in the ones place yields 168\n\nMultiplying 24 by the 1 in the tens place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 24 by the 1 in the tens place yields 240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 168 + 240:\n\nAdd 240 and 168 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 408\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 408"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 15 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 15 by the 1 in the ones place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 15 by the 1 in the ones place yields 15\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 15:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 66 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 66 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 66 by the 2 in the ones place yields 132\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 132:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "349 * 46",
        "answer": "Multiply 349 and 46 step by step:\nMultiplying 349 by the 6 in the ones place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n4 * 6 + 5 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\n3 * 6 + 2 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 349 by the 6 in the ones place yields 2094\n\nMultiplying 349 by the 4 in the tens place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\n3 * 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 349 by the 4 in the tens place yields 13960\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2094 + 13960:\n\nAdd 13960 and 2094 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 16054\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 16054"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 51 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 51 by the 1 in the ones place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 51 by the 1 in the ones place yields 51\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 51:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "466 * 29",
        "answer": "Multiply 466 and 29 step by step:\nMultiplying 466 by the 9 in the ones place\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n6 * 9 + 5 = 59 (carry 5, remainder 9)\n4 * 9 + 5 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 466 by the 9 in the ones place yields 4194\n\nMultiplying 466 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n4 * 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 466 by the 2 in the tens place yields 9320\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4194 + 9320:\n\nAdd 9320 and 4194 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 13514\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 13514"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 61 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 61 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 61 by the 5 in the ones place yields 305\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 305:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "494 * 406",
        "answer": "Multiply 494 and 406 step by step:\nMultiplying 494 by the 6 in the ones place\n4 * 6 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n9 * 6 + 2 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n4 * 6 + 5 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 494 by the 6 in the ones place yields 2964\n\nMultiplying 494 by the 0 in the tens place\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 494 by the 0 in the tens place yields 0000\n\nMultiplying 494 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n9 * 4 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 494 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 197600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2964 + 0000 + 197600:\n\nAdd 2964 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2964\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 2964 + 197600\nAdd 197600 and 2964 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 0 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 2 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 200564\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 200564"
    },
    {
        "question": "29 * 14",
        "answer": "Multiply 29 and 14 step by step:\nMultiplying 29 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n2 * 4 + 3 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 29 by the 4 in the ones place yields 116\n\nMultiplying 29 by the 1 in the tens place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 29 by the 1 in the tens place yields 290\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 116 + 290:\n\nAdd 290 and 116 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 406\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 406"
    },
    {
        "question": "160 * 58",
        "answer": "Multiply 160 and 58 step by step:\nMultiplying 160 by the 8 in the ones place\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n1 * 8 + 4 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 160 by the 8 in the ones place yields 1280\n\nMultiplying 160 by the 5 in the tens place\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n1 * 5 + 3 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 160 by the 5 in the tens place yields 8000\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1280 + 8000:\n\nAdd 8000 and 1280 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9280\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 9280"
    },
    {
        "question": "760 * 559",
        "answer": "Multiply 760 and 559 step by step:\nMultiplying 760 by the 9 in the ones place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n7 * 9 + 5 = 68 (carry 6, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 760 by the 9 in the ones place yields 6840\n\nMultiplying 760 by the 5 in the tens place\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n7 * 5 + 3 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 760 by the 5 in the tens place yields 38000\n\nMultiplying 760 by the 5 in the hundreds place\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n7 * 5 + 3 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 760 by the 5 in the hundreds place yields 380000\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 6840 + 38000 + 380000:\n\nAdd 38000 and 6840 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 44840\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 44840 + 380000\nAdd 380000 and 44840 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 4 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 424840\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 424840"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 * 20",
        "answer": "Multiply 88 and 20 step by step:\nMultiplying 88 by the 0 in the ones place\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 88 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 88 by the 2 in the tens place\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 88 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1760\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 1760:\n\nAdd 1760 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1760\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1760"
    },
    {
        "question": "532 * 96",
        "answer": "Multiply 532 and 96 step by step:\nMultiplying 532 by the 6 in the ones place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n3 * 6 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\n5 * 6 + 1 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 532 by the 6 in the ones place yields 3192\n\nMultiplying 532 by the 9 in the tens place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n3 * 9 + 1 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n5 * 9 + 2 = 47 (carry 4, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 532 by the 9 in the tens place yields 47880\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3192 + 47880:\n\nAdd 47880 and 3192 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 3 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 51072\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 51072"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 * 83",
        "answer": "Multiply 90 and 83 step by step:\nMultiplying 90 by the 3 in the ones place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 90 by the 3 in the ones place yields 270\n\nMultiplying 90 by the 8 in the tens place\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 90 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 270 + 7200:\n\nAdd 7200 and 270 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7470\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7470"
    },
    {
        "question": "557 * 84",
        "answer": "Multiply 557 and 84 step by step:\nMultiplying 557 by the 4 in the ones place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 557 by the 4 in the ones place yields 2228\n\nMultiplying 557 by the 8 in the tens place\n7 * 8 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n5 * 8 + 5 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n5 * 8 + 4 = 44 (carry 4, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 557 by the 8 in the tens place yields 44560\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2228 + 44560:\n\nAdd 44560 and 2228 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 46788\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 46788"
    },
    {
        "question": "479 * 235",
        "answer": "Multiply 479 and 235 step by step:\nMultiplying 479 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n7 * 5 + 4 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\n4 * 5 + 3 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 479 by the 5 in the ones place yields 2395\n\nMultiplying 479 by the 3 in the tens place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\n4 * 3 + 2 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 479 by the 3 in the tens place yields 14370\n\nMultiplying 479 by the 2 in the hundreds place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n4 * 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 479 by the 2 in the hundreds place yields 95800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2395 + 14370 + 95800:\n\nAdd 14370 and 2395 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 16765\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 16765 + 95800\nAdd 95800 and 16765 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 112565\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 112565"
    },
    {
        "question": "496 * 50",
        "answer": "Multiply 496 and 50 step by step:\nMultiplying 496 by the 0 in the ones place\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 496 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 496 by the 5 in the tens place\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 3 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n4 * 5 + 4 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 496 by the 5 in the tens place yields 24800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 24800:\n\nAdd 24800 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 24800\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 24800"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 * 13",
        "answer": "Multiply 91 and 13 step by step:\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place yields 273\n\nMultiplying 91 by the 1 in the tens place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 91 by the 1 in the tens place yields 910\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 273 + 910:\n\nAdd 910 and 273 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 7 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1183\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1183"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 * 39",
        "answer": "Multiply 86 and 39 step by step:\nMultiplying 86 by the 9 in the ones place\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n8 * 9 + 5 = 77 (carry 7, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 86 by the 9 in the ones place yields 774\n\nMultiplying 86 by the 3 in the tens place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 86 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2580\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 774 + 2580:\n\nAdd 2580 and 774 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 7 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3354\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3354"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 56 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 56 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 56 by the 2 in the ones place yields 112\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 112:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 37 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 37 by the 7 in the ones place\n7 * 7 + 0 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\n3 * 7 + 4 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 37 by the 7 in the ones place yields 259\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 259:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 * 20",
        "answer": "Multiply 69 and 20 step by step:\nMultiplying 69 by the 0 in the ones place\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 69 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the tens place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 1380:\n\nAdd 1380 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1380\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1380"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 * 22",
        "answer": "Multiply 37 and 22 step by step:\nMultiplying 37 by the 2 in the ones place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n3 * 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 37 by the 2 in the ones place yields 74\n\nMultiplying 37 by the 2 in the tens place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n3 * 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 37 by the 2 in the tens place yields 740\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 74 + 740:\n\nAdd 740 and 74 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 814\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 814"
    },
    {
        "question": "306 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 306 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 306 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n0 * 2 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 306 by the 2 in the ones place yields 612\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 612:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 * 60",
        "answer": "Multiply 67 and 60 step by step:\nMultiplying 67 by the 0 in the ones place\n7 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 67 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 67 by the 6 in the tens place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n6 * 6 + 4 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 67 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4020\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 4020:\n\nAdd 4020 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4020\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4020"
    },
    {
        "question": "65 * 45",
        "answer": "Multiply 65 and 45 step by step:\nMultiplying 65 by the 5 in the ones place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n6 * 5 + 2 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 65 by the 5 in the ones place yields 325\n\nMultiplying 65 by the 4 in the tens place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n6 * 4 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 65 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 325 + 2600:\n\nAdd 2600 and 325 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2925\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2925"
    },
    {
        "question": "695 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 695 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 695 by the 6 in the ones place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n9 * 6 + 3 = 57 (carry 5, remainder 7)\n6 * 6 + 5 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 695 by the 6 in the ones place yields 4170\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4170:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "415 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 415 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 415 by the 7 in the ones place\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n1 * 7 + 3 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n4 * 7 + 1 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 415 by the 7 in the ones place yields 2905\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2905:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 36 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 36 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n3 * 6 + 3 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 36 by the 6 in the ones place yields 216\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 216:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "52 * 18",
        "answer": "Multiply 52 and 18 step by step:\nMultiplying 52 by the 8 in the ones place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n5 * 8 + 1 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 52 by the 8 in the ones place yields 416\n\nMultiplying 52 by the 1 in the tens place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 52 by the 1 in the tens place yields 520\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 416 + 520:\n\nAdd 520 and 416 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 936\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 936"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 * 47",
        "answer": "Multiply 79 and 47 step by step:\nMultiplying 79 by the 7 in the ones place\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n7 * 7 + 6 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 79 by the 7 in the ones place yields 553\n\nMultiplying 79 by the 4 in the tens place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n7 * 4 + 3 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 79 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3160\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 553 + 3160:\n\nAdd 3160 and 553 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 5 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3713\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3713"
    },
    {
        "question": "48 * 36",
        "answer": "Multiply 48 and 36 step by step:\nMultiplying 48 by the 6 in the ones place\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n4 * 6 + 4 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 48 by the 6 in the ones place yields 288\n\nMultiplying 48 by the 3 in the tens place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n4 * 3 + 2 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 48 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1440\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 288 + 1440:\n\nAdd 1440 and 288 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1728\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1728"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 22 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 22 by the 3 in the ones place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 22 by the 3 in the ones place yields 66\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 66:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "48 * 40",
        "answer": "Multiply 48 and 40 step by step:\nMultiplying 48 by the 0 in the ones place\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 48 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 48 by the 4 in the tens place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 48 by the 4 in the tens place yields 1920\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 1920:\n\nAdd 1920 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1920\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1920"
    },
    {
        "question": "808 * 482",
        "answer": "Multiply 808 and 482 step by step:\nMultiplying 808 by the 2 in the ones place\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n0 * 2 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 808 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1616\n\nMultiplying 808 by the 8 in the tens place\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\n0 * 8 + 6 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 808 by the 8 in the tens place yields 64640\n\nMultiplying 808 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n0 * 4 + 3 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 808 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 323200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1616 + 64640 + 323200:\n\nAdd 64640 and 1616 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 1 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 66256\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 66256 + 323200\nAdd 323200 and 66256 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 3 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 389456\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 389456"
    },
    {
        "question": "26 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 26 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 26 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n2 * 6 + 3 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 26 by the 6 in the ones place yields 156\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 156:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "451 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 451 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 451 by the 1 in the ones place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 451 by the 1 in the ones place yields 451\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 451:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 * 37",
        "answer": "Multiply 38 and 37 step by step:\nMultiplying 38 by the 7 in the ones place\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n3 * 7 + 5 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 38 by the 7 in the ones place yields 266\n\nMultiplying 38 by the 3 in the tens place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n3 * 3 + 2 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 38 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1140\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 266 + 1140:\n\nAdd 1140 and 266 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1406\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1406"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 * 61",
        "answer": "Multiply 73 and 61 step by step:\nMultiplying 73 by the 1 in the ones place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 73 by the 1 in the ones place yields 73\n\nMultiplying 73 by the 6 in the tens place\n3 * 6 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n7 * 6 + 1 = 43 (carry 4, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 73 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 73 + 4380:\n\nAdd 4380 and 73 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4453\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4453"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 61 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 61 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 61 by the 4 in the ones place yields 244\n\nMultiplying 61 by the 2 in the tens place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 61 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1220\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 244 + 1220:\n\nAdd 1220 and 244 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1464\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1464"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 * 17",
        "answer": "Multiply 22 and 17 step by step:\nMultiplying 22 by the 7 in the ones place\n2 * 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n2 * 7 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 22 by the 7 in the ones place yields 154\n\nMultiplying 22 by the 1 in the tens place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 22 by the 1 in the tens place yields 220\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 154 + 220:\n\nAdd 220 and 154 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 374\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 374"
    },
    {
        "question": "77 * 28",
        "answer": "Multiply 77 and 28 step by step:\nMultiplying 77 by the 8 in the ones place\n7 * 8 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n7 * 8 + 5 = 61 (carry 6, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 77 by the 8 in the ones place yields 616\n\nMultiplying 77 by the 2 in the tens place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 77 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1540\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 616 + 1540:\n\nAdd 1540 and 616 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2156\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2156"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 66 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 66 by the 1 in the ones place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 66 by the 1 in the ones place yields 66\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 66:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "55 * 29",
        "answer": "Multiply 55 and 29 step by step:\nMultiplying 55 by the 9 in the ones place\n5 * 9 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n5 * 9 + 4 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 55 by the 9 in the ones place yields 495\n\nMultiplying 55 by the 2 in the tens place\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 55 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1100\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 495 + 1100:\n\nAdd 1100 and 495 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1595\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1595"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 * 53",
        "answer": "Multiply 87 and 53 step by step:\nMultiplying 87 by the 3 in the ones place\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n8 * 3 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 87 by the 3 in the ones place yields 261\n\nMultiplying 87 by the 5 in the tens place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 3 = 43 (carry 4, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 87 by the 5 in the tens place yields 4350\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 261 + 4350:\n\nAdd 4350 and 261 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4611\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4611"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 * 46",
        "answer": "Multiply 56 and 46 step by step:\nMultiplying 56 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n5 * 6 + 3 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 56 by the 6 in the ones place yields 336\n\nMultiplying 56 by the 4 in the tens place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 56 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 336 + 2240:\n\nAdd 2240 and 336 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2576\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2576"
    },
    {
        "question": "21 * 20",
        "answer": "Multiply 21 and 20 step by step:\nMultiplying 21 by the 0 in the ones place\n1 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 21 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 21 by the 2 in the tens place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 21 by the 2 in the tens place yields 420\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 420:\n\nAdd 420 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 420\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 420"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 72 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 72 by the 4 in the ones place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 72 by the 4 in the ones place yields 288\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 288:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "206 * 66",
        "answer": "Multiply 206 and 66 step by step:\nMultiplying 206 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n0 * 6 + 3 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 206 by the 6 in the ones place yields 1236\n\nMultiplying 206 by the 6 in the tens place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n0 * 6 + 3 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 206 by the 6 in the tens place yields 12360\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1236 + 12360:\n\nAdd 12360 and 1236 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 13596\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 13596"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 50 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 50 by the 9 in the ones place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 9 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 50 by the 9 in the ones place yields 450\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 450:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "206 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 206 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 206 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n0 * 2 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 206 by the 2 in the ones place yields 412\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 412:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 * 55",
        "answer": "Multiply 73 and 55 step by step:\nMultiplying 73 by the 5 in the ones place\n3 * 5 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n7 * 5 + 1 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 73 by the 5 in the ones place yields 365\n\nMultiplying 73 by the 5 in the tens place\n3 * 5 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n7 * 5 + 1 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 73 by the 5 in the tens place yields 3650\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 365 + 3650:\n\nAdd 3650 and 365 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4015\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4015"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 22 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 22 by the 6 in the ones place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n2 * 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 22 by the 6 in the ones place yields 132\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 132:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 13 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 13 by the 2 in the ones place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 13 by the 2 in the ones place yields 26\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 26:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "407 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 407 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 407 by the 8 in the ones place\n7 * 8 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n0 * 8 + 5 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n4 * 8 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 407 by the 8 in the ones place yields 3256\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3256:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "182 * 94",
        "answer": "Multiply 182 and 94 step by step:\nMultiplying 182 by the 4 in the ones place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n1 * 4 + 3 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 182 by the 4 in the ones place yields 728\n\nMultiplying 182 by the 9 in the tens place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n8 * 9 + 1 = 73 (carry 7, remainder 3)\n1 * 9 + 7 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 182 by the 9 in the tens place yields 16380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 728 + 16380:\n\nAdd 16380 and 728 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 7 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 17108\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 17108"
    },
    {
        "question": "467 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 467 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 467 by the 9 in the ones place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n6 * 9 + 6 = 60 (carry 6, remainder 0)\n4 * 9 + 6 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 467 by the 9 in the ones place yields 4203\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4203:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "999 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 999 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 999 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n9 * 5 + 4 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\n9 * 5 + 4 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 999 by the 5 in the ones place yields 4995\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4995:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 * 25",
        "answer": "Multiply 59 and 25 step by step:\nMultiplying 59 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 4 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 59 by the 5 in the ones place yields 295\n\nMultiplying 59 by the 2 in the tens place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 59 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1180\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 295 + 1180:\n\nAdd 1180 and 295 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1475\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1475"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 * 85",
        "answer": "Multiply 89 and 85 step by step:\nMultiplying 89 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 4 = 44 (carry 4, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 89 by the 5 in the ones place yields 445\n\nMultiplying 89 by the 8 in the tens place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n8 * 8 + 7 = 71 (carry 7, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 89 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7120\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 445 + 7120:\n\nAdd 7120 and 445 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7565\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7565"
    },
    {
        "question": "126 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 126 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 126 by the 9 in the ones place\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n2 * 9 + 5 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\n1 * 9 + 2 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 126 by the 9 in the ones place yields 1134\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1134:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "962 * 32",
        "answer": "Multiply 962 and 32 step by step:\nMultiplying 962 by the 2 in the ones place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n9 * 2 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 962 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1924\n\nMultiplying 962 by the 3 in the tens place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n9 * 3 + 1 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 962 by the 3 in the tens place yields 28860\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1924 + 28860:\n\nAdd 28860 and 1924 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 30784\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 30784"
    },
    {
        "question": "793 * 51",
        "answer": "Multiply 793 and 51 step by step:\nMultiplying 793 by the 1 in the ones place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 793 by the 1 in the ones place yields 793\n\nMultiplying 793 by the 5 in the tens place\n3 * 5 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n9 * 5 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\n7 * 5 + 4 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 793 by the 5 in the tens place yields 39650\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 793 + 39650:\n\nAdd 39650 and 793 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 7 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 40443\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 40443"
    },
    {
        "question": "842 * 59",
        "answer": "Multiply 842 and 59 step by step:\nMultiplying 842 by the 9 in the ones place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n4 * 9 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\n8 * 9 + 3 = 75 (carry 7, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 842 by the 9 in the ones place yields 7578\n\nMultiplying 842 by the 5 in the tens place\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n4 * 5 + 1 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n8 * 5 + 2 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 842 by the 5 in the tens place yields 42100\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 7578 + 42100:\n\nAdd 42100 and 7578 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 49678\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 49678"
    },
    {
        "question": "649 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 649 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 649 by the 7 in the ones place\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n4 * 7 + 6 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\n6 * 7 + 3 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 649 by the 7 in the ones place yields 4543\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4543:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "804 * 37",
        "answer": "Multiply 804 and 37 step by step:\nMultiplying 804 by the 7 in the ones place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n0 * 7 + 2 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 804 by the 7 in the ones place yields 5628\n\nMultiplying 804 by the 3 in the tens place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n0 * 3 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 804 by the 3 in the tens place yields 24120\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5628 + 24120:\n\nAdd 24120 and 5628 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 29748\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 29748"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 * 65",
        "answer": "Multiply 75 and 65 step by step:\nMultiplying 75 by the 5 in the ones place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n7 * 5 + 2 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 75 by the 5 in the ones place yields 375\n\nMultiplying 75 by the 6 in the tens place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n7 * 6 + 3 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 75 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 375 + 4500:\n\nAdd 4500 and 375 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4875\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4875"
    },
    {
        "question": "777 * 397",
        "answer": "Multiply 777 and 397 step by step:\nMultiplying 777 by the 7 in the ones place\n7 * 7 + 0 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\n7 * 7 + 4 = 53 (carry 5, remainder 3)\n7 * 7 + 5 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 777 by the 7 in the ones place yields 5439\n\nMultiplying 777 by the 9 in the tens place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n7 * 9 + 6 = 69 (carry 6, remainder 9)\n7 * 9 + 6 = 69 (carry 6, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 777 by the 9 in the tens place yields 69930\n\nMultiplying 777 by the 3 in the hundreds place\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 777 by the 3 in the hundreds place yields 233100\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5439 + 69930 + 233100:\n\nAdd 69930 and 5439 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 75369\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 75369 + 233100\nAdd 233100 and 75369 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 3 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 308469\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 308469"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 * 30",
        "answer": "Multiply 58 and 30 step by step:\nMultiplying 58 by the 0 in the ones place\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 58 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 58 by the 3 in the tens place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 3 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 58 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1740\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 1740:\n\nAdd 1740 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1740\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1740"
    },
    {
        "question": "564 * 433",
        "answer": "Multiply 564 and 433 step by step:\nMultiplying 564 by the 3 in the ones place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n6 * 3 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\n5 * 3 + 1 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 564 by the 3 in the ones place yields 1692\n\nMultiplying 564 by the 3 in the tens place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n6 * 3 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\n5 * 3 + 1 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 564 by the 3 in the tens place yields 16920\n\nMultiplying 564 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n6 * 4 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 564 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 225600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1692 + 16920 + 225600:\n\nAdd 16920 and 1692 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 18612\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 18612 + 225600\nAdd 225600 and 18612 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 8 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 2 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 244212\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 244212"
    },
    {
        "question": "284 * 84",
        "answer": "Multiply 284 and 84 step by step:\nMultiplying 284 by the 4 in the ones place\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 4 + 1 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\n2 * 4 + 3 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 284 by the 4 in the ones place yields 1136\n\nMultiplying 284 by the 8 in the tens place\n4 * 8 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n8 * 8 + 3 = 67 (carry 6, remainder 7)\n2 * 8 + 6 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 284 by the 8 in the tens place yields 22720\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1136 + 22720:\n\nAdd 22720 and 1136 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 23856\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 23856"
    },
    {
        "question": "842 * 523",
        "answer": "Multiply 842 and 523 step by step:\nMultiplying 842 by the 3 in the ones place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 842 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2526\n\nMultiplying 842 by the 2 in the tens place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 842 by the 2 in the tens place yields 16840\n\nMultiplying 842 by the 5 in the hundreds place\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n4 * 5 + 1 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n8 * 5 + 2 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 842 by the 5 in the hundreds place yields 421000\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2526 + 16840 + 421000:\n\nAdd 16840 and 2526 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 19366\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 19366 + 421000\nAdd 421000 and 19366 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 4 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 440366\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 440366"
    },
    {
        "question": "451 * 72",
        "answer": "Multiply 451 and 72 step by step:\nMultiplying 451 by the 2 in the ones place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n4 * 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 451 by the 2 in the ones place yields 902\n\nMultiplying 451 by the 7 in the tens place\n1 * 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n4 * 7 + 3 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 451 by the 7 in the tens place yields 31570\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 902 + 31570:\n\nAdd 31570 and 902 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 32472\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 32472"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 28 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 28 by the 8 in the ones place\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\n2 * 8 + 6 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 28 by the 8 in the ones place yields 224\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 224:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "521 * 28",
        "answer": "Multiply 521 and 28 step by step:\nMultiplying 521 by the 8 in the ones place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n5 * 8 + 1 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 521 by the 8 in the ones place yields 4168\n\nMultiplying 521 by the 2 in the tens place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 521 by the 2 in the tens place yields 10420\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4168 + 10420:\n\nAdd 10420 and 4168 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 14588\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 14588"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 91 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place yields 273\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 273:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "814 * 709",
        "answer": "Multiply 814 and 709 step by step:\nMultiplying 814 by the 9 in the ones place\n4 * 9 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n1 * 9 + 3 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n8 * 9 + 1 = 73 (carry 7, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 814 by the 9 in the ones place yields 7326\n\nMultiplying 814 by the 0 in the tens place\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n1 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 814 by the 0 in the tens place yields 0000\n\nMultiplying 814 by the 7 in the hundreds place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n1 * 7 + 2 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 814 by the 7 in the hundreds place yields 569800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 7326 + 0000 + 569800:\n\nAdd 7326 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7326\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 7326 + 569800\nAdd 569800 and 7326 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 5 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 577126\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 577126"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 11 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 11 by the 2 in the ones place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 11 by the 2 in the ones place yields 22\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 22:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "783 * 13",
        "answer": "Multiply 783 and 13 step by step:\nMultiplying 783 by the 3 in the ones place\n3 * 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 783 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2349\n\nMultiplying 783 by the 1 in the tens place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 783 by the 1 in the tens place yields 7830\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2349 + 7830:\n\nAdd 7830 and 2349 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 2 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 10179\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 10179"
    },
    {
        "question": "891 * 638",
        "answer": "Multiply 891 and 638 step by step:\nMultiplying 891 by the 8 in the ones place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n8 * 8 + 7 = 71 (carry 7, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 891 by the 8 in the ones place yields 7128\n\nMultiplying 891 by the 3 in the tens place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n8 * 3 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 891 by the 3 in the tens place yields 26730\n\nMultiplying 891 by the 6 in the hundreds place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n8 * 6 + 5 = 53 (carry 5, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 891 by the 6 in the hundreds place yields 534600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 7128 + 26730 + 534600:\n\nAdd 26730 and 7128 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 33858\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 33858 + 534600\nAdd 534600 and 33858 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 5 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 568458\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 568458"
    },
    {
        "question": "752 * 360",
        "answer": "Multiply 752 and 360 step by step:\nMultiplying 752 by the 0 in the ones place\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 752 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 752 by the 6 in the tens place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n5 * 6 + 1 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\n7 * 6 + 3 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 752 by the 6 in the tens place yields 45120\n\nMultiplying 752 by the 3 in the hundreds place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n7 * 3 + 1 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 752 by the 3 in the hundreds place yields 225600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 45120 + 225600:\n\nAdd 45120 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45120\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 45120 + 225600\nAdd 225600 and 45120 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 4 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 2 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 270720\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 270720"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 * 23",
        "answer": "Multiply 59 and 23 step by step:\nMultiplying 59 by the 3 in the ones place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n5 * 3 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 59 by the 3 in the ones place yields 177\n\nMultiplying 59 by the 2 in the tens place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 59 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1180\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 177 + 1180:\n\nAdd 1180 and 177 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 1 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1357\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1357"
    },
    {
        "question": "894 * 51",
        "answer": "Multiply 894 and 51 step by step:\nMultiplying 894 by the 1 in the ones place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 894 by the 1 in the ones place yields 894\n\nMultiplying 894 by the 5 in the tens place\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 2 = 47 (carry 4, remainder 7)\n8 * 5 + 4 = 44 (carry 4, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 894 by the 5 in the tens place yields 44700\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 894 + 44700:\n\nAdd 44700 and 894 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45594\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 45594"
    },
    {
        "question": "100 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 100 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 100 by the 9 in the ones place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 100 by the 9 in the ones place yields 900\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 900:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 * 19",
        "answer": "Multiply 57 and 19 step by step:\nMultiplying 57 by the 9 in the ones place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n5 * 9 + 6 = 51 (carry 5, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 57 by the 9 in the ones place yields 513\n\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the tens place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the tens place yields 570\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 513 + 570:\n\nAdd 570 and 513 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1083\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1083"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 * 22",
        "answer": "Multiply 76 and 22 step by step:\nMultiplying 76 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 76 by the 2 in the ones place yields 152\n\nMultiplying 76 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 76 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1520\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 152 + 1520:\n\nAdd 1520 and 152 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1672\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1672"
    },
    {
        "question": "62 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 62 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 62 by the 5 in the ones place\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n6 * 5 + 1 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 62 by the 5 in the ones place yields 310\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 310:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 15 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 15 by the 1 in the ones place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 15 by the 1 in the ones place yields 15\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 15:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "535 * 162",
        "answer": "Multiply 535 and 162 step by step:\nMultiplying 535 by the 2 in the ones place\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n3 * 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 535 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1070\n\nMultiplying 535 by the 6 in the tens place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n3 * 6 + 3 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n5 * 6 + 2 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 535 by the 6 in the tens place yields 32100\n\nMultiplying 535 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 535 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 53500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1070 + 32100 + 53500:\n\nAdd 32100 and 1070 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 33170\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 33170 + 53500\nAdd 53500 and 33170 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 86670\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 86670"
    },
    {
        "question": "126 * 27",
        "answer": "Multiply 126 and 27 step by step:\nMultiplying 126 by the 7 in the ones place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n2 * 7 + 4 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n1 * 7 + 1 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 126 by the 7 in the ones place yields 882\n\nMultiplying 126 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n2 * 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 126 by the 2 in the tens place yields 2520\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 882 + 2520:\n\nAdd 2520 and 882 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 8 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3402\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3402"
    },
    {
        "question": "856 * 33",
        "answer": "Multiply 856 and 33 step by step:\nMultiplying 856 by the 3 in the ones place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n5 * 3 + 1 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 856 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2568\n\nMultiplying 856 by the 3 in the tens place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n5 * 3 + 1 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 856 by the 3 in the tens place yields 25680\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2568 + 25680:\n\nAdd 25680 and 2568 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 5 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 28248\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 28248"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 * 43",
        "answer": "Multiply 97 and 43 step by step:\nMultiplying 97 by the 3 in the ones place\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n9 * 3 + 2 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 97 by the 3 in the ones place yields 291\n\nMultiplying 97 by the 4 in the tens place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n9 * 4 + 2 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 97 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3880\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 291 + 3880:\n\nAdd 3880 and 291 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4171\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4171"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 81 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 81 by the 1 in the ones place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 81 by the 1 in the ones place yields 81\n\nMultiplying 81 by the 1 in the tens place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 81 by the 1 in the tens place yields 810\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 81 + 810:\n\nAdd 810 and 81 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 891\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 891"
    },
    {
        "question": "21 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 21 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 21 by the 6 in the ones place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 21 by the 6 in the ones place yields 126\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 126:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "765 * 29",
        "answer": "Multiply 765 and 29 step by step:\nMultiplying 765 by the 9 in the ones place\n5 * 9 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n6 * 9 + 4 = 58 (carry 5, remainder 8)\n7 * 9 + 5 = 68 (carry 6, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 765 by the 9 in the ones place yields 6885\n\nMultiplying 765 by the 2 in the tens place\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 765 by the 2 in the tens place yields 15300\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 6885 + 15300:\n\nAdd 15300 and 6885 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 22185\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 22185"
    },
    {
        "question": "46 * 30",
        "answer": "Multiply 46 and 30 step by step:\nMultiplying 46 by the 0 in the ones place\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 46 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 46 by the 3 in the tens place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n4 * 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 46 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 1380:\n\nAdd 1380 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1380\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1380"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 * 43",
        "answer": "Multiply 80 and 43 step by step:\nMultiplying 80 by the 3 in the ones place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 80 by the 3 in the ones place yields 240\n\nMultiplying 80 by the 4 in the tens place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 80 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 240 + 3200:\n\nAdd 3200 and 240 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3440\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3440"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 * 35",
        "answer": "Multiply 50 and 35 step by step:\nMultiplying 50 by the 5 in the ones place\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 50 by the 5 in the ones place yields 250\n\nMultiplying 50 by the 3 in the tens place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 50 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 250 + 1500:\n\nAdd 1500 and 250 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1750\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1750"
    },
    {
        "question": "547 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 547 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 547 by the 4 in the ones place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n4 * 4 + 2 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n5 * 4 + 1 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 547 by the 4 in the ones place yields 2188\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2188:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "960 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 960 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 960 by the 2 in the ones place\n0 * 2 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n9 * 2 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 960 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1920\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1920:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "321 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 321 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 321 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n3 * 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 321 by the 4 in the ones place yields 1284\n\nMultiplying 321 by the 2 in the tens place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 321 by the 2 in the tens place yields 6420\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1284 + 6420:\n\nAdd 6420 and 1284 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7704\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7704"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 * 74",
        "answer": "Multiply 98 and 74 step by step:\nMultiplying 98 by the 4 in the ones place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n9 * 4 + 3 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 98 by the 4 in the ones place yields 392\n\nMultiplying 98 by the 7 in the tens place\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n9 * 7 + 5 = 68 (carry 6, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 98 by the 7 in the tens place yields 6860\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 392 + 6860:\n\nAdd 6860 and 392 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7252\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7252"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 * 22",
        "answer": "Multiply 69 and 22 step by step:\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the ones place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the ones place yields 138\n\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the tens place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 138 + 1380:\n\nAdd 1380 and 138 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1518\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1518"
    },
    {
        "question": "630 * 71",
        "answer": "Multiply 630 and 71 step by step:\nMultiplying 630 by the 1 in the ones place\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 630 by the 1 in the ones place yields 630\n\nMultiplying 630 by the 7 in the tens place\n0 * 7 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 7 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n6 * 7 + 2 = 44 (carry 4, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 630 by the 7 in the tens place yields 44100\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 630 + 44100:\n\nAdd 44100 and 630 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 44730\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 44730"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 92 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 92 by the 4 in the ones place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 92 by the 4 in the ones place yields 368\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 368:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "291 * 79",
        "answer": "Multiply 291 and 79 step by step:\nMultiplying 291 by the 9 in the ones place\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\n2 * 9 + 8 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 291 by the 9 in the ones place yields 2619\n\nMultiplying 291 by the 7 in the tens place\n1 * 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n2 * 7 + 6 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 291 by the 7 in the tens place yields 20370\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2619 + 20370:\n\nAdd 20370 and 2619 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 22989\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 22989"
    },
    {
        "question": "465 * 20",
        "answer": "Multiply 465 and 20 step by step:\nMultiplying 465 by the 0 in the ones place\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 465 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 465 by the 2 in the tens place\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n4 * 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 465 by the 2 in the tens place yields 9300\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 9300:\n\nAdd 9300 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9300\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 9300"
    },
    {
        "question": "476 * 16",
        "answer": "Multiply 476 and 16 step by step:\nMultiplying 476 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n7 * 6 + 3 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n4 * 6 + 4 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 476 by the 6 in the ones place yields 2856\n\nMultiplying 476 by the 1 in the tens place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 476 by the 1 in the tens place yields 4760\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2856 + 4760:\n\nAdd 4760 and 2856 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 8 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7616\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7616"
    },
    {
        "question": "476 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 476 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 476 by the 4 in the ones place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n7 * 4 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 476 by the 4 in the ones place yields 1904\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1904:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "478 * 66",
        "answer": "Multiply 478 and 66 step by step:\nMultiplying 478 by the 6 in the ones place\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n7 * 6 + 4 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\n4 * 6 + 4 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 478 by the 6 in the ones place yields 2868\n\nMultiplying 478 by the 6 in the tens place\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n7 * 6 + 4 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\n4 * 6 + 4 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 478 by the 6 in the tens place yields 28680\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2868 + 28680:\n\nAdd 28680 and 2868 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 8 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 31548\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 31548"
    },
    {
        "question": "132 * 57",
        "answer": "Multiply 132 and 57 step by step:\nMultiplying 132 by the 7 in the ones place\n2 * 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n3 * 7 + 1 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\n1 * 7 + 2 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 132 by the 7 in the ones place yields 924\n\nMultiplying 132 by the 5 in the tens place\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n3 * 5 + 1 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n1 * 5 + 1 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 132 by the 5 in the tens place yields 6600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 924 + 6600:\n\nAdd 6600 and 924 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7524\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7524"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 45 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 45 by the 4 in the ones place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n4 * 4 + 2 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 45 by the 4 in the ones place yields 180\n\nMultiplying 45 by the 2 in the tens place\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n4 * 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 45 by the 2 in the tens place yields 900\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 180 + 900:\n\nAdd 900 and 180 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1080\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1080"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 70 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 70 by the 7 in the ones place\n0 * 7 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 7 + 0 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 70 by the 7 in the ones place yields 490\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 490:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "789 * 653",
        "answer": "Multiply 789 and 653 step by step:\nMultiplying 789 by the 3 in the ones place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n8 * 3 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 789 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2367\n\nMultiplying 789 by the 5 in the tens place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 4 = 44 (carry 4, remainder 4)\n7 * 5 + 4 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 789 by the 5 in the tens place yields 39450\n\nMultiplying 789 by the 6 in the hundreds place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n8 * 6 + 5 = 53 (carry 5, remainder 3)\n7 * 6 + 5 = 47 (carry 4, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 789 by the 6 in the hundreds place yields 473400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2367 + 39450 + 473400:\n\nAdd 39450 and 2367 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 41817\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 41817 + 473400\nAdd 473400 and 41817 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 5 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 515217\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 515217"
    },
    {
        "question": "217 * 95",
        "answer": "Multiply 217 and 95 step by step:\nMultiplying 217 by the 5 in the ones place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n1 * 5 + 3 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 217 by the 5 in the ones place yields 1085\n\nMultiplying 217 by the 9 in the tens place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n1 * 9 + 6 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n2 * 9 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 217 by the 9 in the tens place yields 19530\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1085 + 19530:\n\nAdd 19530 and 1085 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 20615\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 20615"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 * 34",
        "answer": "Multiply 78 and 34 step by step:\nMultiplying 78 by the 4 in the ones place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n7 * 4 + 3 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 78 by the 4 in the ones place yields 312\n\nMultiplying 78 by the 3 in the tens place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 78 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2340\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 312 + 2340:\n\nAdd 2340 and 312 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2652\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2652"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 * 44",
        "answer": "Multiply 67 and 44 step by step:\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the ones place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n6 * 4 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the ones place yields 268\n\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the tens place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n6 * 4 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2680\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 268 + 2680:\n\nAdd 2680 and 268 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2948\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2948"
    },
    {
        "question": "447 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 447 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 447 by the 6 in the ones place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n4 * 6 + 4 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n4 * 6 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 447 by the 6 in the ones place yields 2682\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2682:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "82 * 64",
        "answer": "Multiply 82 and 64 step by step:\nMultiplying 82 by the 4 in the ones place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 82 by the 4 in the ones place yields 328\n\nMultiplying 82 by the 6 in the tens place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n8 * 6 + 1 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 82 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4920\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 328 + 4920:\n\nAdd 4920 and 328 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5248\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5248"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 84 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 84 by the 9 in the ones place\n4 * 9 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n8 * 9 + 3 = 75 (carry 7, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 84 by the 9 in the ones place yields 756\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 756:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 74 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 74 by the 1 in the ones place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 74 by the 1 in the ones place yields 74\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 74:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "261 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 261 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 261 by the 2 in the ones place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n2 * 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 261 by the 2 in the ones place yields 522\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 522:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "863 * 63",
        "answer": "Multiply 863 and 63 step by step:\nMultiplying 863 by the 3 in the ones place\n3 * 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 863 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2589\n\nMultiplying 863 by the 6 in the tens place\n3 * 6 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 6 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\n8 * 6 + 3 = 51 (carry 5, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 863 by the 6 in the tens place yields 51780\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2589 + 51780:\n\nAdd 51780 and 2589 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 54369\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 54369"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 84 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 84 by the 6 in the ones place\n4 * 6 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n8 * 6 + 2 = 50 (carry 5, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 84 by the 6 in the ones place yields 504\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 504:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 * 87",
        "answer": "Multiply 94 and 87 step by step:\nMultiplying 94 by the 7 in the ones place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n9 * 7 + 2 = 65 (carry 6, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 94 by the 7 in the ones place yields 658\n\nMultiplying 94 by the 8 in the tens place\n4 * 8 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n9 * 8 + 3 = 75 (carry 7, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 94 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7520\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 658 + 7520:\n\nAdd 7520 and 658 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8178\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8178"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 88 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 88 by the 9 in the ones place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n8 * 9 + 7 = 79 (carry 7, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 88 by the 9 in the ones place yields 792\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 792:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 * 61",
        "answer": "Multiply 72 and 61 step by step:\nMultiplying 72 by the 1 in the ones place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 72 by the 1 in the ones place yields 72\n\nMultiplying 72 by the 6 in the tens place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 6 + 1 = 43 (carry 4, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 72 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4320\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 72 + 4320:\n\nAdd 4320 and 72 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4392\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4392"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 * 49",
        "answer": "Multiply 90 and 49 step by step:\nMultiplying 90 by the 9 in the ones place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 90 by the 9 in the ones place yields 810\n\nMultiplying 90 by the 4 in the tens place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 90 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 810 + 3600:\n\nAdd 3600 and 810 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 8 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4410\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4410"
    },
    {
        "question": "568 * 446",
        "answer": "Multiply 568 and 446 step by step:\nMultiplying 568 by the 6 in the ones place\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n6 * 6 + 4 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n5 * 6 + 4 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 568 by the 6 in the ones place yields 3408\n\nMultiplying 568 by the 4 in the tens place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n6 * 4 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 568 by the 4 in the tens place yields 22720\n\nMultiplying 568 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n6 * 4 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 568 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 227200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3408 + 22720 + 227200:\n\nAdd 22720 and 3408 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 3 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 26128\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 26128 + 227200\nAdd 227200 and 26128 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 2 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 253328\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 253328"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 28 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the ones place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the ones place yields 28\n\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the tens place yields 280\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 28 + 280:\n\nAdd 280 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 308\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 308"
    },
    {
        "question": "530 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 530 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 530 by the 3 in the ones place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 530 by the 3 in the ones place yields 1590\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1590:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "711 * 35",
        "answer": "Multiply 711 and 35 step by step:\nMultiplying 711 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 711 by the 5 in the ones place yields 3555\n\nMultiplying 711 by the 3 in the tens place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 711 by the 3 in the tens place yields 21330\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3555 + 21330:\n\nAdd 21330 and 3555 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 24885\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 24885"
    },
    {
        "question": "29 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 29 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 29 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n2 * 4 + 3 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 29 by the 4 in the ones place yields 116\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 116:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "224 * 27",
        "answer": "Multiply 224 and 27 step by step:\nMultiplying 224 by the 7 in the ones place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n2 * 7 + 2 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n2 * 7 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 224 by the 7 in the ones place yields 1568\n\nMultiplying 224 by the 2 in the tens place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 224 by the 2 in the tens place yields 4480\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1568 + 4480:\n\nAdd 4480 and 1568 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 5 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 1 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 6048\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6048"
    },
    {
        "question": "776 * 526",
        "answer": "Multiply 776 and 526 step by step:\nMultiplying 776 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n7 * 6 + 3 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n7 * 6 + 4 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 776 by the 6 in the ones place yields 4656\n\nMultiplying 776 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 776 by the 2 in the tens place yields 15520\n\nMultiplying 776 by the 5 in the hundreds place\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n7 * 5 + 3 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\n7 * 5 + 3 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 776 by the 5 in the hundreds place yields 388000\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4656 + 15520 + 388000:\n\nAdd 15520 and 4656 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 20176\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 20176 + 388000\nAdd 388000 and 20176 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 4 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 408176\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 408176"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 * 44",
        "answer": "Multiply 85 and 44 step by step:\nMultiplying 85 by the 4 in the ones place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n8 * 4 + 2 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 85 by the 4 in the ones place yields 340\n\nMultiplying 85 by the 4 in the tens place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n8 * 4 + 2 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 85 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 340 + 3400:\n\nAdd 3400 and 340 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3740\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3740"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 * 16",
        "answer": "Multiply 84 and 16 step by step:\nMultiplying 84 by the 6 in the ones place\n4 * 6 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n8 * 6 + 2 = 50 (carry 5, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 84 by the 6 in the ones place yields 504\n\nMultiplying 84 by the 1 in the tens place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 84 by the 1 in the tens place yields 840\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 504 + 840:\n\nAdd 840 and 504 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 5 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1344\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1344"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 10 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 10 by the 3 in the ones place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 10 by the 3 in the ones place yields 30\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 30:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "54 * 39",
        "answer": "Multiply 54 and 39 step by step:\nMultiplying 54 by the 9 in the ones place\n4 * 9 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n5 * 9 + 3 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 54 by the 9 in the ones place yields 486\n\nMultiplying 54 by the 3 in the tens place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n5 * 3 + 1 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 54 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1620\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 486 + 1620:\n\nAdd 1620 and 486 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2106\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2106"
    },
    {
        "question": "394 * 102",
        "answer": "Multiply 394 and 102 step by step:\nMultiplying 394 by the 2 in the ones place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n3 * 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 394 by the 2 in the ones place yields 788\n\nMultiplying 394 by the 0 in the tens place\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 394 by the 0 in the tens place yields 0000\n\nMultiplying 394 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 394 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 39400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 788 + 0000 + 39400:\n\nAdd 788 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 788\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 788 + 39400\nAdd 39400 and 788 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 40188\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 40188"
    },
    {
        "question": "613 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 613 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 613 by the 9 in the ones place\n3 * 9 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n1 * 9 + 2 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\n6 * 9 + 1 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 613 by the 9 in the ones place yields 5517\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5517:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 14 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 14 by the 2 in the ones place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 14 by the 2 in the ones place yields 28\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 28:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "927 * 46",
        "answer": "Multiply 927 and 46 step by step:\nMultiplying 927 by the 6 in the ones place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n2 * 6 + 4 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n9 * 6 + 1 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 927 by the 6 in the ones place yields 5562\n\nMultiplying 927 by the 4 in the tens place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n2 * 4 + 2 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n9 * 4 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 927 by the 4 in the tens place yields 37080\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5562 + 37080:\n\nAdd 37080 and 5562 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 5 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 42642\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 42642"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 * 61",
        "answer": "Multiply 84 and 61 step by step:\nMultiplying 84 by the 1 in the ones place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 84 by the 1 in the ones place yields 84\n\nMultiplying 84 by the 6 in the tens place\n4 * 6 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n8 * 6 + 2 = 50 (carry 5, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 84 by the 6 in the tens place yields 5040\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 84 + 5040:\n\nAdd 5040 and 84 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5124\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5124"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 * 64",
        "answer": "Multiply 98 and 64 step by step:\nMultiplying 98 by the 4 in the ones place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n9 * 4 + 3 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 98 by the 4 in the ones place yields 392\n\nMultiplying 98 by the 6 in the tens place\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n9 * 6 + 4 = 58 (carry 5, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 98 by the 6 in the tens place yields 5880\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 392 + 5880:\n\nAdd 5880 and 392 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6272\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6272"
    },
    {
        "question": "75 * 71",
        "answer": "Multiply 75 and 71 step by step:\nMultiplying 75 by the 1 in the ones place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 75 by the 1 in the ones place yields 75\n\nMultiplying 75 by the 7 in the tens place\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n7 * 7 + 3 = 52 (carry 5, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 75 by the 7 in the tens place yields 5250\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 75 + 5250:\n\nAdd 5250 and 75 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5325\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5325"
    },
    {
        "question": "476 * 194",
        "answer": "Multiply 476 and 194 step by step:\nMultiplying 476 by the 4 in the ones place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n7 * 4 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 476 by the 4 in the ones place yields 1904\n\nMultiplying 476 by the 9 in the tens place\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n7 * 9 + 5 = 68 (carry 6, remainder 8)\n4 * 9 + 6 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 476 by the 9 in the tens place yields 42840\n\nMultiplying 476 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 476 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 47600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1904 + 42840 + 47600:\n\nAdd 42840 and 1904 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 44744\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 44744 + 47600\nAdd 47600 and 44744 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 4 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 92344\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 92344"
    },
    {
        "question": "221 * 55",
        "answer": "Multiply 221 and 55 step by step:\nMultiplying 221 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n2 * 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 221 by the 5 in the ones place yields 1105\n\nMultiplying 221 by the 5 in the tens place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n2 * 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 221 by the 5 in the tens place yields 11050\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1105 + 11050:\n\nAdd 11050 and 1105 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 12155\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 12155"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 * 12",
        "answer": "Multiply 61 and 12 step by step:\nMultiplying 61 by the 2 in the ones place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 61 by the 2 in the ones place yields 122\n\nMultiplying 61 by the 1 in the tens place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 61 by the 1 in the tens place yields 610\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 122 + 610:\n\nAdd 610 and 122 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 732\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 732"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 22 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 22 by the 6 in the ones place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n2 * 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 22 by the 6 in the ones place yields 132\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 132:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "43 * 10",
        "answer": "Multiply 43 and 10 step by step:\nMultiplying 43 by the 0 in the ones place\n3 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 43 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 43 by the 1 in the tens place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 43 by the 1 in the tens place yields 430\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 430:\n\nAdd 430 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 3 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 430\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 430"
    },
    {
        "question": "699 * 68",
        "answer": "Multiply 699 and 68 step by step:\nMultiplying 699 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n9 * 8 + 7 = 79 (carry 7, remainder 9)\n6 * 8 + 7 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 699 by the 8 in the ones place yields 5592\n\nMultiplying 699 by the 6 in the tens place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n9 * 6 + 5 = 59 (carry 5, remainder 9)\n6 * 6 + 5 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 699 by the 6 in the tens place yields 41940\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5592 + 41940:\n\nAdd 41940 and 5592 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 9 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 5 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 47532\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 47532"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 * 81",
        "answer": "Multiply 85 and 81 step by step:\nMultiplying 85 by the 1 in the ones place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 85 by the 1 in the ones place yields 85\n\nMultiplying 85 by the 8 in the tens place\n5 * 8 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n8 * 8 + 4 = 68 (carry 6, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 85 by the 8 in the tens place yields 6800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 85 + 6800:\n\nAdd 6800 and 85 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6885\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6885"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 * 60",
        "answer": "Multiply 61 and 60 step by step:\nMultiplying 61 by the 0 in the ones place\n1 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 61 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 61 by the 6 in the tens place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 61 by the 6 in the tens place yields 3660\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 3660:\n\nAdd 3660 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3660\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3660"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 36 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 36 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n3 * 6 + 3 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 36 by the 6 in the ones place yields 216\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 216:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "691 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 691 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 691 by the 9 in the ones place\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\n6 * 9 + 8 = 62 (carry 6, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 691 by the 9 in the ones place yields 6219\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 6219:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 * 89",
        "answer": "Multiply 92 and 89 step by step:\nMultiplying 92 by the 9 in the ones place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n9 * 9 + 1 = 82 (carry 8, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 92 by the 9 in the ones place yields 828\n\nMultiplying 92 by the 8 in the tens place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n9 * 8 + 1 = 73 (carry 7, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 92 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7360\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 828 + 7360:\n\nAdd 7360 and 828 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 8 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8188\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8188"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 * 13",
        "answer": "Multiply 22 and 13 step by step:\nMultiplying 22 by the 3 in the ones place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 22 by the 3 in the ones place yields 66\n\nMultiplying 22 by the 1 in the tens place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 22 by the 1 in the tens place yields 220\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 66 + 220:\n\nAdd 220 and 66 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 286\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 286"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 * 58",
        "answer": "Multiply 92 and 58 step by step:\nMultiplying 92 by the 8 in the ones place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n9 * 8 + 1 = 73 (carry 7, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 92 by the 8 in the ones place yields 736\n\nMultiplying 92 by the 5 in the tens place\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 92 by the 5 in the tens place yields 4600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 736 + 4600:\n\nAdd 4600 and 736 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5336\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5336"
    },
    {
        "question": "19 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 19 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 19 by the 2 in the ones place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n1 * 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 19 by the 2 in the ones place yields 38\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 38:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "52 * 20",
        "answer": "Multiply 52 and 20 step by step:\nMultiplying 52 by the 0 in the ones place\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 52 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 52 by the 2 in the tens place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 52 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1040\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 1040:\n\nAdd 1040 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1040\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1040"
    },
    {
        "question": "198 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 198 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 198 by the 9 in the ones place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n9 * 9 + 7 = 88 (carry 8, remainder 8)\n1 * 9 + 8 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 198 by the 9 in the ones place yields 1782\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1782:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "371 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 371 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 371 by the 8 in the ones place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 8 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n3 * 8 + 5 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 371 by the 8 in the ones place yields 2968\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2968:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 * 32",
        "answer": "Multiply 86 and 32 step by step:\nMultiplying 86 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 86 by the 2 in the ones place yields 172\n\nMultiplying 86 by the 3 in the tens place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 86 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2580\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 172 + 2580:\n\nAdd 2580 and 172 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2752\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2752"
    },
    {
        "question": "286 * 40",
        "answer": "Multiply 286 and 40 step by step:\nMultiplying 286 by the 0 in the ones place\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 286 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 286 by the 4 in the tens place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n8 * 4 + 2 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\n2 * 4 + 3 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 286 by the 4 in the tens place yields 11440\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 11440:\n\nAdd 11440 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 11440\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 11440"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 67 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 67 by the 8 in the ones place\n7 * 8 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n6 * 8 + 5 = 53 (carry 5, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 67 by the 8 in the ones place yields 536\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 536:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 * 13",
        "answer": "Multiply 22 and 13 step by step:\nMultiplying 22 by the 3 in the ones place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 22 by the 3 in the ones place yields 66\n\nMultiplying 22 by the 1 in the tens place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 22 by the 1 in the tens place yields 220\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 66 + 220:\n\nAdd 220 and 66 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 286\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 286"
    },
    {
        "question": "147 * 10",
        "answer": "Multiply 147 and 10 step by step:\nMultiplying 147 by the 0 in the ones place\n7 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n1 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 147 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 147 by the 1 in the tens place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 147 by the 1 in the tens place yields 1470\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 1470:\n\nAdd 1470 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1470\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1470"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 * 18",
        "answer": "Multiply 89 and 18 step by step:\nMultiplying 89 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n8 * 8 + 7 = 71 (carry 7, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 89 by the 8 in the ones place yields 712\n\nMultiplying 89 by the 1 in the tens place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 89 by the 1 in the tens place yields 890\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 712 + 890:\n\nAdd 890 and 712 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1602\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1602"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 73 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 73 by the 1 in the ones place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 73 by the 1 in the ones place yields 73\n\nMultiplying 73 by the 1 in the tens place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 73 by the 1 in the tens place yields 730\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 73 + 730:\n\nAdd 730 and 73 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 803\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 803"
    },
    {
        "question": "527 * 39",
        "answer": "Multiply 527 and 39 step by step:\nMultiplying 527 by the 9 in the ones place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n2 * 9 + 6 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 9 + 2 = 47 (carry 4, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 527 by the 9 in the ones place yields 4743\n\nMultiplying 527 by the 3 in the tens place\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n2 * 3 + 2 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 527 by the 3 in the tens place yields 15810\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4743 + 15810:\n\nAdd 15810 and 4743 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 20553\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 20553"
    },
    {
        "question": "42 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 42 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 42 by the 1 in the ones place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 42 by the 1 in the ones place yields 42\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 42:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "585 * 32",
        "answer": "Multiply 585 and 32 step by step:\nMultiplying 585 by the 2 in the ones place\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 585 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1170\n\nMultiplying 585 by the 3 in the tens place\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n5 * 3 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 585 by the 3 in the tens place yields 17550\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1170 + 17550:\n\nAdd 17550 and 1170 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 18720\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 18720"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 * 13",
        "answer": "Multiply 38 and 13 step by step:\nMultiplying 38 by the 3 in the ones place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n3 * 3 + 2 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 38 by the 3 in the ones place yields 114\n\nMultiplying 38 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 38 by the 1 in the tens place yields 380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 114 + 380:\n\nAdd 380 and 114 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 494\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 494"
    },
    {
        "question": "401 * 168",
        "answer": "Multiply 401 and 168 step by step:\nMultiplying 401 by the 8 in the ones place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 8 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 401 by the 8 in the ones place yields 3208\n\nMultiplying 401 by the 6 in the tens place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n0 * 6 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 6 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 401 by the 6 in the tens place yields 24060\n\nMultiplying 401 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 401 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 40100\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3208 + 24060 + 40100:\n\nAdd 24060 and 3208 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 27268\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 27268 + 40100\nAdd 40100 and 27268 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 67368\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 67368"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 * 37",
        "answer": "Multiply 89 and 37 step by step:\nMultiplying 89 by the 7 in the ones place\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n8 * 7 + 6 = 62 (carry 6, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 89 by the 7 in the ones place yields 623\n\nMultiplying 89 by the 3 in the tens place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n8 * 3 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 89 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2670\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 623 + 2670:\n\nAdd 2670 and 623 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3293\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3293"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 78 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 78 by the 3 in the ones place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 78 by the 3 in the ones place yields 234\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 234:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 91 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place yields 273\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 273:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "989 * 498",
        "answer": "Multiply 989 and 498 step by step:\nMultiplying 989 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n8 * 8 + 7 = 71 (carry 7, remainder 1)\n9 * 8 + 7 = 79 (carry 7, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 989 by the 8 in the ones place yields 7912\n\nMultiplying 989 by the 9 in the tens place\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\n8 * 9 + 8 = 80 (carry 8, remainder 0)\n9 * 9 + 8 = 89 (carry 8, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 989 by the 9 in the tens place yields 89010\n\nMultiplying 989 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n8 * 4 + 3 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n9 * 4 + 3 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 989 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 395600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 7912 + 89010 + 395600:\n\nAdd 89010 and 7912 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 96922\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 96922 + 395600\nAdd 395600 and 96922 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 6 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 9 + 1 = 19 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 4 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 492522\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 492522"
    },
    {
        "question": "794 * 423",
        "answer": "Multiply 794 and 423 step by step:\nMultiplying 794 by the 3 in the ones place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n9 * 3 + 1 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 794 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2382\n\nMultiplying 794 by the 2 in the tens place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 794 by the 2 in the tens place yields 15880\n\nMultiplying 794 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n9 * 4 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\n7 * 4 + 3 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 794 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 317600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2382 + 15880 + 317600:\n\nAdd 15880 and 2382 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 18262\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 18262 + 317600\nAdd 317600 and 18262 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 1 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 3 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 335862\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 335862"
    },
    {
        "question": "307 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 307 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 307 by the 2 in the ones place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n0 * 2 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 307 by the 2 in the ones place yields 614\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 614:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "24 * 17",
        "answer": "Multiply 24 and 17 step by step:\nMultiplying 24 by the 7 in the ones place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n2 * 7 + 2 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 24 by the 7 in the ones place yields 168\n\nMultiplying 24 by the 1 in the tens place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 24 by the 1 in the tens place yields 240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 168 + 240:\n\nAdd 240 and 168 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 408\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 408"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 28 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 28 by the 4 in the ones place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n2 * 4 + 3 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 28 by the 4 in the ones place yields 112\n\nMultiplying 28 by the 2 in the tens place\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n2 * 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 28 by the 2 in the tens place yields 560\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 112 + 560:\n\nAdd 560 and 112 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 672\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 672"
    },
    {
        "question": "668 * 86",
        "answer": "Multiply 668 and 86 step by step:\nMultiplying 668 by the 6 in the ones place\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n6 * 6 + 4 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n6 * 6 + 4 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 668 by the 6 in the ones place yields 4008\n\nMultiplying 668 by the 8 in the tens place\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\n6 * 8 + 6 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n6 * 8 + 5 = 53 (carry 5, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 668 by the 8 in the tens place yields 53440\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4008 + 53440:\n\nAdd 53440 and 4008 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 57448\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 57448"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 * 25",
        "answer": "Multiply 57 and 25 step by step:\nMultiplying 57 by the 5 in the ones place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 3 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 57 by the 5 in the ones place yields 285\n\nMultiplying 57 by the 2 in the tens place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 57 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1140\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 285 + 1140:\n\nAdd 1140 and 285 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1425\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1425"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 57 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the ones place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the ones place yields 57\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 57:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 67 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 67 by the 8 in the ones place\n7 * 8 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n6 * 8 + 5 = 53 (carry 5, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 67 by the 8 in the ones place yields 536\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 536:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 * 32",
        "answer": "Multiply 69 and 32 step by step:\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the ones place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the ones place yields 138\n\nMultiplying 69 by the 3 in the tens place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n6 * 3 + 2 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 69 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2070\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 138 + 2070:\n\nAdd 2070 and 138 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 1 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2208\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2208"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 * 92",
        "answer": "Multiply 93 and 92 step by step:\nMultiplying 93 by the 2 in the ones place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 93 by the 2 in the ones place yields 186\n\nMultiplying 93 by the 9 in the tens place\n3 * 9 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n9 * 9 + 2 = 83 (carry 8, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 93 by the 9 in the tens place yields 8370\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 186 + 8370:\n\nAdd 8370 and 186 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8556\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8556"
    },
    {
        "question": "845 * 63",
        "answer": "Multiply 845 and 63 step by step:\nMultiplying 845 by the 3 in the ones place\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n4 * 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 845 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2535\n\nMultiplying 845 by the 6 in the tens place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n4 * 6 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n8 * 6 + 2 = 50 (carry 5, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 845 by the 6 in the tens place yields 50700\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2535 + 50700:\n\nAdd 50700 and 2535 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 53235\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 53235"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 47 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 47 by the 3 in the ones place\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n4 * 3 + 2 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 47 by the 3 in the ones place yields 141\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 141:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 22 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 22 by the 8 in the ones place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n2 * 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 22 by the 8 in the ones place yields 176\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 176:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "162 * 46",
        "answer": "Multiply 162 and 46 step by step:\nMultiplying 162 by the 6 in the ones place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n6 * 6 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\n1 * 6 + 3 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 162 by the 6 in the ones place yields 972\n\nMultiplying 162 by the 4 in the tens place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n1 * 4 + 2 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 162 by the 4 in the tens place yields 6480\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 972 + 6480:\n\nAdd 6480 and 972 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 9 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7452\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7452"
    },
    {
        "question": "43 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 43 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 43 by the 7 in the ones place\n3 * 7 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n4 * 7 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 43 by the 7 in the ones place yields 301\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 301:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "47 * 37",
        "answer": "Multiply 47 and 37 step by step:\nMultiplying 47 by the 7 in the ones place\n7 * 7 + 0 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\n4 * 7 + 4 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 47 by the 7 in the ones place yields 329\n\nMultiplying 47 by the 3 in the tens place\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n4 * 3 + 2 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 47 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1410\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 329 + 1410:\n\nAdd 1410 and 329 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 2 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1739\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1739"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 * 44",
        "answer": "Multiply 81 and 44 step by step:\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the ones place yields 324\n\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the tens place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 324 + 3240:\n\nAdd 3240 and 324 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3564\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3564"
    },
    {
        "question": "43 * 42",
        "answer": "Multiply 43 and 42 step by step:\nMultiplying 43 by the 2 in the ones place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 43 by the 2 in the ones place yields 86\n\nMultiplying 43 by the 4 in the tens place\n3 * 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n4 * 4 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 43 by the 4 in the tens place yields 1720\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 86 + 1720:\n\nAdd 1720 and 86 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1806\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1806"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 85 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 85 by the 9 in the ones place\n5 * 9 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n8 * 9 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 85 by the 9 in the ones place yields 765\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 765:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "23 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 23 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 23 by the 1 in the ones place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 23 by the 1 in the ones place yields 23\n\nMultiplying 23 by the 1 in the tens place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 23 by the 1 in the tens place yields 230\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 23 + 230:\n\nAdd 230 and 23 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 253\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 253"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 66 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 66 by the 1 in the ones place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 66 by the 1 in the ones place yields 66\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 66:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 94 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 94 by the 1 in the ones place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 94 by the 1 in the ones place yields 94\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 94:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "806 * 23",
        "answer": "Multiply 806 and 23 step by step:\nMultiplying 806 by the 3 in the ones place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n0 * 3 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 806 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2418\n\nMultiplying 806 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n0 * 2 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 806 by the 2 in the tens place yields 16120\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2418 + 16120:\n\nAdd 16120 and 2418 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 18538\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 18538"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 * 17",
        "answer": "Multiply 28 and 17 step by step:\nMultiplying 28 by the 7 in the ones place\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n2 * 7 + 5 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 28 by the 7 in the ones place yields 196\n\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the tens place yields 280\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 196 + 280:\n\nAdd 280 and 196 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 476\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 476"
    },
    {
        "question": "242 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 242 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 242 by the 8 in the ones place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n4 * 8 + 1 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\n2 * 8 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 242 by the 8 in the ones place yields 1936\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1936:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "31 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 31 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 31 by the 6 in the ones place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n3 * 6 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 31 by the 6 in the ones place yields 186\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 186:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 51 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 51 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 51 by the 5 in the ones place yields 255\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 255:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "265 * 97",
        "answer": "Multiply 265 and 97 step by step:\nMultiplying 265 by the 7 in the ones place\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n6 * 7 + 3 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n2 * 7 + 4 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 265 by the 7 in the ones place yields 1855\n\nMultiplying 265 by the 9 in the tens place\n5 * 9 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n6 * 9 + 4 = 58 (carry 5, remainder 8)\n2 * 9 + 5 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 265 by the 9 in the tens place yields 23850\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1855 + 23850:\n\nAdd 23850 and 1855 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 8 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 25705\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 25705"
    },
    {
        "question": "192 * 83",
        "answer": "Multiply 192 and 83 step by step:\nMultiplying 192 by the 3 in the ones place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n1 * 3 + 2 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 192 by the 3 in the ones place yields 576\n\nMultiplying 192 by the 8 in the tens place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n9 * 8 + 1 = 73 (carry 7, remainder 3)\n1 * 8 + 7 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 192 by the 8 in the tens place yields 15360\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 576 + 15360:\n\nAdd 15360 and 576 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 5 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 15936\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 15936"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 67 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the ones place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n6 * 4 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the ones place yields 268\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 268:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 * 53",
        "answer": "Multiply 76 and 53 step by step:\nMultiplying 76 by the 3 in the ones place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n7 * 3 + 1 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 76 by the 3 in the ones place yields 228\n\nMultiplying 76 by the 5 in the tens place\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n7 * 5 + 3 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 76 by the 5 in the tens place yields 3800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 228 + 3800:\n\nAdd 3800 and 228 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4028\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4028"
    },
    {
        "question": "439 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 439 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 439 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n3 * 5 + 4 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\n4 * 5 + 1 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 439 by the 5 in the ones place yields 2195\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2195:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 * 17",
        "answer": "Multiply 56 and 17 step by step:\nMultiplying 56 by the 7 in the ones place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n5 * 7 + 4 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 56 by the 7 in the ones place yields 392\n\nMultiplying 56 by the 1 in the tens place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 56 by the 1 in the tens place yields 560\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 392 + 560:\n\nAdd 560 and 392 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 952\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 952"
    },
    {
        "question": "796 * 770",
        "answer": "Multiply 796 and 770 step by step:\nMultiplying 796 by the 0 in the ones place\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 796 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 796 by the 7 in the tens place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n9 * 7 + 4 = 67 (carry 6, remainder 7)\n7 * 7 + 6 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 796 by the 7 in the tens place yields 55720\n\nMultiplying 796 by the 7 in the hundreds place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n9 * 7 + 4 = 67 (carry 6, remainder 7)\n7 * 7 + 6 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 796 by the 7 in the hundreds place yields 557200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 55720 + 557200:\n\nAdd 55720 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 55720\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 55720 + 557200\nAdd 557200 and 55720 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 5 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 6 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 612920\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 612920"
    },
    {
        "question": "293 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 293 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 293 by the 8 in the ones place\n3 * 8 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n9 * 8 + 2 = 74 (carry 7, remainder 4)\n2 * 8 + 7 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 293 by the 8 in the ones place yields 2344\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2344:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 38 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 38 by the 7 in the ones place\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n3 * 7 + 5 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 38 by the 7 in the ones place yields 266\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 266:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 * 88",
        "answer": "Multiply 96 and 88 step by step:\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the ones place\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n9 * 8 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the ones place yields 768\n\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the tens place\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n9 * 8 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7680\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 768 + 7680:\n\nAdd 7680 and 768 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 7 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8448\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8448"
    },
    {
        "question": "27 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 27 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 27 by the 1 in the ones place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 27 by the 1 in the ones place yields 27\n\nMultiplying 27 by the 1 in the tens place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 27 by the 1 in the tens place yields 270\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 27 + 270:\n\nAdd 270 and 27 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 297\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 297"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 88 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 88 by the 1 in the ones place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 88 by the 1 in the ones place yields 88\n\nMultiplying 88 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 88 by the 1 in the tens place yields 880\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 88 + 880:\n\nAdd 880 and 88 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 968\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 968"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 * 30",
        "answer": "Multiply 92 and 30 step by step:\nMultiplying 92 by the 0 in the ones place\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 92 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 92 by the 3 in the tens place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 92 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2760\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 2760:\n\nAdd 2760 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2760\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2760"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 * 34",
        "answer": "Multiply 67 and 34 step by step:\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the ones place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n6 * 4 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the ones place yields 268\n\nMultiplying 67 by the 3 in the tens place\n7 * 3 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n6 * 3 + 2 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 67 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2010\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 268 + 2010:\n\nAdd 2010 and 268 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2278\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2278"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 * 54",
        "answer": "Multiply 83 and 54 step by step:\nMultiplying 83 by the 4 in the ones place\n3 * 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n8 * 4 + 1 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 83 by the 4 in the ones place yields 332\n\nMultiplying 83 by the 5 in the tens place\n3 * 5 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 1 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 83 by the 5 in the tens place yields 4150\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 332 + 4150:\n\nAdd 4150 and 332 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4482\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4482"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 * 14",
        "answer": "Multiply 69 and 14 step by step:\nMultiplying 69 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n6 * 4 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 69 by the 4 in the ones place yields 276\n\nMultiplying 69 by the 1 in the tens place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 69 by the 1 in the tens place yields 690\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 276 + 690:\n\nAdd 690 and 276 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 966\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 966"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 * 16",
        "answer": "Multiply 56 and 16 step by step:\nMultiplying 56 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n5 * 6 + 3 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 56 by the 6 in the ones place yields 336\n\nMultiplying 56 by the 1 in the tens place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 56 by the 1 in the tens place yields 560\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 336 + 560:\n\nAdd 560 and 336 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 896\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 896"
    },
    {
        "question": "494 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 494 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 494 by the 4 in the ones place\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n9 * 4 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 494 by the 4 in the ones place yields 1976\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1976:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "474 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 474 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 474 by the 8 in the ones place\n4 * 8 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n7 * 8 + 3 = 59 (carry 5, remainder 9)\n4 * 8 + 5 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 474 by the 8 in the ones place yields 3792\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3792:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "55 * 45",
        "answer": "Multiply 55 and 45 step by step:\nMultiplying 55 by the 5 in the ones place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 2 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 55 by the 5 in the ones place yields 275\n\nMultiplying 55 by the 4 in the tens place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 55 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 275 + 2200:\n\nAdd 2200 and 275 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2475\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2475"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 * 43",
        "answer": "Multiply 58 and 43 step by step:\nMultiplying 58 by the 3 in the ones place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 3 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 58 by the 3 in the ones place yields 174\n\nMultiplying 58 by the 4 in the tens place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n5 * 4 + 3 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 58 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2320\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 174 + 2320:\n\nAdd 2320 and 174 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2494\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2494"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 * 44",
        "answer": "Multiply 81 and 44 step by step:\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the ones place yields 324\n\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the tens place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 324 + 3240:\n\nAdd 3240 and 324 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3564\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3564"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 * 89",
        "answer": "Multiply 90 and 89 step by step:\nMultiplying 90 by the 9 in the ones place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 90 by the 9 in the ones place yields 810\n\nMultiplying 90 by the 8 in the tens place\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 90 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 810 + 7200:\n\nAdd 7200 and 810 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8010\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8010"
    },
    {
        "question": "901 * 165",
        "answer": "Multiply 901 and 165 step by step:\nMultiplying 901 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 901 by the 5 in the ones place yields 4505\n\nMultiplying 901 by the 6 in the tens place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n0 * 6 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 901 by the 6 in the tens place yields 54060\n\nMultiplying 901 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 901 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 90100\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4505 + 54060 + 90100:\n\nAdd 54060 and 4505 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 58565\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 58565 + 90100\nAdd 90100 and 58565 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 148665\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 148665"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 60 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 60 by the 3 in the ones place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 60 by the 3 in the ones place yields 180\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 180:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 * 10",
        "answer": "Multiply 37 and 10 step by step:\nMultiplying 37 by the 0 in the ones place\n7 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 37 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 37 by the 1 in the tens place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 37 by the 1 in the tens place yields 370\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 370:\n\nAdd 370 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 370\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 370"
    },
    {
        "question": "570 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 570 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 570 by the 6 in the ones place\n0 * 6 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n5 * 6 + 4 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 570 by the 6 in the ones place yields 3420\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3420:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 28 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the ones place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the ones place yields 28\n\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the tens place yields 280\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 28 + 280:\n\nAdd 280 and 28 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 308\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 308"
    },
    {
        "question": "622 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 622 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 622 by the 1 in the ones place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 622 by the 1 in the ones place yields 622\n\nMultiplying 622 by the 1 in the tens place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 622 by the 1 in the tens place yields 6220\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 622 + 6220:\n\nAdd 6220 and 622 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6842\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6842"
    },
    {
        "question": "299 * 190",
        "answer": "Multiply 299 and 190 step by step:\nMultiplying 299 by the 0 in the ones place\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 299 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 299 by the 9 in the tens place\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\n9 * 9 + 8 = 89 (carry 8, remainder 9)\n2 * 9 + 8 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 299 by the 9 in the tens place yields 26910\n\nMultiplying 299 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 299 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 29900\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 26910 + 29900:\n\nAdd 26910 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 1 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 26910\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 26910 + 29900\nAdd 29900 and 26910 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 56810\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 56810"
    },
    {
        "question": "117 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 117 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 117 by the 2 in the ones place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n1 * 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 117 by the 2 in the ones place yields 234\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 234:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 10 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 10 by the 4 in the ones place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 10 by the 4 in the ones place yields 40\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 40:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 98 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 98 by the 7 in the ones place\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n9 * 7 + 5 = 68 (carry 6, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 98 by the 7 in the ones place yields 686\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 686:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 95 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 95 by the 4 in the ones place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n9 * 4 + 2 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 95 by the 4 in the ones place yields 380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 380:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 * 46",
        "answer": "Multiply 99 and 46 step by step:\nMultiplying 99 by the 6 in the ones place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n9 * 6 + 5 = 59 (carry 5, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 99 by the 6 in the ones place yields 594\n\nMultiplying 99 by the 4 in the tens place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n9 * 4 + 3 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 99 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3960\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 594 + 3960:\n\nAdd 3960 and 594 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 9 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4554\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4554"
    },
    {
        "question": "926 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 926 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 926 by the 5 in the ones place\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n2 * 5 + 3 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n9 * 5 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 926 by the 5 in the ones place yields 4630\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4630:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "949 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 949 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 949 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n4 * 8 + 7 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\n9 * 8 + 3 = 75 (carry 7, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 949 by the 8 in the ones place yields 7592\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 7592:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "82 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 82 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 82 by the 2 in the ones place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 82 by the 2 in the ones place yields 164\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 164:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 * 87",
        "answer": "Multiply 96 and 87 step by step:\nMultiplying 96 by the 7 in the ones place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n9 * 7 + 4 = 67 (carry 6, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 96 by the 7 in the ones place yields 672\n\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the tens place\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n9 * 8 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7680\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 672 + 7680:\n\nAdd 7680 and 672 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8352\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8352"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 * 58",
        "answer": "Multiply 79 and 58 step by step:\nMultiplying 79 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n7 * 8 + 7 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 79 by the 8 in the ones place yields 632\n\nMultiplying 79 by the 5 in the tens place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n7 * 5 + 4 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 79 by the 5 in the tens place yields 3950\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 632 + 3950:\n\nAdd 3950 and 632 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 6 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4582\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4582"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 * 59",
        "answer": "Multiply 67 and 59 step by step:\nMultiplying 67 by the 9 in the ones place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n6 * 9 + 6 = 60 (carry 6, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 67 by the 9 in the ones place yields 603\n\nMultiplying 67 by the 5 in the tens place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n6 * 5 + 3 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 67 by the 5 in the tens place yields 3350\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 603 + 3350:\n\nAdd 3350 and 603 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3953\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3953"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 * 16",
        "answer": "Multiply 57 and 16 step by step:\nMultiplying 57 by the 6 in the ones place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n5 * 6 + 4 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 57 by the 6 in the ones place yields 342\n\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the tens place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the tens place yields 570\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 342 + 570:\n\nAdd 570 and 342 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 912\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 912"
    },
    {
        "question": "796 * 31",
        "answer": "Multiply 796 and 31 step by step:\nMultiplying 796 by the 1 in the ones place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 796 by the 1 in the ones place yields 796\n\nMultiplying 796 by the 3 in the tens place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n9 * 3 + 1 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 796 by the 3 in the tens place yields 23880\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 796 + 23880:\n\nAdd 23880 and 796 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 24676\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 24676"
    },
    {
        "question": "309 * 62",
        "answer": "Multiply 309 and 62 step by step:\nMultiplying 309 by the 2 in the ones place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n0 * 2 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 309 by the 2 in the ones place yields 618\n\nMultiplying 309 by the 6 in the tens place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n0 * 6 + 5 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n3 * 6 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 309 by the 6 in the tens place yields 18540\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 618 + 18540:\n\nAdd 18540 and 618 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 19158\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 19158"
    },
    {
        "question": "585 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 585 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 585 by the 9 in the ones place\n5 * 9 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n8 * 9 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\n5 * 9 + 7 = 52 (carry 5, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 585 by the 9 in the ones place yields 5265\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5265:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "46 * 31",
        "answer": "Multiply 46 and 31 step by step:\nMultiplying 46 by the 1 in the ones place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 46 by the 1 in the ones place yields 46\n\nMultiplying 46 by the 3 in the tens place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n4 * 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 46 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 46 + 1380:\n\nAdd 1380 and 46 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1426\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1426"
    },
    {
        "question": "647 * 555",
        "answer": "Multiply 647 and 555 step by step:\nMultiplying 647 by the 5 in the ones place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n4 * 5 + 3 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\n6 * 5 + 2 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 647 by the 5 in the ones place yields 3235\n\nMultiplying 647 by the 5 in the tens place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n4 * 5 + 3 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\n6 * 5 + 2 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 647 by the 5 in the tens place yields 32350\n\nMultiplying 647 by the 5 in the hundreds place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n4 * 5 + 3 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\n6 * 5 + 2 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 647 by the 5 in the hundreds place yields 323500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3235 + 32350 + 323500:\n\nAdd 32350 and 3235 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 35585\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 35585 + 323500\nAdd 323500 and 35585 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 5 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 3 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 359085\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 359085"
    },
    {
        "question": "57 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 57 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the ones place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the ones place yields 57\n\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the tens place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 57 by the 1 in the tens place yields 570\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 57 + 570:\n\nAdd 570 and 57 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 627\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 627"
    },
    {
        "question": "267 * 20",
        "answer": "Multiply 267 and 20 step by step:\nMultiplying 267 by the 0 in the ones place\n7 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 267 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 267 by the 2 in the tens place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n2 * 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 267 by the 2 in the tens place yields 5340\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 5340:\n\nAdd 5340 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5340\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5340"
    },
    {
        "question": "404 * 31",
        "answer": "Multiply 404 and 31 step by step:\nMultiplying 404 by the 1 in the ones place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 404 by the 1 in the ones place yields 404\n\nMultiplying 404 by the 3 in the tens place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n0 * 3 + 1 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 404 by the 3 in the tens place yields 12120\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 404 + 12120:\n\nAdd 12120 and 404 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 12524\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 12524"
    },
    {
        "question": "848 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 848 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 848 by the 4 in the ones place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\n8 * 4 + 1 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 848 by the 4 in the ones place yields 3392\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3392:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 51 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 51 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 51 by the 4 in the ones place yields 204\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 204:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "607 * 199",
        "answer": "Multiply 607 and 199 step by step:\nMultiplying 607 by the 9 in the ones place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n0 * 9 + 6 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 607 by the 9 in the ones place yields 5463\n\nMultiplying 607 by the 9 in the tens place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n0 * 9 + 6 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 607 by the 9 in the tens place yields 54630\n\nMultiplying 607 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 607 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 60700\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5463 + 54630 + 60700:\n\nAdd 54630 and 5463 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 5 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 60093\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 60093 + 60700\nAdd 60700 and 60093 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 120793\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 120793"
    },
    {
        "question": "86 * 12",
        "answer": "Multiply 86 and 12 step by step:\nMultiplying 86 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 86 by the 2 in the ones place yields 172\n\nMultiplying 86 by the 1 in the tens place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 86 by the 1 in the tens place yields 860\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 172 + 860:\n\nAdd 860 and 172 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 1 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1032\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1032"
    },
    {
        "question": "110 * 94",
        "answer": "Multiply 110 and 94 step by step:\nMultiplying 110 by the 4 in the ones place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 110 by the 4 in the ones place yields 440\n\nMultiplying 110 by the 9 in the tens place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 110 by the 9 in the tens place yields 9900\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 440 + 9900:\n\nAdd 9900 and 440 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 10340\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 10340"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 * 46",
        "answer": "Multiply 90 and 46 step by step:\nMultiplying 90 by the 6 in the ones place\n0 * 6 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 90 by the 6 in the ones place yields 540\n\nMultiplying 90 by the 4 in the tens place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 90 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 540 + 3600:\n\nAdd 3600 and 540 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4140\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4140"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 * 74",
        "answer": "Multiply 78 and 74 step by step:\nMultiplying 78 by the 4 in the ones place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n7 * 4 + 3 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 78 by the 4 in the ones place yields 312\n\nMultiplying 78 by the 7 in the tens place\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n7 * 7 + 5 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 78 by the 7 in the tens place yields 5460\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 312 + 5460:\n\nAdd 5460 and 312 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5772\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5772"
    },
    {
        "question": "32 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 32 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 32 by the 3 in the ones place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n3 * 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 32 by the 3 in the ones place yields 96\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 96:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "446 * 65",
        "answer": "Multiply 446 and 65 step by step:\nMultiplying 446 by the 5 in the ones place\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n4 * 5 + 3 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\n4 * 5 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 446 by the 5 in the ones place yields 2230\n\nMultiplying 446 by the 6 in the tens place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n4 * 6 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n4 * 6 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 446 by the 6 in the tens place yields 26760\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2230 + 26760:\n\nAdd 26760 and 2230 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 28990\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 28990"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 50 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 50 by the 7 in the ones place\n0 * 7 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 50 by the 7 in the ones place yields 350\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 350:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 28 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 28 by the 6 in the ones place\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n2 * 6 + 4 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 28 by the 6 in the ones place yields 168\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 168:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 * 80",
        "answer": "Multiply 80 and 80 step by step:\nMultiplying 80 by the 0 in the ones place\n0 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 80 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 80 by the 8 in the tens place\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 80 by the 8 in the tens place yields 6400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 6400:\n\nAdd 6400 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6400\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6400"
    },
    {
        "question": "67 * 45",
        "answer": "Multiply 67 and 45 step by step:\nMultiplying 67 by the 5 in the ones place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n6 * 5 + 3 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 67 by the 5 in the ones place yields 335\n\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the tens place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n6 * 4 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 67 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2680\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 335 + 2680:\n\nAdd 2680 and 335 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3015\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3015"
    },
    {
        "question": "35 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 35 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 35 by the 7 in the ones place\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n3 * 7 + 3 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 35 by the 7 in the ones place yields 245\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 245:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "380 * 26",
        "answer": "Multiply 380 and 26 step by step:\nMultiplying 380 by the 6 in the ones place\n0 * 6 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n3 * 6 + 4 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 380 by the 6 in the ones place yields 2280\n\nMultiplying 380 by the 2 in the tens place\n0 * 2 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n3 * 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 380 by the 2 in the tens place yields 7600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2280 + 7600:\n\nAdd 7600 and 2280 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9880\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 9880"
    },
    {
        "question": "33 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 33 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 33 by the 9 in the ones place\n3 * 9 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n3 * 9 + 2 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 33 by the 9 in the ones place yields 297\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 297:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 12 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 12 by the 7 in the ones place\n2 * 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n1 * 7 + 1 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 12 by the 7 in the ones place yields 84\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 84:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 17 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 17 by the 1 in the ones place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 17 by the 1 in the ones place yields 17\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 17:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 * 22",
        "answer": "Multiply 87 and 22 step by step:\nMultiplying 87 by the 2 in the ones place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 87 by the 2 in the ones place yields 174\n\nMultiplying 87 by the 2 in the tens place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 87 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1740\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 174 + 1740:\n\nAdd 1740 and 174 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1914\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1914"
    },
    {
        "question": "820 * 485",
        "answer": "Multiply 820 and 485 step by step:\nMultiplying 820 by the 5 in the ones place\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n8 * 5 + 1 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 820 by the 5 in the ones place yields 4100\n\nMultiplying 820 by the 8 in the tens place\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 8 + 1 = 65 (carry 6, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 820 by the 8 in the tens place yields 65600\n\nMultiplying 820 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 820 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 328000\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4100 + 65600 + 328000:\n\nAdd 65600 and 4100 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 69700\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 69700 + 328000\nAdd 328000 and 69700 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 6 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 3 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 397700\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 397700"
    },
    {
        "question": "34 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 34 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 34 by the 9 in the ones place\n4 * 9 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n3 * 9 + 3 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 34 by the 9 in the ones place yields 306\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 306:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "994 * 507",
        "answer": "Multiply 994 and 507 step by step:\nMultiplying 994 by the 7 in the ones place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n9 * 7 + 2 = 65 (carry 6, remainder 5)\n9 * 7 + 6 = 69 (carry 6, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 994 by the 7 in the ones place yields 6958\n\nMultiplying 994 by the 0 in the tens place\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 994 by the 0 in the tens place yields 0000\n\nMultiplying 994 by the 5 in the hundreds place\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 2 = 47 (carry 4, remainder 7)\n9 * 5 + 4 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 994 by the 5 in the hundreds place yields 497000\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 6958 + 0000 + 497000:\n\nAdd 6958 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6958\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 6958 + 497000\nAdd 497000 and 6958 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 0 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 5 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 503958\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 503958"
    },
    {
        "question": "861 * 85",
        "answer": "Multiply 861 and 85 step by step:\nMultiplying 861 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n8 * 5 + 3 = 43 (carry 4, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 861 by the 5 in the ones place yields 4305\n\nMultiplying 861 by the 8 in the tens place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n8 * 8 + 4 = 68 (carry 6, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 861 by the 8 in the tens place yields 68880\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4305 + 68880:\n\nAdd 68880 and 4305 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 73185\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 73185"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 79 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 79 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n7 * 4 + 3 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 79 by the 4 in the ones place yields 316\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 316:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "24 * 15",
        "answer": "Multiply 24 and 15 step by step:\nMultiplying 24 by the 5 in the ones place\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n2 * 5 + 2 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 24 by the 5 in the ones place yields 120\n\nMultiplying 24 by the 1 in the tens place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 24 by the 1 in the tens place yields 240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 120 + 240:\n\nAdd 240 and 120 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 360\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 360"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 * 55",
        "answer": "Multiply 85 and 55 step by step:\nMultiplying 85 by the 5 in the ones place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 2 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 85 by the 5 in the ones place yields 425\n\nMultiplying 85 by the 5 in the tens place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 2 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 85 by the 5 in the tens place yields 4250\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 425 + 4250:\n\nAdd 4250 and 425 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4675\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4675"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 * 14",
        "answer": "Multiply 59 and 14 step by step:\nMultiplying 59 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n5 * 4 + 3 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 59 by the 4 in the ones place yields 236\n\nMultiplying 59 by the 1 in the tens place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 59 by the 1 in the tens place yields 590\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 236 + 590:\n\nAdd 590 and 236 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 826\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 826"
    },
    {
        "question": "48 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 48 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 48 by the 5 in the ones place\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n4 * 5 + 4 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 48 by the 5 in the ones place yields 240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 240:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 89 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 89 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 4 = 44 (carry 4, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 89 by the 5 in the ones place yields 445\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 445:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "699 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 699 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 699 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n9 * 5 + 4 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\n6 * 5 + 4 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 699 by the 5 in the ones place yields 3495\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3495:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "571 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 571 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 571 by the 7 in the ones place\n1 * 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n7 * 7 + 0 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\n5 * 7 + 4 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 571 by the 7 in the ones place yields 3997\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3997:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "339 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 339 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 339 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n3 * 8 + 7 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\n3 * 8 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 339 by the 8 in the ones place yields 2712\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2712:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "939 * 594",
        "answer": "Multiply 939 and 594 step by step:\nMultiplying 939 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n3 * 4 + 3 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n9 * 4 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 939 by the 4 in the ones place yields 3756\n\nMultiplying 939 by the 9 in the tens place\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\n3 * 9 + 8 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n9 * 9 + 3 = 84 (carry 8, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 939 by the 9 in the tens place yields 84510\n\nMultiplying 939 by the 5 in the hundreds place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n3 * 5 + 4 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\n9 * 5 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 939 by the 5 in the hundreds place yields 469500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3756 + 84510 + 469500:\n\nAdd 84510 and 3756 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 8 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 88266\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 88266 + 469500\nAdd 469500 and 88266 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 8 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 5 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 557766\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 557766"
    },
    {
        "question": "442 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 442 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 442 by the 2 in the ones place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 442 by the 2 in the ones place yields 884\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 884:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 * 13",
        "answer": "Multiply 45 and 13 step by step:\nMultiplying 45 by the 3 in the ones place\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n4 * 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 45 by the 3 in the ones place yields 135\n\nMultiplying 45 by the 1 in the tens place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 45 by the 1 in the tens place yields 450\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 135 + 450:\n\nAdd 450 and 135 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 585\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 585"
    },
    {
        "question": "845 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 845 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 845 by the 1 in the ones place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 845 by the 1 in the ones place yields 845\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 845:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 * 19",
        "answer": "Multiply 36 and 19 step by step:\nMultiplying 36 by the 9 in the ones place\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n3 * 9 + 5 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 36 by the 9 in the ones place yields 324\n\nMultiplying 36 by the 1 in the tens place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 36 by the 1 in the tens place yields 360\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 324 + 360:\n\nAdd 360 and 324 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 684\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 684"
    },
    {
        "question": "751 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 751 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 751 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n7 * 4 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 751 by the 4 in the ones place yields 3004\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3004:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "41 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 41 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 41 by the 9 in the ones place\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n4 * 9 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 41 by the 9 in the ones place yields 369\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 369:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "262 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 262 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 262 by the 1 in the ones place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 262 by the 1 in the ones place yields 262\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 262:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 * 33",
        "answer": "Multiply 83 and 33 step by step:\nMultiplying 83 by the 3 in the ones place\n3 * 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 83 by the 3 in the ones place yields 249\n\nMultiplying 83 by the 3 in the tens place\n3 * 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 83 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2490\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 249 + 2490:\n\nAdd 2490 and 249 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2739\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2739"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 36 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 36 by the 4 in the ones place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n3 * 4 + 2 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 36 by the 4 in the ones place yields 144\n\nMultiplying 36 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n3 * 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 36 by the 2 in the tens place yields 720\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 144 + 720:\n\nAdd 720 and 144 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 864\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 864"
    },
    {
        "question": "636 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 636 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 636 by the 3 in the ones place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n3 * 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n6 * 3 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 636 by the 3 in the ones place yields 1908\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1908:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "49 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 49 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 49 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 49 by the 4 in the ones place yields 196\n\nMultiplying 49 by the 2 in the tens place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n4 * 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 49 by the 2 in the tens place yields 980\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 196 + 980:\n\nAdd 980 and 196 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1176\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1176"
    },
    {
        "question": "77 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 77 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 77 by the 4 in the ones place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n7 * 4 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 77 by the 4 in the ones place yields 308\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 308:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "520 * 10",
        "answer": "Multiply 520 and 10 step by step:\nMultiplying 520 by the 0 in the ones place\n0 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 520 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 520 by the 1 in the tens place\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 520 by the 1 in the tens place yields 5200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 5200:\n\nAdd 5200 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5200\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5200"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 73 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 73 by the 4 in the ones place\n3 * 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 4 + 1 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 73 by the 4 in the ones place yields 292\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 292:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 15",
        "answer": "Multiply 18 and 15 step by step:\nMultiplying 18 by the 5 in the ones place\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n1 * 5 + 4 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 18 by the 5 in the ones place yields 90\n\nMultiplying 18 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 18 by the 1 in the tens place yields 180\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 90 + 180:\n\nAdd 180 and 90 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 270\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 270"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 * 26",
        "answer": "Multiply 99 and 26 step by step:\nMultiplying 99 by the 6 in the ones place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n9 * 6 + 5 = 59 (carry 5, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 99 by the 6 in the ones place yields 594\n\nMultiplying 99 by the 2 in the tens place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n9 * 2 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 99 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1980\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 594 + 1980:\n\nAdd 1980 and 594 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2574\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2574"
    },
    {
        "question": "22 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 22 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 22 by the 1 in the ones place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 22 by the 1 in the ones place yields 22\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 22:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "586 * 271",
        "answer": "Multiply 586 and 271 step by step:\nMultiplying 586 by the 1 in the ones place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 586 by the 1 in the ones place yields 586\n\nMultiplying 586 by the 7 in the tens place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n8 * 7 + 4 = 60 (carry 6, remainder 0)\n5 * 7 + 6 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 586 by the 7 in the tens place yields 41020\n\nMultiplying 586 by the 2 in the hundreds place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 586 by the 2 in the hundreds place yields 117200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 586 + 41020 + 117200:\n\nAdd 41020 and 586 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 5 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 41606\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 41606 + 117200\nAdd 117200 and 41606 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 1 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 158806\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 158806"
    },
    {
        "question": "741 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 741 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 741 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n7 * 4 + 1 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 741 by the 4 in the ones place yields 2964\n\nMultiplying 741 by the 2 in the tens place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 741 by the 2 in the tens place yields 14820\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2964 + 14820:\n\nAdd 14820 and 2964 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 17784\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 17784"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 * 21",
        "answer": "Multiply 72 and 21 step by step:\nMultiplying 72 by the 1 in the ones place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 72 by the 1 in the ones place yields 72\n\nMultiplying 72 by the 2 in the tens place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 72 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1440\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 72 + 1440:\n\nAdd 1440 and 72 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 5 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1512\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1512"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 69 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 69 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n6 * 4 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 69 by the 4 in the ones place yields 276\n\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the tens place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 276 + 1380:\n\nAdd 1380 and 276 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1656\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1656"
    },
    {
        "question": "478 * 409",
        "answer": "Multiply 478 and 409 step by step:\nMultiplying 478 by the 9 in the ones place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n7 * 9 + 7 = 70 (carry 7, remainder 0)\n4 * 9 + 7 = 43 (carry 4, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 478 by the 9 in the ones place yields 4302\n\nMultiplying 478 by the 0 in the tens place\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 478 by the 0 in the tens place yields 0000\n\nMultiplying 478 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n7 * 4 + 3 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\n4 * 4 + 3 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 478 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 191200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4302 + 0000 + 191200:\n\nAdd 4302 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 3 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4302\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 4302 + 191200\nAdd 191200 and 4302 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 4 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 9 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 1 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 195502\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 195502"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 * 72",
        "answer": "Multiply 72 and 72 step by step:\nMultiplying 72 by the 2 in the ones place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 72 by the 2 in the ones place yields 144\n\nMultiplying 72 by the 7 in the tens place\n2 * 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n7 * 7 + 1 = 50 (carry 5, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 72 by the 7 in the tens place yields 5040\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 144 + 5040:\n\nAdd 5040 and 144 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5184\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5184"
    },
    {
        "question": "395 * 18",
        "answer": "Multiply 395 and 18 step by step:\nMultiplying 395 by the 8 in the ones place\n5 * 8 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n9 * 8 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\n3 * 8 + 7 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 395 by the 8 in the ones place yields 3160\n\nMultiplying 395 by the 1 in the tens place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 395 by the 1 in the tens place yields 3950\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3160 + 3950:\n\nAdd 3950 and 3160 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7110\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7110"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 * 54",
        "answer": "Multiply 81 and 54 step by step:\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 81 by the 4 in the ones place yields 324\n\nMultiplying 81 by the 5 in the tens place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 81 by the 5 in the tens place yields 4050\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 324 + 4050:\n\nAdd 4050 and 324 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4374\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4374"
    },
    {
        "question": "666 * 30",
        "answer": "Multiply 666 and 30 step by step:\nMultiplying 666 by the 0 in the ones place\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 666 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 666 by the 3 in the tens place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 3 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\n6 * 3 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 666 by the 3 in the tens place yields 19980\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 19980:\n\nAdd 19980 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 9 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 0 + 0 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 19980\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 19980"
    },
    {
        "question": "39 * 12",
        "answer": "Multiply 39 and 12 step by step:\nMultiplying 39 by the 2 in the ones place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n3 * 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 39 by the 2 in the ones place yields 78\n\nMultiplying 39 by the 1 in the tens place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 39 by the 1 in the tens place yields 390\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 78 + 390:\n\nAdd 390 and 78 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 7 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 468\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 468"
    },
    {
        "question": "52 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 52 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 52 by the 9 in the ones place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n5 * 9 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 52 by the 9 in the ones place yields 468\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 468:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 * 15",
        "answer": "Multiply 98 and 15 step by step:\nMultiplying 98 by the 5 in the ones place\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 4 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 98 by the 5 in the ones place yields 490\n\nMultiplying 98 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 98 by the 1 in the tens place yields 980\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 490 + 980:\n\nAdd 980 and 490 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1470\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1470"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 * 56",
        "answer": "Multiply 85 and 56 step by step:\nMultiplying 85 by the 6 in the ones place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n8 * 6 + 3 = 51 (carry 5, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 85 by the 6 in the ones place yields 510\n\nMultiplying 85 by the 5 in the tens place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 2 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 85 by the 5 in the tens place yields 4250\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 510 + 4250:\n\nAdd 4250 and 510 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4760\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4760"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 * 38",
        "answer": "Multiply 81 and 38 step by step:\nMultiplying 81 by the 8 in the ones place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 81 by the 8 in the ones place yields 648\n\nMultiplying 81 by the 3 in the tens place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 81 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2430\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 648 + 2430:\n\nAdd 2430 and 648 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 4 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3078\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3078"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 * 83",
        "answer": "Multiply 84 and 83 step by step:\nMultiplying 84 by the 3 in the ones place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 84 by the 3 in the ones place yields 252\n\nMultiplying 84 by the 8 in the tens place\n4 * 8 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n8 * 8 + 3 = 67 (carry 6, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 84 by the 8 in the tens place yields 6720\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 252 + 6720:\n\nAdd 6720 and 252 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6972\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6972"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 * 74",
        "answer": "Multiply 80 and 74 step by step:\nMultiplying 80 by the 4 in the ones place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 80 by the 4 in the ones place yields 320\n\nMultiplying 80 by the 7 in the tens place\n0 * 7 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 80 by the 7 in the tens place yields 5600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 320 + 5600:\n\nAdd 5600 and 320 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5920\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5920"
    },
    {
        "question": "629 * 44",
        "answer": "Multiply 629 and 44 step by step:\nMultiplying 629 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n2 * 4 + 3 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\n6 * 4 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 629 by the 4 in the ones place yields 2516\n\nMultiplying 629 by the 4 in the tens place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n2 * 4 + 3 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\n6 * 4 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 629 by the 4 in the tens place yields 25160\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2516 + 25160:\n\nAdd 25160 and 2516 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 5 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 27676\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 27676"
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 12",
        "answer": "Multiply 16 and 12 step by step:\nMultiplying 16 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n1 * 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 16 by the 2 in the ones place yields 32\n\nMultiplying 16 by the 1 in the tens place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 16 by the 1 in the tens place yields 160\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 32 + 160:\n\nAdd 160 and 32 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 1 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 192\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 192"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 * 80",
        "answer": "Multiply 80 and 80 step by step:\nMultiplying 80 by the 0 in the ones place\n0 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 80 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 80 by the 8 in the tens place\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 80 by the 8 in the tens place yields 6400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 6400:\n\nAdd 6400 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 0 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6400\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6400"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 15 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 15 by the 8 in the ones place\n5 * 8 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n1 * 8 + 4 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 15 by the 8 in the ones place yields 120\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 120:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 * 26",
        "answer": "Multiply 87 and 26 step by step:\nMultiplying 87 by the 6 in the ones place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n8 * 6 + 4 = 52 (carry 5, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 87 by the 6 in the ones place yields 522\n\nMultiplying 87 by the 2 in the tens place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 87 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1740\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 522 + 1740:\n\nAdd 1740 and 522 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2262\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2262"
    },
    {
        "question": "350 * 83",
        "answer": "Multiply 350 and 83 step by step:\nMultiplying 350 by the 3 in the ones place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n3 * 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 350 by the 3 in the ones place yields 1050\n\nMultiplying 350 by the 8 in the tens place\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 8 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n3 * 8 + 4 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 350 by the 8 in the tens place yields 28000\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1050 + 28000:\n\nAdd 28000 and 1050 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 29050\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 29050"
    },
    {
        "question": "859 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 859 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 859 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 4 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\n8 * 5 + 2 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 859 by the 5 in the ones place yields 4295\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4295:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 * 73",
        "answer": "Multiply 74 and 73 step by step:\nMultiplying 74 by the 3 in the ones place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 3 + 1 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 74 by the 3 in the ones place yields 222\n\nMultiplying 74 by the 7 in the tens place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n7 * 7 + 2 = 51 (carry 5, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 74 by the 7 in the tens place yields 5180\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 222 + 5180:\n\nAdd 5180 and 222 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5402\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5402"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 * 80",
        "answer": "Multiply 93 and 80 step by step:\nMultiplying 93 by the 0 in the ones place\n3 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 93 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 93 by the 8 in the tens place\n3 * 8 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n9 * 8 + 2 = 74 (carry 7, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 93 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7440\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 7440:\n\nAdd 7440 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 4 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7440\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7440"
    },
    {
        "question": "454 * 30",
        "answer": "Multiply 454 and 30 step by step:\nMultiplying 454 by the 0 in the ones place\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 454 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 454 by the 3 in the tens place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n5 * 3 + 1 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n4 * 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 454 by the 3 in the tens place yields 13620\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 13620:\n\nAdd 13620 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 13620\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 13620"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 * 70",
        "answer": "Multiply 95 and 70 step by step:\nMultiplying 95 by the 0 in the ones place\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 95 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 95 by the 7 in the tens place\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n9 * 7 + 3 = 66 (carry 6, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 95 by the 7 in the tens place yields 6650\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 6650:\n\nAdd 6650 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6650\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6650"
    },
    {
        "question": "31 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 31 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 31 by the 2 in the ones place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 31 by the 2 in the ones place yields 62\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 62:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "171 * 14",
        "answer": "Multiply 171 and 14 step by step:\nMultiplying 171 by the 4 in the ones place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n1 * 4 + 2 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 171 by the 4 in the ones place yields 684\n\nMultiplying 171 by the 1 in the tens place\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 171 by the 1 in the tens place yields 1710\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 684 + 1710:\n\nAdd 1710 and 684 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2394\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2394"
    },
    {
        "question": "32 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 32 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 32 by the 3 in the ones place\n2 * 3 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n3 * 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 32 by the 3 in the ones place yields 96\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 96:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "30 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 30 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 30 by the 7 in the ones place\n0 * 7 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 7 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 30 by the 7 in the ones place yields 210\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 210:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "675 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 675 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 675 by the 1 in the ones place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 675 by the 1 in the ones place yields 675\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 675:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 * 54",
        "answer": "Multiply 68 and 54 step by step:\nMultiplying 68 by the 4 in the ones place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n6 * 4 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 68 by the 4 in the ones place yields 272\n\nMultiplying 68 by the 5 in the tens place\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n6 * 5 + 4 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 68 by the 5 in the tens place yields 3400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 272 + 3400:\n\nAdd 3400 and 272 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3672\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3672"
    },
    {
        "question": "452 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 452 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 452 by the 8 in the ones place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n5 * 8 + 1 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\n4 * 8 + 4 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 452 by the 8 in the ones place yields 3616\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3616:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "911 * 70",
        "answer": "Multiply 911 and 70 step by step:\nMultiplying 911 by the 0 in the ones place\n1 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n1 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 911 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 911 by the 7 in the tens place\n1 * 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n1 * 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 911 by the 7 in the tens place yields 63770\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 63770:\n\nAdd 63770 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 63770\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 63770"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 * 25",
        "answer": "Multiply 69 and 25 step by step:\nMultiplying 69 by the 5 in the ones place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n6 * 5 + 4 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 69 by the 5 in the ones place yields 345\n\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the tens place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 69 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 345 + 1380:\n\nAdd 1380 and 345 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1725\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1725"
    },
    {
        "question": "53 * 18",
        "answer": "Multiply 53 and 18 step by step:\nMultiplying 53 by the 8 in the ones place\n3 * 8 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 8 + 2 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 53 by the 8 in the ones place yields 424\n\nMultiplying 53 by the 1 in the tens place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 53 by the 1 in the tens place yields 530\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 424 + 530:\n\nAdd 530 and 424 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 2 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 954\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 954"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 * 69",
        "answer": "Multiply 71 and 69 step by step:\nMultiplying 71 by the 9 in the ones place\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 71 by the 9 in the ones place yields 639\n\nMultiplying 71 by the 6 in the tens place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 71 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4260\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 639 + 4260:\n\nAdd 4260 and 639 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4899\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4899"
    },
    {
        "question": "526 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 526 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 526 by the 5 in the ones place\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n2 * 5 + 3 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n5 * 5 + 1 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 526 by the 5 in the ones place yields 2630\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2630:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 15 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 15 by the 5 in the ones place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n1 * 5 + 2 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 15 by the 5 in the ones place yields 75\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 75:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "792 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 792 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 792 by the 5 in the ones place\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\n7 * 5 + 4 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 792 by the 5 in the ones place yields 3960\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3960:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 * 22",
        "answer": "Multiply 56 and 22 step by step:\nMultiplying 56 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 56 by the 2 in the ones place yields 112\n\nMultiplying 56 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 56 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1120\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 112 + 1120:\n\nAdd 1120 and 112 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1232\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1232"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 * 26",
        "answer": "Multiply 56 and 26 step by step:\nMultiplying 56 by the 6 in the ones place\n6 * 6 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n5 * 6 + 3 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 56 by the 6 in the ones place yields 336\n\nMultiplying 56 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 56 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1120\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 336 + 1120:\n\nAdd 1120 and 336 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 3 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1456\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1456"
    },
    {
        "question": "92 * 29",
        "answer": "Multiply 92 and 29 step by step:\nMultiplying 92 by the 9 in the ones place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n9 * 9 + 1 = 82 (carry 8, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 92 by the 9 in the ones place yields 828\n\nMultiplying 92 by the 2 in the tens place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 92 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1840\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 828 + 1840:\n\nAdd 1840 and 828 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2668\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2668"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 37 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 37 by the 4 in the ones place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n3 * 4 + 2 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 37 by the 4 in the ones place yields 148\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 148:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "399 * 353",
        "answer": "Multiply 399 and 353 step by step:\nMultiplying 399 by the 3 in the ones place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n9 * 3 + 2 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\n3 * 3 + 2 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 399 by the 3 in the ones place yields 1197\n\nMultiplying 399 by the 5 in the tens place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n9 * 5 + 4 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\n3 * 5 + 4 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 399 by the 5 in the tens place yields 19950\n\nMultiplying 399 by the 3 in the hundreds place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n9 * 3 + 2 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\n3 * 3 + 2 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 399 by the 3 in the hundreds place yields 119700\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1197 + 19950 + 119700:\n\nAdd 19950 and 1197 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 21147\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 21147 + 119700\nAdd 119700 and 21147 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 2 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 1 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 140847\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 140847"
    },
    {
        "question": "451 * 65",
        "answer": "Multiply 451 and 65 step by step:\nMultiplying 451 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n4 * 5 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 451 by the 5 in the ones place yields 2255\n\nMultiplying 451 by the 6 in the tens place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n4 * 6 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 451 by the 6 in the tens place yields 27060\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2255 + 27060:\n\nAdd 27060 and 2255 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 29315\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 29315"
    },
    {
        "question": "469 * 78",
        "answer": "Multiply 469 and 78 step by step:\nMultiplying 469 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n6 * 8 + 7 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\n4 * 8 + 5 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 469 by the 8 in the ones place yields 3752\n\nMultiplying 469 by the 7 in the tens place\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n6 * 7 + 6 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n4 * 7 + 4 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 469 by the 7 in the tens place yields 32830\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3752 + 32830:\n\nAdd 32830 and 3752 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 3 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 36582\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 36582"
    },
    {
        "question": "50 * 17",
        "answer": "Multiply 50 and 17 step by step:\nMultiplying 50 by the 7 in the ones place\n0 * 7 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 50 by the 7 in the ones place yields 350\n\nMultiplying 50 by the 1 in the tens place\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 50 by the 1 in the tens place yields 500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 350 + 500:\n\nAdd 500 and 350 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 850\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 850"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 * 65",
        "answer": "Multiply 70 and 65 step by step:\nMultiplying 70 by the 5 in the ones place\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 70 by the 5 in the ones place yields 350\n\nMultiplying 70 by the 6 in the tens place\n0 * 6 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 70 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 350 + 4200:\n\nAdd 4200 and 350 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4550\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4550"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 79 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 79 by the 3 in the ones place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n7 * 3 + 2 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 79 by the 3 in the ones place yields 237\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 237:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 51 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 51 by the 7 in the ones place\n1 * 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 51 by the 7 in the ones place yields 357\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 357:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "634 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 634 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 634 by the 5 in the ones place\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n3 * 5 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n6 * 5 + 1 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 634 by the 5 in the ones place yields 3170\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3170:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "761 * 383",
        "answer": "Multiply 761 and 383 step by step:\nMultiplying 761 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n7 * 3 + 1 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 761 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2283\n\nMultiplying 761 by the 8 in the tens place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n7 * 8 + 4 = 60 (carry 6, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 761 by the 8 in the tens place yields 60880\n\nMultiplying 761 by the 3 in the hundreds place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n7 * 3 + 1 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 761 by the 3 in the hundreds place yields 228300\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2283 + 60880 + 228300:\n\nAdd 60880 and 2283 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 63163\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 63163 + 228300\nAdd 228300 and 63163 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 6 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 2 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 291463\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 291463"
    },
    {
        "question": "841 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 841 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 841 by the 9 in the ones place\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n4 * 9 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n8 * 9 + 3 = 75 (carry 7, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 841 by the 9 in the ones place yields 7569\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 7569:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "37 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 37 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 37 by the 9 in the ones place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n3 * 9 + 6 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 37 by the 9 in the ones place yields 333\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 333:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "55 * 47",
        "answer": "Multiply 55 and 47 step by step:\nMultiplying 55 by the 7 in the ones place\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n5 * 7 + 3 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 55 by the 7 in the ones place yields 385\n\nMultiplying 55 by the 4 in the tens place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 55 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 385 + 2200:\n\nAdd 2200 and 385 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2585\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2585"
    },
    {
        "question": "473 * 174",
        "answer": "Multiply 473 and 174 step by step:\nMultiplying 473 by the 4 in the ones place\n3 * 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 4 + 1 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\n4 * 4 + 2 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 473 by the 4 in the ones place yields 1892\n\nMultiplying 473 by the 7 in the tens place\n3 * 7 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n7 * 7 + 2 = 51 (carry 5, remainder 1)\n4 * 7 + 5 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 473 by the 7 in the tens place yields 33110\n\nMultiplying 473 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 473 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 47300\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1892 + 33110 + 47300:\n\nAdd 33110 and 1892 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 8 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 35002\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 35002 + 47300\nAdd 47300 and 35002 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 3 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 82302\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 82302"
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 14 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 14 by the 1 in the ones place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 14 by the 1 in the ones place yields 14\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 14:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "48 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 48 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 48 by the 8 in the ones place\n8 * 8 + 0 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\n4 * 8 + 6 = 38 (carry 3, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 48 by the 8 in the ones place yields 384\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 384:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 * 23",
        "answer": "Multiply 51 and 23 step by step:\nMultiplying 51 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 51 by the 3 in the ones place yields 153\n\nMultiplying 51 by the 2 in the tens place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 51 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1020\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 153 + 1020:\n\nAdd 1020 and 153 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 5 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1173\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1173"
    },
    {
        "question": "30 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 30 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 30 by the 9 in the ones place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 9 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 30 by the 9 in the ones place yields 270\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 270:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "937 * 161",
        "answer": "Multiply 937 and 161 step by step:\nMultiplying 937 by the 1 in the ones place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 937 by the 1 in the ones place yields 937\n\nMultiplying 937 by the 6 in the tens place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n3 * 6 + 4 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\n9 * 6 + 2 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 937 by the 6 in the tens place yields 56220\n\nMultiplying 937 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 937 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 93700\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 937 + 56220 + 93700:\n\nAdd 56220 and 937 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 57157\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 57157 + 93700\nAdd 93700 and 57157 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 7 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 150857\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 150857"
    },
    {
        "question": "857 * 40",
        "answer": "Multiply 857 and 40 step by step:\nMultiplying 857 by the 0 in the ones place\n7 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 857 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 857 by the 4 in the tens place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\n8 * 4 + 2 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 857 by the 4 in the tens place yields 34280\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 34280:\n\nAdd 34280 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 8 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 34280\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 34280"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 66 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 66 by the 7 in the ones place\n6 * 7 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n6 * 7 + 4 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 66 by the 7 in the ones place yields 462\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 462:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "83 * 67",
        "answer": "Multiply 83 and 67 step by step:\nMultiplying 83 by the 7 in the ones place\n3 * 7 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n8 * 7 + 2 = 58 (carry 5, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 83 by the 7 in the ones place yields 581\n\nMultiplying 83 by the 6 in the tens place\n3 * 6 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n8 * 6 + 1 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 83 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4980\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 581 + 4980:\n\nAdd 4980 and 581 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 5 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5561\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5561"
    },
    {
        "question": "900 * 339",
        "answer": "Multiply 900 and 339 step by step:\nMultiplying 900 by the 9 in the ones place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 9 + 0 = 81 (carry 8, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 900 by the 9 in the ones place yields 8100\n\nMultiplying 900 by the 3 in the tens place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 900 by the 3 in the tens place yields 27000\n\nMultiplying 900 by the 3 in the hundreds place\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n0 * 3 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 900 by the 3 in the hundreds place yields 270000\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 8100 + 27000 + 270000:\n\nAdd 27000 and 8100 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 35100\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 35100 + 270000\nAdd 270000 and 35100 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 3 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 305100\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 305100"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 93 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 93 by the 3 in the ones place\n3 * 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 93 by the 3 in the ones place yields 279\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 279:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "33 * 24",
        "answer": "Multiply 33 and 24 step by step:\nMultiplying 33 by the 4 in the ones place\n3 * 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n3 * 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 33 by the 4 in the ones place yields 132\n\nMultiplying 33 by the 2 in the tens place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 33 by the 2 in the tens place yields 660\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 132 + 660:\n\nAdd 660 and 132 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 792\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 792"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 * 88",
        "answer": "Multiply 96 and 88 step by step:\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the ones place\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n9 * 8 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the ones place yields 768\n\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the tens place\n6 * 8 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n9 * 8 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 96 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7680\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 768 + 7680:\n\nAdd 7680 and 768 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 7 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8448\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8448"
    },
    {
        "question": "95 * 86",
        "answer": "Multiply 95 and 86 step by step:\nMultiplying 95 by the 6 in the ones place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n9 * 6 + 3 = 57 (carry 5, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 95 by the 6 in the ones place yields 570\n\nMultiplying 95 by the 8 in the tens place\n5 * 8 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n9 * 8 + 4 = 76 (carry 7, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 95 by the 8 in the tens place yields 7600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 570 + 7600:\n\nAdd 7600 and 570 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8170\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8170"
    },
    {
        "question": "558 * 90",
        "answer": "Multiply 558 and 90 step by step:\nMultiplying 558 by the 0 in the ones place\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 558 by the 0 in the ones place yields 000\n\nMultiplying 558 by the 9 in the tens place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n5 * 9 + 7 = 52 (carry 5, remainder 2)\n5 * 9 + 5 = 50 (carry 5, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 558 by the 9 in the tens place yields 50220\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 000 + 50220:\n\nAdd 50220 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 2 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 0 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 50220\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 50220"
    },
    {
        "question": "915 * 386",
        "answer": "Multiply 915 and 386 step by step:\nMultiplying 915 by the 6 in the ones place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n1 * 6 + 3 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 915 by the 6 in the ones place yields 5490\n\nMultiplying 915 by the 8 in the tens place\n5 * 8 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n1 * 8 + 4 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n9 * 8 + 1 = 73 (carry 7, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 915 by the 8 in the tens place yields 73200\n\nMultiplying 915 by the 3 in the hundreds place\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n1 * 3 + 1 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 915 by the 3 in the hundreds place yields 274500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5490 + 73200 + 274500:\n\nAdd 73200 and 5490 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 4 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 5 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 7 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 78690\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 78690 + 274500\nAdd 274500 and 78690 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 8 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 7 + 7 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 3 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 353190\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 353190"
    },
    {
        "question": "753 * 625",
        "answer": "Multiply 753 and 625 step by step:\nMultiplying 753 by the 5 in the ones place\n3 * 5 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 1 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\n7 * 5 + 2 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 753 by the 5 in the ones place yields 3765\n\nMultiplying 753 by the 2 in the tens place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 753 by the 2 in the tens place yields 15060\n\nMultiplying 753 by the 6 in the hundreds place\n3 * 6 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n5 * 6 + 1 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\n7 * 6 + 3 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 753 by the 6 in the hundreds place yields 451800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 3765 + 15060 + 451800:\n\nAdd 15060 and 3765 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 7 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 18825\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 18825 + 451800\nAdd 451800 and 18825 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 8 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 1 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 4 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 470625\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 470625"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 * 28",
        "answer": "Multiply 97 and 28 step by step:\nMultiplying 97 by the 8 in the ones place\n7 * 8 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n9 * 8 + 5 = 77 (carry 7, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 97 by the 8 in the ones place yields 776\n\nMultiplying 97 by the 2 in the tens place\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n9 * 2 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 97 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1940\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 776 + 1940:\n\nAdd 1940 and 776 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 7 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2716\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2716"
    },
    {
        "question": "30 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 30 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 30 by the 8 in the ones place\n0 * 8 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 8 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 30 by the 8 in the ones place yields 240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 240:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "39 * 34",
        "answer": "Multiply 39 and 34 step by step:\nMultiplying 39 by the 4 in the ones place\n9 * 4 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n3 * 4 + 3 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 39 by the 4 in the ones place yields 156\n\nMultiplying 39 by the 3 in the tens place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n3 * 3 + 2 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 39 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1170\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 156 + 1170:\n\nAdd 1170 and 156 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 1 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1326\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1326"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 * 72",
        "answer": "Multiply 93 and 72 step by step:\nMultiplying 93 by the 2 in the ones place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 93 by the 2 in the ones place yields 186\n\nMultiplying 93 by the 7 in the tens place\n3 * 7 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n9 * 7 + 2 = 65 (carry 6, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 93 by the 7 in the tens place yields 6510\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 186 + 6510:\n\nAdd 6510 and 186 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 8 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6696\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6696"
    },
    {
        "question": "419 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 419 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 419 by the 2 in the ones place\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n1 * 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 419 by the 2 in the ones place yields 838\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 838:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "222 * 64",
        "answer": "Multiply 222 and 64 step by step:\nMultiplying 222 by the 4 in the ones place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 222 by the 4 in the ones place yields 888\n\nMultiplying 222 by the 6 in the tens place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n2 * 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\n2 * 6 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 222 by the 6 in the tens place yields 13320\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 888 + 13320:\n\nAdd 13320 and 888 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 8 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 14208\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 14208"
    },
    {
        "question": "78 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 78 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 78 by the 1 in the ones place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 78 by the 1 in the ones place yields 78\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 78:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 * 64",
        "answer": "Multiply 72 and 64 step by step:\nMultiplying 72 by the 4 in the ones place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 72 by the 4 in the ones place yields 288\n\nMultiplying 72 by the 6 in the tens place\n2 * 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 6 + 1 = 43 (carry 4, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 72 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4320\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 288 + 4320:\n\nAdd 4320 and 288 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 2 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4608\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4608"
    },
    {
        "question": "74 * 22",
        "answer": "Multiply 74 and 22 step by step:\nMultiplying 74 by the 2 in the ones place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 74 by the 2 in the ones place yields 148\n\nMultiplying 74 by the 2 in the tens place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 2 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 74 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1480\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 148 + 1480:\n\nAdd 1480 and 148 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 1 + 1 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1628\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1628"
    },
    {
        "question": "104 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 104 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 104 by the 8 in the ones place\n4 * 8 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n0 * 8 + 3 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 104 by the 8 in the ones place yields 832\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 832:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "829 * 663",
        "answer": "Multiply 829 and 663 step by step:\nMultiplying 829 by the 3 in the ones place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n2 * 3 + 2 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 829 by the 3 in the ones place yields 2487\n\nMultiplying 829 by the 6 in the tens place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n2 * 6 + 5 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n8 * 6 + 1 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 829 by the 6 in the tens place yields 49740\n\nMultiplying 829 by the 6 in the hundreds place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n2 * 6 + 5 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n8 * 6 + 1 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 829 by the 6 in the hundreds place yields 497400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2487 + 49740 + 497400:\n\nAdd 49740 and 2487 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 8 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 2 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 52227\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 52227 + 497400\nAdd 497400 and 52227 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 2 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 5 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 549627\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 549627"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 98 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 98 by the 1 in the ones place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 98 by the 1 in the ones place yields 98\n\nMultiplying 98 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 98 by the 1 in the tens place yields 980\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 98 + 980:\n\nAdd 980 and 98 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 9 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 0 + 1 = 10 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 0 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1078\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1078"
    },
    {
        "question": "33 * 20",
        "answer": "Multiply 33 and 20 step by step:\nMultiplying 33 by the 0 in the ones place\n3 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n3 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 33 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 33 by the 2 in the tens place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 33 by the 2 in the tens place yields 660\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 660:\n\nAdd 660 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 6 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 660\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 660"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 * 53",
        "answer": "Multiply 91 and 53 step by step:\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place yields 273\n\nMultiplying 91 by the 5 in the tens place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 91 by the 5 in the tens place yields 4550\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 273 + 4550:\n\nAdd 4550 and 273 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4823\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4823"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 58 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 58 by the 4 in the ones place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n5 * 4 + 3 = 23 (carry 2, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 58 by the 4 in the ones place yields 232\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 232:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "84 * 84",
        "answer": "Multiply 84 and 84 step by step:\nMultiplying 84 by the 4 in the ones place\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 4 + 1 = 33 (carry 3, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 84 by the 4 in the ones place yields 336\n\nMultiplying 84 by the 8 in the tens place\n4 * 8 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n8 * 8 + 3 = 67 (carry 6, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 84 by the 8 in the tens place yields 6720\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 336 + 6720:\n\nAdd 6720 and 336 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7056\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7056"
    },
    {
        "question": "189 * 17",
        "answer": "Multiply 189 and 17 step by step:\nMultiplying 189 by the 7 in the ones place\n9 * 7 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n8 * 7 + 6 = 62 (carry 6, remainder 2)\n1 * 7 + 6 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 189 by the 7 in the ones place yields 1323\n\nMultiplying 189 by the 1 in the tens place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 189 by the 1 in the tens place yields 1890\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1323 + 1890:\n\nAdd 1890 and 1323 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 2 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 1 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 3213\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3213"
    },
    {
        "question": "73 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 73 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 73 by the 9 in the ones place\n3 * 9 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n7 * 9 + 2 = 65 (carry 6, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 73 by the 9 in the ones place yields 657\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 657:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "683 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 683 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 683 by the 8 in the ones place\n3 * 8 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n8 * 8 + 2 = 66 (carry 6, remainder 6)\n6 * 8 + 6 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 683 by the 8 in the ones place yields 5464\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5464:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "58 * 39",
        "answer": "Multiply 58 and 39 step by step:\nMultiplying 58 by the 9 in the ones place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n5 * 9 + 7 = 52 (carry 5, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 58 by the 9 in the ones place yields 522\n\nMultiplying 58 by the 3 in the tens place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 3 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 58 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1740\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 522 + 1740:\n\nAdd 1740 and 522 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 5 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2262\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2262"
    },
    {
        "question": "69 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 69 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 69 by the 6 in the ones place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n6 * 6 + 5 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 69 by the 6 in the ones place yields 414\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 414:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 * 35",
        "answer": "Multiply 81 and 35 step by step:\nMultiplying 81 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 81 by the 5 in the ones place yields 405\n\nMultiplying 81 by the 3 in the tens place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 81 by the 3 in the tens place yields 2430\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 405 + 2430:\n\nAdd 2430 and 405 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2835\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2835"
    },
    {
        "question": "82 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 82 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 82 by the 8 in the ones place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 8 + 1 = 65 (carry 6, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 82 by the 8 in the ones place yields 656\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 656:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "82 * 74",
        "answer": "Multiply 82 and 74 step by step:\nMultiplying 82 by the 4 in the ones place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 82 by the 4 in the ones place yields 328\n\nMultiplying 82 by the 7 in the tens place\n2 * 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\n8 * 7 + 1 = 57 (carry 5, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 82 by the 7 in the tens place yields 5740\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 328 + 5740:\n\nAdd 5740 and 328 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 3 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6068\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6068"
    },
    {
        "question": "692 * 11",
        "answer": "Multiply 692 and 11 step by step:\nMultiplying 692 by the 1 in the ones place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 692 by the 1 in the ones place yields 692\n\nMultiplying 692 by the 1 in the tens place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 692 by the 1 in the tens place yields 6920\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 692 + 6920:\n\nAdd 6920 and 692 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 6 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 1 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 7 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 7612\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 7612"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 11 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 11 by the 5 in the ones place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 11 by the 5 in the ones place yields 55\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 55:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 * 41",
        "answer": "Multiply 56 and 41 step by step:\nMultiplying 56 by the 1 in the ones place\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 56 by the 1 in the ones place yields 56\n\nMultiplying 56 by the 4 in the tens place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 4 + 2 = 22 (carry 2, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 56 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2240\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 56 + 2240:\n\nAdd 2240 and 56 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 2 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2296\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2296"
    },
    {
        "question": "482 * 92",
        "answer": "Multiply 482 and 92 step by step:\nMultiplying 482 by the 2 in the ones place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n4 * 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 482 by the 2 in the ones place yields 964\n\nMultiplying 482 by the 9 in the tens place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n8 * 9 + 1 = 73 (carry 7, remainder 3)\n4 * 9 + 7 = 43 (carry 4, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 482 by the 9 in the tens place yields 43380\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 964 + 43380:\n\nAdd 43380 and 964 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 9 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 44344\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 44344"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 * 15",
        "answer": "Multiply 90 and 15 step by step:\nMultiplying 90 by the 5 in the ones place\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 90 by the 5 in the ones place yields 450\n\nMultiplying 90 by the 1 in the tens place\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 90 by the 1 in the tens place yields 900\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 450 + 900:\n\nAdd 900 and 450 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1350\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1350"
    },
    {
        "question": "76 * 4",
        "answer": "Multiply 76 and 4 step by step:\nMultiplying 76 by the 4 in the ones place\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n7 * 4 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 76 by the 4 in the ones place yields 304\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 304:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "477 * 96",
        "answer": "Multiply 477 and 96 step by step:\nMultiplying 477 by the 6 in the ones place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n7 * 6 + 4 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\n4 * 6 + 4 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 477 by the 6 in the ones place yields 2862\n\nMultiplying 477 by the 9 in the tens place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n7 * 9 + 6 = 69 (carry 6, remainder 9)\n4 * 9 + 6 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 477 by the 9 in the tens place yields 42930\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2862 + 42930:\n\nAdd 42930 and 2862 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 3 + 6 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 8 + 0 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 2 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45792\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 45792"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 93 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 93 by the 8 in the ones place\n3 * 8 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n9 * 8 + 2 = 74 (carry 7, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 93 by the 8 in the ones place yields 744\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 744:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "36 * 33",
        "answer": "Multiply 36 and 33 step by step:\nMultiplying 36 by the 3 in the ones place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n3 * 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 36 by the 3 in the ones place yields 108\n\nMultiplying 36 by the 3 in the tens place\n6 * 3 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n3 * 3 + 1 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 36 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1080\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 108 + 1080:\n\nAdd 1080 and 108 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1188\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1188"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 * 7",
        "answer": "Multiply 38 and 7 step by step:\nMultiplying 38 by the 7 in the ones place\n8 * 7 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\n3 * 7 + 5 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 38 by the 7 in the ones place yields 266\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 266:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "644 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 644 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 644 by the 2 in the ones place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 644 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1288\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1288:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "99 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 99 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 99 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n9 * 8 + 7 = 79 (carry 7, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 99 by the 8 in the ones place yields 792\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 792:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "425 * 317",
        "answer": "Multiply 425 and 317 step by step:\nMultiplying 425 by the 7 in the ones place\n5 * 7 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n2 * 7 + 3 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n4 * 7 + 1 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 425 by the 7 in the ones place yields 2975\n\nMultiplying 425 by the 1 in the tens place\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 425 by the 1 in the tens place yields 4250\n\nMultiplying 425 by the 3 in the hundreds place\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n2 * 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 425 by the 3 in the hundreds place yields 127500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2975 + 4250 + 127500:\n\nAdd 4250 and 2975 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 9 + 1 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 2 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 7225\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 7225 + 127500\nAdd 127500 and 7225 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 7 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 1 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 134725\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 134725"
    },
    {
        "question": "94 * 25",
        "answer": "Multiply 94 and 25 step by step:\nMultiplying 94 by the 5 in the ones place\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n9 * 5 + 2 = 47 (carry 4, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 94 by the 5 in the ones place yields 470\n\nMultiplying 94 by the 2 in the tens place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 94 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1880\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 470 + 1880:\n\nAdd 1880 and 470 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2350\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2350"
    },
    {
        "question": "928 * 916",
        "answer": "Multiply 928 and 916 step by step:\nMultiplying 928 by the 6 in the ones place\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\n2 * 6 + 4 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n9 * 6 + 1 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 928 by the 6 in the ones place yields 5568\n\nMultiplying 928 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 928 by the 1 in the tens place yields 9280\n\nMultiplying 928 by the 9 in the hundreds place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n2 * 9 + 7 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n9 * 9 + 2 = 83 (carry 8, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 928 by the 9 in the hundreds place yields 835200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 5568 + 9280 + 835200:\n\nAdd 9280 and 5568 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 6 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 5 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 14848\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 14848 + 835200\nAdd 835200 and 14848 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 4 + 1 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 1 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 8 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 850048\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 850048"
    },
    {
        "question": "68 * 25",
        "answer": "Multiply 68 and 25 step by step:\nMultiplying 68 by the 5 in the ones place\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n6 * 5 + 4 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 68 by the 5 in the ones place yields 340\n\nMultiplying 68 by the 2 in the tens place\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 68 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1360\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 340 + 1360:\n\nAdd 1360 and 340 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1700\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1700"
    },
    {
        "question": "188 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 188 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 188 by the 2 in the ones place\n8 * 2 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n8 * 2 + 1 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n1 * 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 188 by the 2 in the ones place yields 376\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 376:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "531 * 258",
        "answer": "Multiply 531 and 258 step by step:\nMultiplying 531 by the 8 in the ones place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n3 * 8 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n5 * 8 + 2 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 531 by the 8 in the ones place yields 4248\n\nMultiplying 531 by the 5 in the tens place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n3 * 5 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 1 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 531 by the 5 in the tens place yields 26550\n\nMultiplying 531 by the 2 in the hundreds place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 531 by the 2 in the hundreds place yields 106200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4248 + 26550 + 106200:\n\nAdd 26550 and 4248 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 4 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 30798\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 30798 + 106200\nAdd 106200 and 30798 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 1 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 136998\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 136998"
    },
    {
        "question": "44 * 27",
        "answer": "Multiply 44 and 27 step by step:\nMultiplying 44 by the 7 in the ones place\n4 * 7 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n4 * 7 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 44 by the 7 in the ones place yields 308\n\nMultiplying 44 by the 2 in the tens place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 44 by the 2 in the tens place yields 880\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 308 + 880:\n\nAdd 880 and 308 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1188\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1188"
    },
    {
        "question": "51 * 43",
        "answer": "Multiply 51 and 43 step by step:\nMultiplying 51 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 51 by the 3 in the ones place yields 153\n\nMultiplying 51 by the 4 in the tens place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 51 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2040\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 153 + 2040:\n\nAdd 2040 and 153 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2193\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2193"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 * 69",
        "answer": "Multiply 97 and 69 step by step:\nMultiplying 97 by the 9 in the ones place\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\n9 * 9 + 6 = 87 (carry 8, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 97 by the 9 in the ones place yields 873\n\nMultiplying 97 by the 6 in the tens place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n9 * 6 + 4 = 58 (carry 5, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 97 by the 6 in the tens place yields 5820\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 873 + 5820:\n\nAdd 5820 and 873 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 7 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6693\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6693"
    },
    {
        "question": "87 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 87 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 87 by the 6 in the ones place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n8 * 6 + 4 = 52 (carry 5, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 87 by the 6 in the ones place yields 522\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 522:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "79 * 68",
        "answer": "Multiply 79 and 68 step by step:\nMultiplying 79 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n7 * 8 + 7 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 79 by the 8 in the ones place yields 632\n\nMultiplying 79 by the 6 in the tens place\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\n7 * 6 + 5 = 47 (carry 4, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 79 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4740\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 632 + 4740:\n\nAdd 4740 and 632 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 3 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 6 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5372\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5372"
    },
    {
        "question": "119 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 119 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 119 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n1 * 8 + 7 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n1 * 8 + 1 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 119 by the 8 in the ones place yields 952\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 952:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 61 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 61 by the 2 in the ones place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 61 by the 2 in the ones place yields 122\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 122:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "542 * 409",
        "answer": "Multiply 542 and 409 step by step:\nMultiplying 542 by the 9 in the ones place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n4 * 9 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\n5 * 9 + 3 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 542 by the 9 in the ones place yields 4878\n\nMultiplying 542 by the 0 in the tens place\n2 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 542 by the 0 in the tens place yields 0000\n\nMultiplying 542 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n2 * 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n5 * 4 + 1 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 542 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 216800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4878 + 0000 + 216800:\n\nAdd 4878 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 8 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4878\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 4878 + 216800\nAdd 216800 and 4878 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 4 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 1 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 2 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 2 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 221678\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 221678"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 * 59",
        "answer": "Multiply 71 and 59 step by step:\nMultiplying 71 by the 9 in the ones place\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n7 * 9 + 0 = 63 (carry 6, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 71 by the 9 in the ones place yields 639\n\nMultiplying 71 by the 5 in the tens place\n1 * 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 71 by the 5 in the tens place yields 3550\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 639 + 3550:\n\nAdd 3550 and 639 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 3 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 6 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4189\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4189"
    },
    {
        "question": "806 * 5",
        "answer": "Multiply 806 and 5 step by step:\nMultiplying 806 by the 5 in the ones place\n6 * 5 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n0 * 5 + 3 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 806 by the 5 in the ones place yields 4030\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4030:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "718 * 49",
        "answer": "Multiply 718 and 49 step by step:\nMultiplying 718 by the 9 in the ones place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n1 * 9 + 7 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n7 * 9 + 1 = 64 (carry 6, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 718 by the 9 in the ones place yields 6462\n\nMultiplying 718 by the 4 in the tens place\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\n1 * 4 + 3 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 718 by the 4 in the tens place yields 28720\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 6462 + 28720:\n\nAdd 28720 and 6462 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 4 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 35182\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 35182"
    },
    {
        "question": "41 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 41 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 41 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 41 by the 3 in the ones place yields 123\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 123:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "869 * 18",
        "answer": "Multiply 869 and 18 step by step:\nMultiplying 869 by the 8 in the ones place\n9 * 8 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n6 * 8 + 7 = 55 (carry 5, remainder 5)\n8 * 8 + 5 = 69 (carry 6, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 869 by the 8 in the ones place yields 6952\n\nMultiplying 869 by the 1 in the tens place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 869 by the 1 in the tens place yields 8690\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 6952 + 8690:\n\nAdd 8690 and 6952 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 9 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 6 + 1 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 15642\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 15642"
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 11 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 11 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 11 by the 3 in the ones place yields 33\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 33:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 * 8",
        "answer": "Multiply 45 and 8 step by step:\nMultiplying 45 by the 8 in the ones place\n5 * 8 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n4 * 8 + 4 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 45 by the 8 in the ones place yields 360\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 360:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "97 * 15",
        "answer": "Multiply 97 and 15 step by step:\nMultiplying 97 by the 5 in the ones place\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\n9 * 5 + 3 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 97 by the 5 in the ones place yields 485\n\nMultiplying 97 by the 1 in the tens place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 97 by the 1 in the tens place yields 970\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 485 + 970:\n\nAdd 970 and 485 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 8 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 4 + 1 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1455\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1455"
    },
    {
        "question": "44 * 39",
        "answer": "Multiply 44 and 39 step by step:\nMultiplying 44 by the 9 in the ones place\n4 * 9 + 0 = 36 (carry 3, remainder 6)\n4 * 9 + 3 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 44 by the 9 in the ones place yields 396\n\nMultiplying 44 by the 3 in the tens place\n4 * 3 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n4 * 3 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 44 by the 3 in the tens place yields 1320\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 396 + 1320:\n\nAdd 1320 and 396 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 3 + 1 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1716\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1716"
    },
    {
        "question": "804 * 56",
        "answer": "Multiply 804 and 56 step by step:\nMultiplying 804 by the 6 in the ones place\n4 * 6 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n0 * 6 + 2 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n8 * 6 + 0 = 48 (carry 4, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 804 by the 6 in the ones place yields 4824\n\nMultiplying 804 by the 5 in the tens place\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n0 * 5 + 2 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 804 by the 5 in the tens place yields 40200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4824 + 40200:\n\nAdd 40200 and 4824 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 8 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 4 + 1 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 45024\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 45024"
    },
    {
        "question": "774 * 41",
        "answer": "Multiply 774 and 41 step by step:\nMultiplying 774 by the 1 in the ones place\n4 * 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 774 by the 1 in the ones place yields 774\n\nMultiplying 774 by the 4 in the tens place\n4 * 4 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n7 * 4 + 1 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\n7 * 4 + 2 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 774 by the 4 in the tens place yields 30960\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 774 + 30960:\n\nAdd 30960 and 774 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 7 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 7 + 1 = 17 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 0 + 1 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 3 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 31734\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 31734"
    },
    {
        "question": "89 * 50",
        "answer": "Multiply 89 and 50 step by step:\nMultiplying 89 by the 0 in the ones place\n9 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n8 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 89 by the 0 in the ones place yields 00\n\nMultiplying 89 by the 5 in the tens place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n8 * 5 + 4 = 44 (carry 4, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 89 by the 5 in the tens place yields 4450\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 00 + 4450:\n\nAdd 4450 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 5 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4450\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4450"
    },
    {
        "question": "554 * 205",
        "answer": "Multiply 554 and 205 step by step:\nMultiplying 554 by the 5 in the ones place\n4 * 5 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n5 * 5 + 2 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n5 * 5 + 2 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 554 by the 5 in the ones place yields 2770\n\nMultiplying 554 by the 0 in the tens place\n4 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n5 * 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 554 by the 0 in the tens place yields 0000\n\nMultiplying 554 by the 2 in the hundreds place\n4 * 2 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n5 * 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 554 by the 2 in the hundreds place yields 110800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 2770 + 0000 + 110800:\n\nAdd 2770 and 0 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the tens, so we write down the 7 from the tens spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundreds: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 7 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2770\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 2770 + 110800\nAdd 110800 and 2770 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 7 + 0 = 15 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 0 + 2 + 1 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 1 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 1 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 113570\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 113570"
    },
    {
        "question": "682 * 159",
        "answer": "Multiply 682 and 159 step by step:\nMultiplying 682 by the 9 in the ones place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n8 * 9 + 1 = 73 (carry 7, remainder 3)\n6 * 9 + 7 = 61 (carry 6, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 682 by the 9 in the ones place yields 6138\n\nMultiplying 682 by the 5 in the tens place\n2 * 5 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n8 * 5 + 1 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\n6 * 5 + 4 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 682 by the 5 in the tens place yields 34100\n\nMultiplying 682 by the 1 in the hundreds place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 682 by the 1 in the hundreds place yields 68200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 6138 + 34100 + 68200:\n\nAdd 34100 and 6138 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 6 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 4 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 40238\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 40238 + 68200\nAdd 68200 and 40238 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ten thousands place)\nThe final answer is 108438\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 108438"
    },
    {
        "question": "71 * 68",
        "answer": "Multiply 71 and 68 step by step:\nMultiplying 71 by the 8 in the ones place\n1 * 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n7 * 8 + 0 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 71 by the 8 in the ones place yields 568\n\nMultiplying 71 by the 6 in the tens place\n1 * 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 71 by the 6 in the tens place yields 4260\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 568 + 4260:\n\nAdd 4260 and 568 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 5 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 4 + 0 + 0 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 4 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 4828\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 4828"
    },
    {
        "question": "91 * 3",
        "answer": "Multiply 91 and 3 step by step:\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place\n1 * 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 91 by the 3 in the ones place yields 273\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 273:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 * 49",
        "answer": "Multiply 61 and 49 step by step:\nMultiplying 61 by the 9 in the ones place\n1 * 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 61 by the 9 in the ones place yields 549\n\nMultiplying 61 by the 4 in the tens place\n1 * 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n6 * 4 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 61 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2440\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 549 + 2440:\n\nAdd 2440 and 549 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 9 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 4 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 5 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 2 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 2989\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 2989"
    },
    {
        "question": "61 * 2",
        "answer": "Multiply 61 and 2 step by step:\nMultiplying 61 by the 2 in the ones place\n1 * 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 61 by the 2 in the ones place yields 122\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 122:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 15 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 15 by the 9 in the ones place\n5 * 9 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n1 * 9 + 4 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 15 by the 9 in the ones place yields 135\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 135:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "85 * 43",
        "answer": "Multiply 85 and 43 step by step:\nMultiplying 85 by the 3 in the ones place\n5 * 3 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n8 * 3 + 1 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 85 by the 3 in the ones place yields 255\n\nMultiplying 85 by the 4 in the tens place\n5 * 4 + 0 = 20 (carry 2, remainder 0)\n8 * 4 + 2 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 85 by the 4 in the tens place yields 3400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 255 + 3400:\n\nAdd 3400 and 255 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3655\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3655"
    },
    {
        "question": "66 * 22",
        "answer": "Multiply 66 and 22 step by step:\nMultiplying 66 by the 2 in the ones place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 66 by the 2 in the ones place yields 132\n\nMultiplying 66 by the 2 in the tens place\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n6 * 2 + 1 = 13 (carry 1, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 66 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1320\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 132 + 1320:\n\nAdd 1320 and 132 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 3 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 1 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1452\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1452"
    },
    {
        "question": "59 * 53",
        "answer": "Multiply 59 and 53 step by step:\nMultiplying 59 by the 3 in the ones place\n9 * 3 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n5 * 3 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 59 by the 3 in the ones place yields 177\n\nMultiplying 59 by the 5 in the tens place\n9 * 5 + 0 = 45 (carry 4, remainder 5)\n5 * 5 + 4 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 59 by the 5 in the tens place yields 2950\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 177 + 2950:\n\nAdd 2950 and 177 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3127\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3127"
    },
    {
        "question": "952 * 912",
        "answer": "Multiply 952 and 912 step by step:\nMultiplying 952 by the 2 in the ones place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n9 * 2 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 952 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1904\n\nMultiplying 952 by the 1 in the tens place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n5 * 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0, remainder 5)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 952 by the 1 in the tens place yields 9520\n\nMultiplying 952 by the 9 in the hundreds place\n2 * 9 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n5 * 9 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\n9 * 9 + 4 = 85 (carry 8, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 952 by the 9 in the hundreds place yields 856800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1904 + 9520 + 856800:\n\nAdd 9520 and 1904 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 0 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 9 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 11424\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 11424 + 856800\nAdd 856800 and 11424 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 1 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 8 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 868224\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 868224"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 * 62",
        "answer": "Multiply 90 and 62 step by step:\nMultiplying 90 by the 2 in the ones place\n0 * 2 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 90 by the 2 in the ones place yields 180\n\nMultiplying 90 by the 6 in the tens place\n0 * 6 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n9 * 6 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 90 by the 6 in the tens place yields 5400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 180 + 5400:\n\nAdd 5400 and 180 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 8 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 5 + 0 + 0 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 5 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 5580\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 5580"
    },
    {
        "question": "817 * 416",
        "answer": "Multiply 817 and 416 step by step:\nMultiplying 817 by the 6 in the ones place\n7 * 6 + 0 = 42 (carry 4, remainder 2)\n1 * 6 + 4 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\n8 * 6 + 1 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 817 by the 6 in the ones place yields 4902\n\nMultiplying 817 by the 1 in the tens place\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 817 by the 1 in the tens place yields 8170\n\nMultiplying 817 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\n1 * 4 + 2 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n8 * 4 + 0 = 32 (carry 3, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 817 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 326800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4902 + 8170 + 326800:\n\nAdd 8170 and 4902 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 0 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 4 + 1 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 13072\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 13072 + 326800\nAdd 326800 and 13072 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 2 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 3 + 0 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 2 + 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 3 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 339872\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 339872"
    },
    {
        "question": "33 * 28",
        "answer": "Multiply 33 and 28 step by step:\nMultiplying 33 by the 8 in the ones place\n3 * 8 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n3 * 8 + 2 = 26 (carry 2, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 33 by the 8 in the ones place yields 264\n\nMultiplying 33 by the 2 in the tens place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 33 by the 2 in the tens place yields 660\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 264 + 660:\n\nAdd 660 and 264 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 2 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 924\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 924"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 * 91",
        "answer": "Multiply 93 and 91 step by step:\nMultiplying 93 by the 1 in the ones place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 93 by the 1 in the ones place yields 93\n\nMultiplying 93 by the 9 in the tens place\n3 * 9 + 0 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\n9 * 9 + 2 = 83 (carry 8, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 93 by the 9 in the tens place yields 8370\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 93 + 8370:\n\nAdd 8370 and 93 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 7 + 9 + 0 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 4 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 0 = 8 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 8 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 8463\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 8463"
    },
    {
        "question": "28 * 15",
        "answer": "Multiply 28 and 15 step by step:\nMultiplying 28 by the 5 in the ones place\n8 * 5 + 0 = 40 (carry 4, remainder 0)\n2 * 5 + 4 = 14 (carry 1, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 28 by the 5 in the ones place yields 140\n\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the tens place\n8 * 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0, remainder 8)\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 28 by the 1 in the tens place yields 280\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 140 + 280:\n\nAdd 280 and 140 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 8 + 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 1 + 1 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 420\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 420"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 * 45",
        "answer": "Multiply 70 and 45 step by step:\nMultiplying 70 by the 5 in the ones place\n0 * 5 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 5 + 0 = 35 (carry 3, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 70 by the 5 in the ones place yields 350\n\nMultiplying 70 by the 4 in the tens place\n0 * 4 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n7 * 4 + 0 = 28 (carry 2, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 70 by the 4 in the tens place yields 2800\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 350 + 2800:\n\nAdd 2800 and 350 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 3 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 0 + 1 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3150\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3150"
    },
    {
        "question": "38 * 9",
        "answer": "Multiply 38 and 9 step by step:\nMultiplying 38 by the 9 in the ones place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n3 * 9 + 7 = 34 (carry 3, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 38 by the 9 in the ones place yields 342\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 342:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "935 * 565",
        "answer": "Multiply 935 and 565 step by step:\nMultiplying 935 by the 5 in the ones place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n3 * 5 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n9 * 5 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 935 by the 5 in the ones place yields 4675\n\nMultiplying 935 by the 6 in the tens place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n3 * 6 + 3 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n9 * 6 + 2 = 56 (carry 5, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 935 by the 6 in the tens place yields 56100\n\nMultiplying 935 by the 5 in the hundreds place\n5 * 5 + 0 = 25 (carry 2, remainder 5)\n3 * 5 + 2 = 17 (carry 1, remainder 7)\n9 * 5 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 935 by the 5 in the hundreds place yields 467500\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 4675 + 56100 + 467500:\n\nAdd 56100 and 4675 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 6 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 4 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 60775\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 60775 + 467500\nAdd 467500 and 60775 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 5 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 7 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 7 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 0 + 1 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 6 + 6 + 0 = 12 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 5 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 528275\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 528275"
    },
    {
        "question": "93 * 71",
        "answer": "Multiply 93 and 71 step by step:\nMultiplying 93 by the 1 in the ones place\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 93 by the 1 in the ones place yields 93\n\nMultiplying 93 by the 7 in the tens place\n3 * 7 + 0 = 21 (carry 2, remainder 1)\n9 * 7 + 2 = 65 (carry 6, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 93 by the 7 in the tens place yields 6510\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 93 + 6510:\n\nAdd 6510 and 93 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 1 + 9 + 0 = 10 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundreds, so we write down the 6 from the hundreds spot from the top number)\nAdding the thousands: 6 + 0 + 0 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 6 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 6603\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 6603"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 * 93",
        "answer": "Multiply 98 and 93 step by step:\nMultiplying 98 by the 3 in the ones place\n8 * 3 + 0 = 24 (carry 2, remainder 4)\n9 * 3 + 2 = 29 (carry 2, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 98 by the 3 in the ones place yields 294\n\nMultiplying 98 by the 9 in the tens place\n8 * 9 + 0 = 72 (carry 7, remainder 2)\n9 * 9 + 7 = 88 (carry 8, remainder 8)\nMultiplying 98 by the 9 in the tens place yields 8820\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 294 + 8820:\n\nAdd 8820 and 294 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 8 + 2 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 8 + 0 + 1 = 9 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 9 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 9114\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 9114"
    },
    {
        "question": "52 * 28",
        "answer": "Multiply 52 and 28 step by step:\nMultiplying 52 by the 8 in the ones place\n2 * 8 + 0 = 16 (carry 1, remainder 6)\n5 * 8 + 1 = 41 (carry 4, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 52 by the 8 in the ones place yields 416\n\nMultiplying 52 by the 2 in the tens place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n5 * 2 + 0 = 10 (carry 1, remainder 0)\nMultiplying 52 by the 2 in the tens place yields 1040\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 416 + 1040:\n\nAdd 1040 and 416 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 1 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 1456\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1456"
    },
    {
        "question": "19 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 19 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 19 by the 1 in the ones place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n1 * 1 + 0 = 1 (carry 0, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 19 by the 1 in the ones place yields 19\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 19:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "63 * 52",
        "answer": "Multiply 63 and 52 step by step:\nMultiplying 63 by the 2 in the ones place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\nMultiplying 63 by the 2 in the ones place yields 126\n\nMultiplying 63 by the 5 in the tens place\n3 * 5 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n6 * 5 + 1 = 31 (carry 3, remainder 1)\nMultiplying 63 by the 5 in the tens place yields 3150\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 126 + 3150:\n\nAdd 3150 and 126 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 2 + 0 = 7 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 7 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 1 + 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 2 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 3 + 0 + 0 = 3 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the thousands, so we write down the 3 from the thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 3276\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 3276"
    },
    {
        "question": "39 * 1",
        "answer": "Multiply 39 and 1 step by step:\nMultiplying 39 by the 1 in the ones place\n9 * 1 + 0 = 9 (carry 0, remainder 9)\n3 * 1 + 0 = 3 (carry 0, remainder 3)\nMultiplying 39 by the 1 in the ones place yields 39\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 39:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 * 6",
        "answer": "Multiply 45 and 6 step by step:\nMultiplying 45 by the 6 in the ones place\n5 * 6 + 0 = 30 (carry 3, remainder 0)\n4 * 6 + 3 = 27 (carry 2, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 45 by the 6 in the ones place yields 270\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 270:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 * 19",
        "answer": "Multiply 60 and 19 step by step:\nMultiplying 60 by the 9 in the ones place\n0 * 9 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 9 + 0 = 54 (carry 5, remainder 4)\nMultiplying 60 by the 9 in the ones place yields 540\n\nMultiplying 60 by the 1 in the tens place\n0 * 1 + 0 = 0 (carry 0, remainder 0)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\nMultiplying 60 by the 1 in the tens place yields 600\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 540 + 600:\n\nAdd 600 and 540 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 0 + 0 = 0 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 0 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nThe final answer is 1140\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 1140"
    },
    {
        "question": "993 * 452",
        "answer": "Multiply 993 and 452 step by step:\nMultiplying 993 by the 2 in the ones place\n3 * 2 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n9 * 2 + 0 = 18 (carry 1, remainder 8)\n9 * 2 + 1 = 19 (carry 1, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 993 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1986\n\nMultiplying 993 by the 5 in the tens place\n3 * 5 + 0 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\n9 * 5 + 1 = 46 (carry 4, remainder 6)\n9 * 5 + 4 = 49 (carry 4, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 993 by the 5 in the tens place yields 49650\n\nMultiplying 993 by the 4 in the hundreds place\n3 * 4 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n9 * 4 + 1 = 37 (carry 3, remainder 7)\n9 * 4 + 3 = 39 (carry 3, remainder 9)\nMultiplying 993 by the 4 in the hundreds place yields 397200\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1986 + 49650 + 397200:\n\nAdd 49650 and 1986 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 5 + 8 + 0 = 13 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 9 + 1 = 16 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 9 + 1 + 1 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 4 + 0 + 1 = 5 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 5 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 51636\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 51636 + 397200\nAdd 397200 and 51636 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 6 + 0 = 6 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 6 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 3 + 0 = 3 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 3 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 2 + 6 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 0 = 8 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 8 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 9 + 5 + 0 = 14 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ten thousands place)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 3 + 0 + 1 = 4 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 4 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 448836\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 448836"
    },
    {
        "question": "762 * 212",
        "answer": "Multiply 762 and 212 step by step:\nMultiplying 762 by the 2 in the ones place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 762 by the 2 in the ones place yields 1524\n\nMultiplying 762 by the 1 in the tens place\n2 * 1 + 0 = 2 (carry 0, remainder 2)\n6 * 1 + 0 = 6 (carry 0, remainder 6)\n7 * 1 + 0 = 7 (carry 0, remainder 7)\nMultiplying 762 by the 1 in the tens place yields 7620\n\nMultiplying 762 by the 2 in the hundreds place\n2 * 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0, remainder 4)\n6 * 2 + 0 = 12 (carry 1, remainder 2)\n7 * 2 + 1 = 15 (carry 1, remainder 5)\nMultiplying 762 by the 2 in the hundreds place yields 152400\n\nAdding all of our intermediate solutions together 1524 + 7620 + 152400:\n\nAdd 7620 and 1524 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 2 + 2 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 6 + 5 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 7 + 1 + 1 = 9 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 9 at the thousands place)\nThe final answer is 9144\n\nAfter adding the intermediates now are 9144 + 152400\nAdd 152400 and 9144 step by step:\nAdding the ones: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the ones place)\nAdding the tens: 0 + 4 + 0 = 4 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 4 at the tens place)\nAdding the hundreds: 4 + 1 + 0 = 5 (carry 0 to the next pair, and we write down 5 at the hundreds place)\nAdding the thousands: 2 + 9 + 0 = 11 (carry 1 to the next pair, and we write down 1 at the thousands place)\nAdding the ten thousands: 5 + 0 + 1 = 6 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the ten thousands, so we write down the 6 from the ten thousands spot from the top number)\nAdding the hundred thousands: 1 + 0 + 0 = 1 (There are no digits in the smaller number greater greater than the hundred thousands, so we write down the 1 from the hundred thousands spot from the top number)\nThe final answer is 161544\n\nAdding all of the intermediates results in the final solution of: 161544"
    }
]